
<artists>

 <artist>
  <name>Samiyyah Manning</name>
  <slug>samiyyah-manning</slug>
  <tag></tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Samiyyah Manning, better known as “Ms. Me-Me,” has made a name for herself after only being on the comedy scene for a year and a half. The Washington D.C. native, who resides in SE Maryland, was influenced by comediennes such as: Sommore and Monique, uses her unique sarcasm, quick wit, and unexpected humor to catch her audience pleasantly off guard. Her ability to make jokes based on her life, as well as her improvisational skills, being a single mother of three children, and an ex-wife, she has a lot to say and brings the truth to what she speaks. She is a regular at places such as The Comedy Factory, The Brightwood Bistro, My Place, and countless other places in D.C., Maryland, and Virginia. In November of 2010, she opened up for Cedric The Entertainer at the D.C. Convention Center. Currently she has her own comedy room every Wednesday at the Fab 5 VIP Lounge in Clinton, MD., and will soon be a host on the upcoming online radio show High Society Radio. Ms. Me-Me has been dubbed the “Diva of Comedy” in the D.C., Maryland, and Virginia areas and lives up to the name “Diva of Comedy”. o come see the answer to the question “What the hell is so damn funny???”
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo></photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Kandace Saunders</name>
  <slug>kandace-saunders</slug>
  <tag></tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>While growing up on the outskirts of Aberdeen Proving Ground, MD. Kandace decided she would rather write jokes than play with ordnance. Kandace then used those jokes to entertain classmates and family members. In 2005, while employed at the Improv in Baltimore, Kandace began her career as a standup comedian. Kandace’s sarcasm and quick wit, coupled with her ability to turn life experiences into “extremely laughable situations”, keep audiences guessing, (and laughing) at every turn. Her unique brand of comedy has allowed her to work with Pablo Francisco, Tony Woods, and other big name acts. Kandace recently performed for sold out crowds at the University of Maryland, and The Funnybone Comedy Club in Richmond, VA. Kandace can be seen performing at clubs and colleges up and down the east coast.</p>


      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Kandace_Saunders.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Anissa &#8216;Darkchild&#8217; Banes</name>
  <slug>anissa-darkchild-banes</slug>
  <tag></tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Philly’s own Anissa Bane A.K.A/ Ms. Darkchild, brings an energy, passion and vision to the comedy stage. Ms. Darkchild began her comedy career in Philadelphia in 1999 and has earned the title &#8220;The Princess of Comedy&#8221;.&nbsp; Ms. Darkchild can be seen regularly at open mics and comedy clubs throughout Philadelphia and much of the East Coast. She&#8217;s opened for T.K. Kirkland AND Roz G. at Philly&#8217;s LaffHouse, and ROCKED OUT at the Riot Act  for the DIVAS OF COMEDY show in November, as well as and PHILLY’S FINEST show in January! You don’t want to miss her!</p>


      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_DarkChild.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Brandon Wardell</name>
  <slug>brandon-wardell</slug>
  <tag></tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Brandon Wardell is a comedy wunderkind. Brandon Wardell has been in the stand-up comedy game for two years. Brandon Wardell has performed comedy jokes at SXSW and the Bridgetown Comedy Festival. Brandon Wardell lives in the Washington DC area, where he is truly the golden child of their comedy scene. 
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/IMG_9009.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Tommy Griffith</name>
  <slug>tommy-griffith</slug>
  <tag></tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Tommy Griffiths is host of the morning show on Washington, DC&#8217;s Classic Rock station Big 100.3, he&#8217;s opened for John Pinette, Ralphie May, Jeffery Ross&#8217; Roasting America coming soon to  Comedy Central, and hosted Charlie Sheen&#8217;s Torpedo of Truth Tour in DC in 2011. Tommy&#8217;s proudest moment was serving as a &#8220;guest security guard&#8221; on the Jerry Springer Show last May.</p>


      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/tommy_g_001.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Sampson McCormick</name>
  <slug>sampson-mccormick</slug>
  <tag></tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Sampson is an openly gay, black stand up comedian, writer and activist. He&#8217;s been touring the country, performing comedy since 2003, and includes tirelessly speaking out against homophobia and youth homelessness to his schedule as an activist. Although he fits into a &#8220;double minority&#8221; category, being black and gay, he refuses to be defined by these portions of his identity and performs mainstream venues and comedy clubs that include Broadway in New York, Arena Stage, DAR Constitution Hall, College Campuses including Harvard University and University of Maryland, LGBT Pride Festivals, Churches, Theatres, Bars, Nightclubs, Strip clubs, STD Clinics, on one occassion a Funeral Home, and with many notable acts including Patti LaBelle and RuPaul. </p>

<p>He also self produced a wildy successful run of his comedy concert, &#8220;Don&#8217;t Make Me Take Off My Earrings&#8221;, which was released as a live stand up album in 2011. He also has a comedy cooking show &#8220;Cooking: For Bitches Who Want to Keep Their Men Happy&#8221;, an online video blog and has written a book &#8220;Taboo Village: A Perspective on Being Gay in Black America&#8221;. He has also been seen on BET &amp; MTV and the Comcast Online Network. His comedy has been called &#8220;riveting, refreshing, conversational, bold, intelligent and honest&#8221; as his takes on life, religion, politics, sexuality, children and opinions leave audiences doubled over in laughter.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Sampson.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Shorty Ward</name>
  <slug>shorty-ward</slug>
  <tag></tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Born in Raritan, NJ and raised in Paterson, NJ comedian Shorty has been blazing the comedy scene for more than 10 years. Most recently, Shorty has filmed a television pilot for BET called &#8220;Busted&#8221; (aired April 12, 2008-check BET.com for more details), performed at the 2008 Los Angeles Comedy Festival, filmed an appearance for BET’S  NOTARIZED (aired New Year’s Eve 2008) and graced the stages of Talant&#8217;s (It’s Just Comedy Tour) and Hot 97&#8217;s DJ Cipha Sounds Comedy show at Comix in Manhattan, NY. Shorty is also a regular at the Wendy Williams Comedy Experience and  Ed Lover’s and Friends Comedy Show at Carolines. Shorty’s awesome talent was first noticed by Bill Belamy in (1997) at New Jersey&#8217;s Peppermint Lounge, Shorty has since molded his craft in to quick-witted, off-the-cuff, make-your-face-hurt kind of comedy enjoyed by all.<br />
&nbsp; <br />
Audiences throughout Canada, Bermuda and across the US have been left gasping for air following Shorty&#8217;s performances at Carolines (NY), Rascal&#8217;s (NJ), Miami Improv (FL), Jokes n&#8217; Notes (IL), LA Improv (CA), Laugh Factory (LA &amp; NY), and the FunnyBone Comedy Club (OH &amp; VA). Working alongside comedians Mike Epps, Michael Blackson, J. Anthony Brown, Bill Bellamy, Talent, Tony Roberts and Andrew Kennedy, just to name a few; Shorty continues to perfect his skill and leave audiences demanding more. Shorty attributes his success not only to his hard work and perseverance but also to the support of his friends and family, who continue to keep him highly motivated and focused on continued success. To contact Shorty or get information on upcoming performances please visit <a href="http://www.laffwithshorty.com">http://www.laffwithshorty.com</a> and <a href="http://www.myspace.com/kidcomedy">http://www.myspace.com/kidcomedy</a>.</p>


      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/shorty0794web.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Erin Conroy</name>
  <slug>erin-conroy</slug>
  <tag></tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Erin Conroy is a comedian and hockey fan from Buffalo NY.&nbsp; She has performed in clubs and colleges all over the East Coast, and currently runs the popular monthly comedy showcase &#8220;Motherboy&#8221; in New York City&#8217;s lower East Side.&nbsp; She is a co-host of the &#8220;Caligula&#8217;s Grotto&#8221; podcast, and thinks you look really nice today.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/headshot.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Mike James</name>
  <slug>mike-james</slug>
  <tag></tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Mike James comedy career began at the age of ten, when during show-and-tell he would recite jokes he heard on Letterman. Now that he’s all grown-up, he writes his own stuff. His smart, energetic act pokes holes in the faulty logic of others by combining razor sharp wit with outright absurdity. He’s opened for some of the best stand-ups in the world, including Todd Barry, Dana Gould, Ted Alexandro, and Nick Thune.</p>


      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/MikeJames.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Ryan Conner</name>
  <slug>ryan-conner1</slug>
  <tag></tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Originally from Washington, DC and based in New York City, Ryan Conner has a style of sharp story-telling that is &#8220;unique and extremely funny,&#8221; and he &#8220;has all the makings of a great stand-up,&#8221; according to Punchline Magazine.</p>

<p>His stand-up act has earned him a position as a contributing writer for Saturday Night Live&#8217;s Weekend Update for two seasons. Other credits have ranged from being in a pilot for the NFL Network, doing political comedy commentary for the BBC, and being featured in The Onion, The Washington Post and Time-Out NY. All this has led On-Tap Magazine, Washington DC&#8217;s leading entertainment guide, to label him a &#8220;stand-up comedy phenom.&#8221;</p>


      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/ryan_conner.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Sarah Newell</name>
  <slug>sarah-newell</slug>
  <tag></tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Sarah Newell is a former bikini and fashion model turned comedian and actress.&nbsp; Sarah has be seen on numerous TV shows, she played Sarah Barton on CSI Miami and has also been seen in King of Queens and Law Order,&nbsp; she can also be seen in the Justin Timberlake movie Friends with Benefits.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Sarahheadshot-32.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Ian Salmon</name>
  <slug>ian-salmon</slug>
  <tag></tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Ian Salmon is noted for his ability to keep his jokes fresh and unique, he weaves together experiences of travel, divorce and fatherhood, creating an enthralling web of comedy that will leave people in side-splitting laughter. With everything he’s done, the man has endless material to use for the reward of a good laugh. Ian has appeared on such TV shows as CSI NY, The Mentalist, Baggage and  in movies like Minority Report, Dark Eyes and has featured role in the movie Minkow staring Janes Caan, Ving Rhames and Mark Hamill he has aslo appeared on comedy shows such as Comedy Central and Showtime at The Apollo.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/IanSalmonHeadshot.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Matt Kazam</name>
  <slug>matt-kazam</slug>
  <tag></tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Matt Kazam is a veteran comic with 23 years experience who can be seen performing at all the nation’s top comedy clubs, theaters and casinos.&nbsp; Matt has performed stand-up comedy over 6,000 times in 42 states and 7 countries. He has made television appearances on NBC’s “Last Comic Standing”, Fox’s “Big Red Couch”, Comedy Central’s “Stand-Up Stand-Up”, VH-1’s “Fools For Love”, TLC’s “Two For Vegas”, The Discovery Channel’s “Lux List”. In addition, Matt has a comedy special entitled “Stand-Up and Sit-Down with Matt Kazam” currently airing on SIRIUSXM Satellite Radio. In Fall 2012 Matt will appear in his first ever 1 hour comedy special for Showtime called &#8220;Mac N Cheese&#8221;.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/mattkazamheadshot1.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Emma Willmann</name>
  <slug>emma-willmann</slug>
  <tag></tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Emma Willmann is a Stand - Up Comic and Entertainer based out of New York City. Originally from in rural Maine, Willmann discovered humor and comedy at an early age, as a way to distract herself from her rural surroundings. Becoming familiar with Stand – Up comedy in Boston, Willmann hit the scene hard - winning first place in The Boston Comedy Riots and making the finals in New England’s Funniest Comic Competition, both in 2010. Now based out of NYC, Willmann has been featured at major comedy clubs throughout Manhattan, appeared on Sirius XM Radio, in The Women in Comedy Festival, and alongside Jim Ganfighan, Jerry Sinfield, and Aziz Ansari, among many more.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/emma-willmann.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Lori Sommer</name>
  <slug>lori-sommer</slug>
  <tag>From Club MTV, Soul Train &amp; The Great 51st State of Long Island </tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>A showbiz triple threat&#8212;-Dancer, actress, stand-up comedian. Lori Sommer took an unlikely path to stand-up comedy that started with her being a hip hop dancer on shows like Club MTV and Soul Train.&nbsp; It brought her all the way to the bright lights of NYC where she traded her tap shoes for punch-lines. Lori never lost her dancing sensibilities as her comedy is rhythmic, majestic and prone to unexpected moves.</p>

<p>How exactly did this Italian girl from Long Island go from dancing on stage with DMX to performing on stage with a two drink minimum?&nbsp; Come to a show and find out!
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/LoriSommer2.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Randolph Terrance</name>
  <slug>randolph-terrance</slug>
  <tag></tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Originally from San Antonio, Texas and now making his home in the Washington DC area, Randolph is a consummate professional comedian with the ability to make any group of people laugh. As Randolph says, &#8220;I once read a quote from Woody Allen that sums up my feelings on stand-up: &#8216;If people come away relating to me as a person rather than just enjoying my jokes, if they come away wanting to hear me again no matter what I might talk about then I&#8217;m succeeding&#8217;&#8221;.</p>

<p>His universal appeal brings insight and poise to every show he performs. Randolph&#8217;s style has been said to be &#8220;strictly for the grown and sexy&#8221; pairing a smooth delivery with sharp, funny material.</p>


      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Randolph_Terrance_2.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Chico</name>
  <slug>chico</slug>
  <tag></tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>“I’m just an avid student of comedy and I love the passion, control and commitment it takes to become a great comedian.” Words spoken from a true comic at heart; making his mark in the comic era for over 8 years, CHICO has definitely helped push the comic scene into a new direction and has put his city on the map. Born and raised in Washington D.C., CHICO never would’ve imagined that he<br />
would become a comedian, but one incident changed his views of life forever. Being critically wounded and hospitalized due to a gunshot wound in early 2001, he spent a lot of time in the hospital bed contemplating on his life changes and the path to take next. “I was watching an episode of Comic View on BET, and it hit me; these comics aren’t really all that, I can do that.” After recouping from his injury, he decided to put his actions to a test, and tried out comedy for the first time appearing at D.C.’s infamous Takoma Station nightclub. From then on, he knew that this was a career to embark on.</p>

<p>CHICO began hosting Takoma Station weekly while working other gigs at other comedy venues in the D.C. area. Within 3 years, CHICO had already performed with D.C.’s best; such as Joe Clair and Red Grant just to name a few. He was blessed to be chosen to perform at Howard University’s Homecoming Comedy Show; then selected to appear on the second season of B.E.T Coming to the Stage, he’s also been featured outside of D.C. headlining at the Virginia House of Comedy, Richmond Funnybone and opening up for big music acts such as R&amp;B singer Pleasure P (of Pretty Ricky) and soul music legends THE WHISPERS and the list goes on. Chico loves giving back to his community hosting charity events such as Make-a-Wish. Chico was recently featured on BET&#8217;s 106&amp;Park for the Martin Luther King Memorial Tribute. He is also a comedic writer who writes for several comedians in Washington D.C area.</p>

<p>Currently, CHICO is still hosting and performing at venues worldwide, as well as writing and producing shows. He’s the lead writer for the sketch shows “DMV Comedy Sit Down” and “CHICOMENTARY,” and he’s one of the writers and commentators on “Reel Critics.” His future goals are to write for a wide range of comedians as well as for sitcoms. CHICO’s dogma is to “Always stay focused.”
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/ChicoHeadshot.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Seaton Smith</name>
  <slug>seaton-smith</slug>
  <tag>From Comedy Around Your Corner &amp; Up Your Street</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Applying smooth charisma to a layer of explosive energy, topped off with unforgettable characters sure to permanently reside in your brain, Seaton Smith leaves his audience in a state of comedic euphoria as he killed performing on Opie and Anthony “Virus” tour and the “New Faces” show at Just For Laughs Comedy Festival in Montreal. He also is a online phenom signing a deal with Sierra Mist where he was able to showcase his chops at producing the skit “Pimpin Referee.”
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Seaton_Smith.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Rachel Feinstein</name>
  <slug>rachel-feinstein</slug>
  <tag>From Season 7 of 'Last Comic Standing' &amp; Comedy Central Presents</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Rachel Feinstein grew up outside Washington DC, the daughter of a civil rights lawyer and a blues musician, giving her a keen eye for the absurd and unjust. She developed her hilarious, character-driven style by opening for her fatherʼs blues band as a kid and doing impressions of various loud and jarring relatives. Rachel was a finalist on Season 7 of Last Comic Standing, she was featured on <br />
Russell Simmon&#8217;s Presents Live at the El Ray, and she has had her own half hour special Comedy Central Presents Rachel Feinstein. </p>

<p>She has voiced various characters on Adult Swim&#8217;s Venture Brothers, comedycentral.comʼs Samurai Love God, and spike.comʼs Battle Pope. She has also appeared on VH1ʼs Jewtastic and CNNʼs Not Just Another Cable News Show. Rachel reviews hip hop as her Grandma &#8220;Ice Cold Rhoda: World&#8217;s Oldest Hater&#8221; (using a Star of David rating system) on comedycentral.com and for Cipha Sounds &amp; Rosenberg on New Yorkʼs Hot 97 FM. She is a supporting actress in the independent film Circus Maximus as well as in Peace After Marriage which won the Tribeca All Access Award. Rachel headlines comedy clubs and colleges across the country and she has performed internationally at the Just For Laughs comedy festival in Montreal, the Glasgow Comedy Festival, and the Amsterdam Comedy Festival. Her first comedy album will be released soon on Comedy Central Records. 
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/RachelFeinstein1Profile.jpeg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Robert Kelly</name>
  <slug>robert-kelly</slug>
  <tag>From The Tourgasm Tour and FX's Louie</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Robert Kelly has overcome many hardships in his life, all of which have made him the actor/comedian he is today. From his early days as a kid growing up in Boston in and out of Juvenile Hall, Kelly&#8217;s unique, honest take on his own life and his relationships makes his comedy clever, abrasive, funny, but yet refreshingly vulnerable.</p>

<p>He has been winning over audiences for the last 18 years. In addition to clubs and colleges nationwide, Kelly has traveled across the country in the &#8220;Tourgasm Live&#8221; tour with Dane Cook and Gary Gulman and has performed at the Just For Laughs Festival (Montreal 2010). He was recently seen as Louie CK&#8217;s brother Robbie on FX’s &#8220;Louie&#8221; and will soon be seen on CBS’s new drama “NYC 22” produced by Robert DeNiro. His other credits include Comedy Central Special &#8220;Comics Anonymous,&#8221; &#8220;Comedy Central Presents Robert Kelly,&#8221; &#8220;Tourgasm&#8221; on HBO, &#8220;Jimmy Kimmel Live&#8221; on ABC, &#8220;Premium Blend&#8221; on Comedy Central, &#8220;Tough Crowd with Colin Quinn&#8221; on Comedy Central, &#8220;The Carson Daly Show&#8221; on NBC, &#8221; “Law &amp; Order,” “Awesomely Oversexed&#8221; on VH1 and &#8220;The Jim Breuer Show&#8221; on MTV.</p>

<p>His movie credits include &#8220;Ghost Town,&#8221; &#8220;What Doesn&#8217;t Kill You,&#8221; &#8220;Children of Invention&#8221;, &#8220;Bachelor No. 2&#8221; and &#8220;Good Luck Chuck.&#8221; He also produced and starred in his first short film &#8220;Cheat “ which debuted at The Tribeca Film Festival in New York. He also has a book coming out based on the movie and a top rated podcast called “You Know What Dude?” that can be found on iTunes or riotcast.com
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/RobertKellyHeadshot2.jpeg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Mike Way</name>
  <slug>mike-way</slug>
  <tag>Local Favorite &amp; Winner of Funniest Person in Baltimore Award </tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Mike started doing standup in December 2005 and has since become one of the rising stars of the East Coast comedy scene. In addition to winning the DC Improv Showcase Finals and being a finalist at the Funniest Person in Baltimore contest, he has also performed at the DC, Boston, and California Comedy Festivals, the World Series of Comedy in Las Vegas and the Laughing Skull Festival in Atlanta.</p>

<p>Inspired by the observational comedy of Chris Rock and Jerry Seinfeld, Mike&#8217;s known for his relaxed, conversational delivery and well-crafted material with which everyone can relate. Mike&#8217;s jokes have been well-received all over the country, and so far it&#8217;s afforded him the opportunity to work with a wide variety of comedy luminaries, including Frank Caliendo, Pablo Francisco, John Oliver, Steve Byrne, Loni Love, Dave Attell, and standup legend Robert Klein.</p>


      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/MikeWayHeadshot.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Justin Daniels</name>
  <slug>justin-daniels</slug>
  <tag>From The Late Night Fiasco on Baltimore 98 Rock &amp; Comedy Festivals Countrywide</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>DC native Justin Daniels has an ever impressive list of comedy accomplishments. Host of the “The Late Night Fiasco” on Baltimore’s 98 Rock. Justin has been featured at the prestigious Just For Laughs Montreal Comedy Festival, Detroit Comedy Festival, and Boston Comedy Festival. He has also been seen on national Toyota Commercials, Lifetime Television, VH1, and writes for popular online comedy website PunchlineMagazine.com. This young star is on the come up!</p>


      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Justin-Schlegel-1.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Ted Alexandro</name>
  <slug>ted-alexandro</slug>
  <tag>From Every Late Night Talk Show &amp; Comedy Central</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Ted Alexandro was born and raised in Bellerose, NY, the second of five children. An artistic brood, the Alexandros performed community theater together almost every summer of Ted’s teenage years.</p>

<p>In 1992 Ted graduated with a Master’s Degree in Elementary Education from Queens College (“The Harvard of the CUNY system”; their words.) He started his comedy career as part of the duo “James &amp; Ted” with his good friend, Hollis James, whom he met at Queens College. Learn more about Ted at his website TedAlexandro.com.</p>

<p>Ted Alexandro was named one of the top comics working today by Time Out NY magazine.</p>

<p>Ted has performed on David Letterman, Conan O’Brien, Jimmy Kimmel, Craig Ferguson, The View, and he&#8217;s had two half-hour specials on Comedy Central. He&#8217;s also performed at the Bonnaroo Music Festival, Just For Laughs Festival and The New York Comedy Festival.</p>

<p>Ted has performed internationally in Jordan, Egypt, Kuwait, Hong Kong, South Korea, Singapore, Jakarta, England, Holland, Israel and Qatar, as well as appearing on television incredible shows such as “Oz”, “Dr. Katz” and “Louie”.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/TedAlexBioShot.jpeg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Jessica Kirson</name>
  <slug>jessica-kirson</slug>
  <tag>From Comedy Central's "Premium Blend" and Last Comic Standing</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Jessica Kirson&#8217;s unique style and captivating stage presence captures the attention of audiences and club bookers everywhere she performs. Her wide variety of characters brings a diverse energy to her routine. Once you have seen her amazing talent, it is easy to understand why she was selected to perform at the Hamptons, Toyota, Marshall&#8217;s Women in Comedy, Comedy Central&#8217;s South Beach and HBO&#8217;s Las Vegas comedy festivals. </p>

<p>She has been featured on various television shows, including, Comedy Central&#8217;s &#8220;Premium Blend&#8221; and &#8220;Fresh Faces,&#8221; Nickelodeon&#8217;s &#8220;Sixth in the Suburbs,&#8221; Noggin&#8217;s &#8220;LOL,&#8221; VH1&#8217;s &#8220;Awesomely Bad&#8221; Shows, Showtime&#8217;s, &#8220;White Boyz in the Hood,&#8221;.Oxygen&#8217;s premier game show &#8220;Can You Tell?,&#8221; Bravo&#8217;s &#8220;The Great Things About Being,&#8221; The Women&#8217;s Television Network, &#8220;She&#8217;s So Funny,&#8221; NBC&#8217;s &#8220;Last Comic Standing&#8221; Seasons 2 and 3, NBC&#8217;s &#8220;Last Call With Carson Daly&#8221;, and, &#8220;The Tonight Show with Jay Leno&#8221;. </p>

<p>Jessica performed at The Stockholm Comedy Festival in the fall of 2009 and her character voices can be heard in early 2010 in Nickelodeon&#8217;s &#8220;Bubbleguppies.&#8221; Jessica appeared in her own LOGO Special, &#8220;My Cookie&#8217;sGone.&#8221; and LOGO&#8217;s New Now Next Best of 2009.&nbsp; In late 2009, Jessica starred in a Television Pilot, considered to be a new breed of entertainment – The Reality Talk Show, entitled, THE JESSY K SHOW, executive produced by Zach Braff.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/JessicaKirsonHeadshot.gif</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Ali Wong</name>
  <slug>ali-wong</slug>
  <tag>From The Tonight Show, Fox's "Breaking In" &amp; Comedy Central's "Comics to Watch" List</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>ALI WONG is a stand-up comedian living in Los Angeles, CA. After SF Weekly selected her as “The Best Comedian of 2009″ and the SF Bay Guardian awarded her “Best of the Bay,” she decided that it was finally time to depart her hometown. Since then, Ali has performed on “The Tonight Show with Jay Leno”, the FOX series “Breaking In”, E!’s “50 Super Epic TV Moments”, and can be seen in Oliver Stone’s “Savages” to be released later this year. In 2010, Comedy Central listed Ali Wong as one of 7 “Comic’s to Watch” and Ali appeared in the 2011 Just for LaughsComedy Festival in Montreal, QC. She is currently a series regular on NBC’s “Are You There, Chelsea?”
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/AliWongHeadshotHiRes.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Dean Edwards</name>
  <slug>dean-edwards</slug>
  <tag>From the SNL Cast &amp; Russel Simmons Def Comedy Jam</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Actor/Comedian Dean Edwards has been making his mark in comedy following two successful seasons as a cast member on “Saturday Night Live.”&nbsp; With such memorable impressions as Don Cheadle, Michael Jackson and Denzel Washington, as well as such original characters as &#8220;Man in Elevator&#8221; and &#8220;Cop#2&#8221;. Dean has pushed himself to the limits of creativity and exhaustion.&nbsp; Always the multi-tasker, Dean found the momentum to juggle his SNL career, his numerous standup appearances and multiple television appearances on tv. Dean most recently appeared in Showtime’s “Comics Without Borders, the nine-week comedy series which showcased multi-cultural stand-up comedians.&nbsp; Dean also helped workshop and create the character of Donkey for nearly 2 years, leading up to Dreamworks’ SHREK THE MUSICAL on Broadway. </p>

<p>Dean has made several late night appearances, including “The Late Show with Craig Ferguson” and “Last Call with Carson Daly.”&nbsp; He is also a favorite and frequent guest on Byron Allen’s “Comic Unleashed,” and is frequently providing comedic commentary on various VH1 highlight shows. Director Malcolm Lee also chose Dean to finish Bernie Mac&#8217;s voice/ADR work on &#8220;Soul Men&#8221; after the comedian’s untimely death.&nbsp; Dean also provided the voiceover of Barack Obama&#8217;s on the CNN’s show, “D.L. Hughley Breaks the News”. </p>

<p>Born in the Bronx and raised throughout New York, Dean&#8217;s travels made it easy for him to communicate with all walks of life.&nbsp; After dividing his college career between classes and a 6-year term in the U.S. Army reserves, Dean ultimately made the choice to devote his career to comedy.&nbsp; Although his fellow soldiers loved his impressions of their drill sergeant, Dean spent many an afternoon doing push-ups to pay for his comedic talent.&nbsp; That talent paid off and Dean found his career after participating a college talent show.</p>

<p>Armed with a degree in communications, Dean became an in-demand comic, and landed his first big break on Russell Simmons&#8217; “Def Comedy Jam.” Though the show is renown for it&#8217;s blue humor, Dean found a way to break the traditional mold with his mainstream appeal. Subsequently, he was a featured comedian on “Showtime at the Apollo” a few years later. Dean followed his TV appearances by starring in numerous commercials, and also worked with Spike Lee on the hit feature film “The Original Kings of Comedy” </p>

<p>Edwards has since earned a reputation as a headlining favorite at comedy clubs and colleges across the country. An international sensation, Dean was chosen to perform at the Jozi, Cape Town and Durban Comedy Festival’s in Johannesburg, Cape Town, and Durban South Africa, as well as Saudi Arabia in late, 2009. More recently, Dean completed a tour of the Middle East, performing in front of more than 10,000 comedy fans: beginning in Cairo, Egypt and ending in Kuwait. </p>

<p>Next up, Dean’s vocal talents can be heard in Dreamworks upcoming Halloween classic, SCARED SHREKLESS and he can be seen starring in the upcoming independent feature, APRIL FOOLS. Dean’s first comedy CD, “REAL TALK WITH FAKE PEOPLE, Volume 1” debuted at the top of Itunes comedy charts in 2009 and he plans to release an hour long special/DVD with Salient Media in late-2010.</p>

<p>
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/EdwardsUse.jpeg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Jess Wood</name>
  <slug>jess-wood</slug>
  <tag></tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Jess Wood got her start in stand up comedy at New York Comedy Club, where she won the prestigious Best African-American Comedy Contest four times in a row. A veritable tornado on stage, Jess was the first white girl to perform on HBO’s Def Comedy Jam.&nbsp; Raised in the 1970’s by vegan hippies on welfare, embraced by Mexican gang members, and saved by stand-up comedy, she escaped violence, drug abuse, and prostitution by finding humor in all of it.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/JessWood.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Frank Liotti</name>
  <slug>frank-liotti</slug>
  <tag>From Law &amp; Order land and comedy clubs up and down the East Coast</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Frank Liotti has been seen playing criminals on multiple episodes of Law and Order: Criminal Intent, Law and Order: Special Victims Unit, Fox TV&#8217;s Jonny Zero, New York Undercover and Canturbury&#8217;s Law with Julianna Margulies.&nbsp; A graduate of Yale School of Drama (MFA) and SUNY Purchase (BFA), he landed the cover of The New York Times Arts and Leisure section for the production &#8220;Cats Talk Back&#8221;, a mocumentary of life as a cast member within the Broadway hit &#8220;Cats&#8221;, which was the winner of &#8220;Best Overall Production&#8221; in the 2003 NYC Fringe Festival and was revived this past Spring of 2011 in &#8220;Fringe Benefits: Best of the Fringe&#8221;.</p>

<p>He came in first place in a New York division of the prestigious Laughing Skull Comedy Festival two years in a row (headlined by Margaret Cho) and was a finalist in the Boston Comedy Festival NY Showcase as well as the Los Angeles Comedy Festival. Theatrically, he has performed at Yale Repertory Theatre, Rattlestick Theatre, Signature Theatre, Williamstown Theatre Festival, Stageworks/Hudson and others.&nbsp; He is in the upcoming film BearCity2, a TLA Release.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/frank_liotti.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Terrance the Comedian</name>
  <slug>terrance-the-comedian</slug>
  <tag>From The Riot Act MC &amp; Feature Family &amp; Your Local Mess Hall</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Washington DC native Terrance The Comedian first began his comedy career while serving in the United States Marines Corps in the mid-1990&#8217;s. He went above and beyond his duty to raise the morale and welfare of his fellow marines while stationed in Hawaii. He had access to a platform to voice his experiences of being separated from his family as well as his bond with his buddies by looking at day to day tasks/routines through a critical comedic eye. Upon returning home to civilian life, the scope of Terrance&#8217;s comedic material began to encompass his home-life, his hometown. This subject matter would eventually have a trickle down effect into every aspect of Terrance&#8217;s life experiences ranging from relationships (family &amp; romantic), social interaction, fatherhood, and his outlook on historical, national, and current world events. </p>

<p>Terrance diligently honed his comedy craftsmanship at open mics, talent shows, low or no paying gigs, whatever, in order to strengthen his stage presence AND fanbase. In fact, many fellow comedians and show producers have found out the hard way that &#8220;Terrance is Headline Material&#8221; and a tough act to follow. Terrence has the rare ability to elevate the intensity of a show that many peers voluntarily refuse to follow this talented comic who quickly establishes a rapor with any audience. </p>

<p>Terrance has established a strong presence in the of the regional comedy circuits; he has gained visibility via his comedy stand-up performances and hosting high profile events. 
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Terrence_8x10_pic.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Josh Wolf</name>
  <slug>josh-wolf</slug>
  <tag></tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Josh Wolf started doing comedy in Seattle 12 years ago.&nbsp; After moving to Los Angeles, his unique, honest and high energy style of storytelling made him an instant favorite at The Impov, The Laugh Factory and The World Famous Comedy Store.&nbsp; He also caught the eye of network TV.&nbsp; After doing his first one man show at the HBO Workspace, Josh landed a two year talent deal at 20th Century Fox and ABC for his own television show.&nbsp; Although his show never made the air, Josh learned a lot from watching people develop and write scripts. He learned so much that he decided to write one himself and he sold it to NBC.&nbsp; It was titled “Fairly Normal” and it, too, was to have Josh in the starring role.&nbsp; Being bit by the writing bug, Josh wrote on sitcoms for the next four years working on shows like “Yes, Dear”, Will Smith&#8217;s “All of Us” and “Cuts” starring Shannon Elizabeth. As he was wondering whether to go back for another season of writing, Josh decided he was tired of making other people funny and he jumped back into stand-up.&nbsp; He immediately got cast in Last Comic Standing and was on the season finale as one of the Last Comics Downloaded.&nbsp; Since then he has had acting roles on “All of Us”, he has a recurring role on “My Name is Earl” and he has done several hosting gigs for E!</p>

<p>He&#8217;s currently a regular on the hit E! series “Chelsea Lately” and is currently touring with Larry The Cable Guy and Chelsea Handler. Josh is also co-writing a feature for Sony and Happy Madison and hosts “The College Experiment,” a comedic weekly online college football show for Fox Sports. This year he will be touring with “The Comedians of Chelsea Lately.”
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/APPROVED_Josh_Wolf_Photo.jpeg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Rory Albanese</name>
  <slug>rory-albanese</slug>
  <tag>From The Daily Show and Lewis Black's "Red White and Screwed" Tour</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Rory Albanese is a four time Emmy-winning Executive Producer of The Daily Show with Jon Stewart. He has been a key part of The Daily Show since 1999. Rory is also an accomplished stand-up comedian. In the summer of 2006 he joined Lewis Black&#8217;s &#8220;Red White and Screwed&#8221; tour performing with Lewis all over the country. Most recently Rory has been seen performing with Daily Show correspondent John Oliver as well as headlining his own shows at clubs and colleges throughout the country. He will have his own half hour comedy special on Comedy Central in 2010. Albanese and John Oliver have just signed a film deal with Paramount Studios for an undisclosed sum.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/RoryAlbanese_051410.jpeg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Conrad Roth</name>
  <slug>conrad-roth</slug>
  <tag>From the City of Brotherly Love and Bill Bellamy's 'Who's Got Jokes'</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Conrad Roth is a stand-up comedian, writer, and actor originally from Philadelphia. His first national TV appearance came as a featured comedian on “Bill Bellamy’s - Who’s Got Jokes.”&nbsp; Conrad was handpicked to perform at the Boston Comedy Festival in 2008 and Salt Lake City’s Rocky Mountain Comedy Festival in 2011.&nbsp; He spent the last two years in San Francisco where he was a guest performer on the TV show “Creepy Movie Time,” headlined the world famous Purple Onion, and performed with Robin Williams.&nbsp; Conrad is a regular at Helium Comedy Club in Philadelphia and is currently creating his best work in New York City.&nbsp; </p>


      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/conrad_small_1_of_4.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Nikki Carr</name>
  <slug>nikki-carr</slug>
  <tag>From BET's  "Comic View" and "It's Showtime At The Apollo"</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Nikki Carr is a fresh face on the comedy scene.</p>

<p>Nikki has been all over the country learning her craft and developing her style, bringing audiences to their feet everywhere she goes, using truth, personality, poetry and music to completely enthrall her audience.&nbsp; </p>

<p>In just a short time, Nikki Carr has appeared on both BET&#8217;s Comic View and It&#8217;s Showtime at the Apollo.&nbsp; Nikki is well known for her comedic national anthem &#8220;Fat Girls.&#8221;&nbsp; Since making her television appearance on BET&#8217;s Comic View and It&#8217;s Showtime at the Apollo, Nikki Carr has been highly request by Colleges, University and Military Bases nationwide as well as worldwide.&nbsp; She has performed at Caroline&#8217;s in New York, The Comedy Zone in North Carolina, the Comedy Cabana in Myrtle Beach as well as many other clubs and colleges throughout the country. 
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Nikki_Carr.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Barry Rothbart</name>
  <slug>barry-rothbart</slug>
  <tag>From "The Tonight Show With Jay Leno" and Montreal's "Just For Laughs Festival!"</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Barry Rothbart is one of the young rising stars in comedy today, appearing recently on the Tonight Show with Jay Leno, starring in the new season of MTV’s “Punk’d” and landing a role as “Ben” on TNT’s “Men of A Certain Age”. He also co-wrote and starred in the IFC Channel show “Do Whatever”, as well as a series of national commercials including: Taco Bell, Honda and Miller Light. He was also named a “New Face” and “Best of the Fest” performer at the 2011 Just For Laughs Montreal Comedy Fest. In addition to stand up he has performed sketch and improv for several years at the UCB Theater in NY and LA and a one man character show in 2010.</p>

<p>
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Barry_Rothbart.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Tony Roberts</name>
  <slug>tony-roberts1</slug>
  <tag>From HBO’s “Def Comedy Jame,” “It's Showtime at the Apollo,” and “BET’S Comic View!” </tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Originally from Detroit, comedian, actor, writer and (sometimes) director Tony T. Roberts has been blessed with the coveted honor of being the, “Comedians-comedian.”&nbsp; The guy other performers love to watch work.&nbsp; His hilarious and refreshing energetic comedy style has granted him respect and created a huge demand for him on the comedy circuit, here in the states and abroad.&nbsp; Legendary comedian and sitcom director, David Steinberg, acclaimed Tony as, “A breakout talent” after witnessing Tony’s stand-up act and casting him as the lead in a series of funny burger king commercials he directed.</p>

<p>Tony has entertained audiences in some of the nations hottest comedy arenas including: Caroline’s, The Boston Comedy Club in New York City; The Peppermint Lounge in New Jersey; All Jokes Aside in both Chicago and Detroit; and The Comedy Act Theater in Los Angeles, just to name a few.&nbsp; But Tony’s television debut was on HBO’s “DEF COMEDY JAM”, followed by, “IT’S SHOWTIME AT THE APOLLO” and “BET’S COMICVIEW.”&nbsp; Early on, Tony received BET’s, ROBIN HARRIS AWARD, for Most Original Comic.</p>

<p>Soon after, HBO noticed Tony’s rising star and sent him to be featured at the 11th Annual U.S. Comedy Festival in Aspen Colorado.&nbsp; Upon returning, Tony was asked to return to the stage again for HBO, this time due to popular demand from his initial performance on HBO’s “DEF COMEDY JAM.” He would later appear in the Season premiere of Russell Simmons presents, Comedy at the El Rey for Comedy Central.&nbsp; Shortly After, Showtime Network and Salient Media placed there stamp of approval on  Tony, and agreed to tape and air his one hour comedy special, WIRED!&nbsp; Which aired in January 2010 and was the most sold comedy special of the year for Salient Media.&nbsp; The DVD is nationally featured in Walmart’s across the nation.</p>

<p>No Stranger to TV and Film, as an actor Tony has toured with a major theatre play, has been cast in a sketch comedy pilot for CBS entitled, JUST ADD WATER and has appeared in half a dozen movies. As a host, Tony recently hosted the vh1 pilot “Dance Slam Cam, ” and a Guest Lead in “Nite Tales” for BET and recently sat on the couch as guest on The Monique Show.&nbsp; Keep an eye on Tony Roberts…America’s next great talent!!!!
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Tony_Roberts.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Forrest Shaw</name>
  <slug>forrest-shaw</slug>
  <tag></tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Born in Miami and raised as an only child by a single hippie mother, Forrest Shaw got into stand-up comedy after a decade of life as a marine biologist. Saving manatees and counting seagrass by day, at night, Forrest dedicated himself to comedy, quickly working his way into regular club work. The influence of his former life as a biologist is evident in his material. Forrest delivers witty and clever anecdotes of his unorthodox life with a wry smile. He shares his own faults and failures with the audience in hopes that they too can find the lighter side of those things in life, which sometimes seem too much to bear. He also isn’t fond of stupid people. “Life is complicated and it shouldn’t be. We have created all of this stress and aggravation so the healthiest thing to do is make fun of ourselves and laugh about it.” </p>

<p>He was in the 2011/2010 Comedy Central South Beach Comedy Festival, the 2011 Laugh Detroit festival, the 2010 New York Underground Comedy Festival, the 2010 World Series of Comedy, the 2009 Just For Laugh’s Comedy Festival showcase, and Sleepless Night 2009. Forrest was a finalist for the 2007 Comedy Central Open Mic Fight and the 2007 Las Vegas Comedy Festival Lucky 21 showcase. He was a finalist for the 2007 Carnival Comedy Challenge and the winner of the 2006 South Florida New Faces Comedy Contest. Forrest is a member of The All Organic Comedy Tour. Forrest was featured in a commercial for the Florida Marlins 2009 campaign. He has also appeared in several other television ads, radio ads, on CBS4 news, and WSVN (Deco Drive).</p>


      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Forrest_photo_med.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Peter Bergen</name>
  <slug>peter-bergen</slug>
  <tag></tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Drawing on an array of life experiences that he wishes on nobody, PETE BERGEN will have you both laughing and thanking god that you did not have to go through what he has. He draws on his struggles with weight, addiction, social anxiety all while being the youngest in a big Irish family. Pete is also a faculty member at Washington Improv Theater and those improvisational skills in addition to a refreshing honesty and vulnerability have made him a hit while opening for comedians such as Jim Short and Bob Marley. Come see Pete and feel better about your life.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/pete_on_wall.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Erin Foley</name>
  <slug>erin-foley</slug>
  <tag>From Comedy Central, MTV, Fox, E!, and the Montreal Comedy Festival! </tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Erin Foley, a recent transplant to Los Angeles, spent years in New York City’s comedy clubs mastering the art of stand-up comedy while successfully pursuing her acting career. In New York and Los Angeles, Erin can be regularly seen at Gotham Comedy Club, Caroline&#8217;s on Broadway, The Improv, The Laugh Factory and Stand Up New York. She has performed at the Just for Laughs/TBS Comedy Festival in Chicago and the Marshall’s Women in Comedy Festival. Foley has had the honor of being selected to perform at the prestigious Montreal Comedy Festival three times. Not only has Erin had a successful career in comedy, but she also succeeds on the small screen with several national television commercial campaigns.</p>

<p>At the present time, Erin is filming a comedy pilot for E! Entertainment. She recently shot her own half hour comedy special for Comedy Central and has taped Chelsea Lately and The Kilborn File on FOX. Simultaneously, Erin has enjoyed success in the field of acting. She can be seen in the short films “Cried Suicide” and “Squeezplay”, as well as a pilot for MTV called, “This is Ray.” Her favorite role to date was in Cameron Crowe’s film “Almost Famous”. Erin played the role of Allison, the fact checker. Erin has branded a unique position for herself in the industry as not only a gifted stand-up but a talented actress. Her versatility makes her one of the most sought- after women working the comedy scene today.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Erin_Foley.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Michael Capozzola</name>
  <slug>michael-capozzola</slug>
  <tag></tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Michael Capozzola is a Bay Area based Stand Up Comedian. He has appeared on MTV and is a regular Invited performer at SketchFest. He’s performed in Canada, London, Edinburgh and Jerusalem. He’s also a published cartoonist and contributed to The San Francisco Chronicle, Mad Magazine, TED Talks / TEDxSV, The New York Times, The Humor Times, National Lampoon, McSweeney&#8217;s and the nationally syndicated cartoon, BIZARRO.<br />
 
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/MikeCapazzolaHeadshot.gif</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Danny Charnley</name>
  <slug>danny-charnley</slug>
  <tag>From your favorite Montgomery County drinking hole</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Danny Charnley did not submit a &#8220;bio&#8221; per se, because Danny Charnley prefers to write his bio in the 3rd person from a secure computer located within the comedy club.&nbsp; In the meantime, you can observe his antics on twitter (@DanKCharnley) or at <a href="http://www.dankcharnley.com">http://www.dankcharnley.com</a>. Danny Charnley is an amazing genius, by the way&#8230;I mean, that guy is just great.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/dank_mona_lisa.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Sam Morril</name>
  <slug>sam-morril</slug>
  <tag></tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Sam Morril, one of the fastest rising comics in New York City, is also one of the best joke writers in the scene today. How do you know that&#8217;s true? Because he is writing this bio, and he wouldn&#8217;t lie about that to get extra work. He won March Madness 2010 at Comix, has performed in a Friars Roast, and was featured in a 4-page spread in the Daily News as &#8220;one of the four funniest in New York?&#8221; He then won the Laughing Skull Festival in Atlanta, beating out over 600 applicants. Sam was recently named a 2011 “Comic to Watch” by Comedy Central. His comedy can be heard on Sirius XM radio, and he’s a regular at all the top clubs in the city, all at the tender and supple age of 25. Come see Sam before his ego gets too big to do small rooms.</p>


      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/SamMorril.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Shep Da Comedian</name>
  <slug>shep-da-comedian</slug>
  <tag>Known for her "Fly on the Wall" comedy style, Shep repeatedly shocks various audiences with her shenanigans brought on by the daily comical incidents that she encounters.  Known for her "Fly on the Wall" comedy style, Shep repeatedly shocks various audie</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Shep the Comedienne crashed onto the comedy scene in the fall of 2009.&nbsp; Known for her &#8220;Fly on the Wall&#8221; comedy style, Shep repeatedly shocks various audiences with her shenanigans brought on by the daily comical incidients that she encounters. Shep the Comedienne keeps it real. She has been seen on sporadic stages all over the DC, MD, VA, PA, NY, FL and Vegas. Shep Da Comedienne has a charismatic approach to difficult subjects that is sure to keep you in awe while you laugh your butt off!
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Shep_Da_Comedienne.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Jessica Brodkin</name>
  <slug>jessica-brodkin</slug>
  <tag></tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Jessica Brodkin is one of fastest rising comics based out of the DC Area. She has been featured in a number of National Comedy Festivals including the Laughing Skull, the North Carolina Comedy Arts, Philadelphia Improv Festival, and Boston&#8217;s Women in Comedy Festival. She is a regular in the top clubs in DC, Maryland, and Virgina and has opened for comedy legends including Tommy Davidson and Pablo Fransisco. In addition to her standup, she plays a recurring Russian character named Ludmilla, and has years of improvisation comedy experience. </p>


      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Jessica_Brodkin1.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Sara Contreras</name>
  <slug>sara-contreras</slug>
  <tag>From Showtime's Latin Divas of Comedy</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Sara Contreras was showcased as one of the country’s best female comedians in Showtime’s “The Original Latin Divas of Comedy,” which received an ALMA nomination for Best Comedy Special. She has also appeared as a commentator and writer for MTV3. Television credits include” NBC’s “Law &amp; Order: SVU” (two episodes), “Third Watch,“ and “Conviction,”; Comedy Central’s “Comic Groove;” Metrochannel’s “New Joke City;” A&amp;E’s “American Comedy: What’s So Funny?;” ABC’s “The View” and “New York Comedy Festival;” SiTV’s “Funny is Funny;” and TNC’s “Que Loco.” She taped with Nick Turturro for his spec television pilot “Doorman,” with Marlo Thomas for the web-series “Auntie Marlo &amp; Kate,” and for Univision’s Spanish-language stand-up comedy special “Los Locos y Revueltos.” Sara performed for our military troops in Iraq/Kuwait in March 2011.</p>

<p>A regular performer on the N.Y. tri-state comedy club/college circuit, she has also been seen across the country at premier comedy clubs and venues. Sara has performed at the New York Comedy Festival, the Marshalls Women in Comedy Festival, the Urban Comedy Festival, and the Toyota Comedy Festival. She has been critically acclaimed for her work with the N.Y.-based “Sistas Doing Comedy” and the L.A.-based “Hot &amp; Spicy Tamales.” Sara received an impressive N.Y. Times review for her work as a writer/monologist in the off-Broadway production “Jose Can Speak.”
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/SaraI1.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Charles Walden</name>
  <slug>charles-walden</slug>
  <tag>From BET's Comic View, Martin Lawrence 1st Amendment, and Def Comedy Jam’s All-Star Season!</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Charles Walden gives his audiences the most inspirational laughing good time they have had in a while.&nbsp; Charles Walden a 15-year veteran to comedy is challenged by Cerebral Palsy, which has become a unique theme to his show.&nbsp; Charles Walden has taken his comedy to the stages of BETs Comic View, Martin Lawrence 1st Amendment, and Def Comedy Jam’s All-Star Season.&nbsp; Charles is a requested favorite performing his CLEAN routine at comedy clubs, colleges, and universities across the Country.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/charleswalden.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Andy Kline</name>
  <slug>andy-kline</slug>
  <tag></tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Since getting his comedy start in D.C., Andy Kline has branched out to clubs across the country, in addition to regular appearances on 98 Rock and SiruisXM Radio.&nbsp; Andy can also be heard weekly on the acclaimed comedy podcast, Three Guys On - <a href="http://www.threeguyson.com">http://www.threeguyson.com</a>.&nbsp; With a mix of strong opinions, insight, and common sense, Andy manages to be more than just funny.&nbsp; He manages to be memorable.&nbsp; Andy&#8217;s talents have enabled him to work with some of the biggest names in the business, including Dave Chappelle, Wanda Sykes, and Marc Maron.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Andy_Kline.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Tony Deyo</name>
  <slug>tony-deyo</slug>
  <tag>From the HBO Aspen Comedy Festival and the Bob &amp; Tom Radio Show!</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>A rising young talent, Deyo is known for his sharp, quick material and near perfect comedic timing almost certainly gained from his years as a professional symphony musician.&nbsp; In 2007, he had the incredible opportunity to perform at the prestigious HBO Aspen Comedy Festival.  In 2011, he was named one of the year&#8217;s best by the New York Post, and can be heard on the nationally syndicated Bob &amp; Tom Radio Show.</p>

<p>Tony grew up in a small town in rural Virginia.&nbsp; After receiving a bachelor&#8217;s degree in education and master&#8217;s degree in music, he spent several years performing with various symphonies.&nbsp; He was also a middle school teacher for three years before realizing that he had a strong distaste for children.</p>

<p>After moving to Austin, TX, Deyo discovered comedy. He began performing, influenced by the work of Jerry Seinfeld and Brian Regan. Like his influences, Tony&#8217;s act is clean and suitable for nearly any audience.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Tony_Deyo.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Mike Storck</name>
  <slug>mike-storck</slug>
  <tag>From the humble Baltimore beginnings &amp; Comedy Festivals Nation Wide</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Barely taking things at face value, even the most ordinary of topics are spun into new directions that only his creatively warped mind could envision. Mike always keeps audiences on their toes by being about as predictable as a car thief whose options are running out. He is the comedic wheel man, taking audiences on a conceptual joyride fueled by an overactive imagination. Along the way, they find humor on every corner, and taboos thrown into a ditch like a drifter with no money for gas.<br />
 <br />
A native Baltimorian, Mike Storck started his stand-up career at an open mic night in &#8216;98 with a broken microphone and a frayed notepad. His act developed at an exponential rate, and within the first few months he quickly started catching the eyes and ears of club owners and comics in the stand-up circuit. Since then he has honed his skill for working with an audience and generating tons of fresh original A-list material.</p>

<p>After moving to New York City, he was quickly recognized as a comedic talent to be reckoned with, making a name for himself in the circuit as a strong writer with the performance skills to match. Storck has performed at the Boston Comedy Festival, the Asheville Comedy Festival, the Prince Edward Island Festival, and the Laughing Skull Festival in Atlanta, GA.</p>

<p>He was a contributing writer for &#8220;The Complete Idiot&#8217;s Guide to Jokes&#8221; and the book &#8220;Kiss Your Butts Goodbye&#8221;. In 2007 he was the Mid-Atlantic winner of &#8220;HBO&#8217;s Lucky 21&#8221; contest. He has been heard on the nationally syndicated &#8220;Bob and Tom&#8221; radio show, the Canadian radio show and podcast &#8220;What&#8217;s So Funny&#8221; and is a regularly featured comic on XM Satellite Radio.</p>

<p>Velocity Magazine called him, &#8220;...funnier than a rubber crucifix.&#8221;. The Ottawa Comedy Resource stated, &#8220;...Mike tore the room apart with stunningly good, original and smart stuff. He may very well be the best act on the &#8216;alternative&#8217; circuit&#8230;&#8221; and &#8220;...delivered cleanly without pretense or exaggerated character, he&#8217;s just being himself.&nbsp; If it&#8217;s rehearsed it doesn&#8217;t show.&#8221; Sén magazine said, &#8220;...Storck had my guts spilling out of my splitting sides&#8230;&#8221;<br />
 <br />
Mike continues to work the comedy club circuit across the United States and Canada, continually writing and performing new material. 
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Mike_Storck.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Tim Miller</name>
  <slug>tim-miller</slug>
  <tag>From the American Armed Forces &amp; your Washington DC Comedy Stage</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Tim Miller&#8217;s aggressive but endearing comedy style creates a show worth seeing more than once. His life as a sheltered son of Pentecostal ministers from Waco, TX, and working at the White House (during three administrations) has made for an energetic comedy style that combines an engaging stage presence with a sarcastic zing.&nbsp; </p>

<p>Tim started doing stand-up after 8 years in the US Army. After five years he has slowly began trying to leave his professional day job in Washington DC and go head first into wherever the entertainment industry would take him. Since then, Tim has worked with todays biggest names in comedy from Pablo Francisco, Daniel Tosh, Ted Alexandro, and Bob Marley. After performing at the DC Comedy Fest, he was named one of the funniest comics in The District.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Tim_Miller.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Karith Foster</name>
  <slug>karith-foster</slug>
  <tag>From Comedy Central’s Premium Blend, NBC’s Today Show, and Last Comic Standing</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Karith has appeared on Comedy Central’s Premium Blend, NBC’s Today Show and Last Comic Standing, VH-1’s Best Week Ever, Awesomely Bad…and Black to the Future series. You may have also seen her on BET, BRAVO, and The Travel and Fine Living Channels. Her greatest triumphs include performing on Showtime at the Apollo (getting applause, not boos), doing live audience warm-up for the Oprah Winfrey Show and later as a guest on Oprah. Her comedy CD “Karith Foster: Straight Outta Plano is currently in rotation on Sirius/XM’s Raw Dog Comedy Channel.</p>

<p>Karith credits her entrée into the entertainment world to her upbringing in the affluent suburb of Plano, Texas, where irony of all ironies she starred in her high school’s otherwise ALL WHITE production of A Raisin in the Sun. Two guesses who the raisin was! This self-described “Huxtable” has been nicknamed “Princess” by several friends who are convinced she’s actually a Jewish girl from Long Island trapped in that body—which would technically make her a JA-AP (Jewish African-American Princess). So, in her case it’s not “talk to the hand,” but “talk to the manicure.” She may never have cooked a full meal in her life but she has the Zagats Restaurant Guide practically memorized- that’s gotta count for something.</p>

<p>Karith is bi-coastal residing in both NYC and LA. When she’s not headlining colleges and clubs across the country she performs weekly at a variety of NYC comedy clubs including: The Cellar, The Comic Strip Live, Caroline’s on Broadway, Gotham Comedy Club, Stand-up New York Comedy Club, Broadway Comedy Club &amp; Café, New York Comedy Club. When out West you can find her at Pasadena’s Ice House, LA’s Improv, The Laugh Factory, The Comedy Store and The Story Salon.</p>

<p>Karith has also transitioned her comedy into a speaking career and is one of the most sought after speakers for colleges and corporations in the areas of: Diversity, Leadership, Women, Team Building and Motivation. She is also the founder of “Laughter Bootcamp” a workshop, which she leads for groups, social organizations,and corporations. She is the author of “Laugh Your Way to Happiness: 101 Ways to Have a Great Laugh” and the soon to be released children’s book “Lealah Finds Love.”</p>

<p>Karith was recently honored by being named spokesperson for the amazing organization Books for Kids Foundation- which promotes literacy among all children with a special emphasis on low-income and at-risk preschool-aged children. Books for Kids creates libraries, donates books, and partners with literacy programs to develop the critical early foundation and skills which young children need to be successful in life.</p>

<p>Karith lives by the comic’s law: All is fair in love and comedy.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Karith_Foster_Navy_headshot.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Jason Dudey</name>
  <slug>jason-dudey</slug>
  <tag></tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Jason Dudey has been performing around the country for the past decade, sharing his quirky views on every day life, love and family.&nbsp; He has opened for Judy Gold, Ant, Natasha Legerro, Craig Shoemaker, Sandra Bernhardt and more; he has appeared on LOGO’s Wisecracks—OutLaugh Comedy Festival; and he currently tours the US of A with the brilliant Kathleen Madigan.&nbsp; He is the creator and producer of “Come Out Laughing” – a comedy extravaganza that features only the funniest comedians regardless of who they sleep with.&nbsp; As the host of The Jason Dudey Show, Jason brings the best, most entertaining, aspects of the comedy world to your radio, computer, iPod/pad/phone/book/etc. and fulfills a lifelong dream of taking his talented tongue to the world of radio. Check out The Jason Dudey Show on <a href="http://www.gvbradio.com">http://www.gvbradio.com</a> or stitcher or itunes or call his mother, she might have a copy.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/jason-dudey-blue-shirt.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Brad Trackman</name>
  <slug>brad-trackman</slug>
  <tag>The Riot Act Comedy School Instructor Extraordinaire</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Brad Trackman is a NYC comedian with universal appeal. He has made national television appearances on NBC&#8217;s &#8220;Later&#8221; and &#8220;Friday Night&#8221;, CBS&#8217;s &#8220;Star Search&#8221;, ABC&#8217;s &#8220;NY Comedy Festival&#8221;, Metro TV&#8217;s &#8220;New Joke City&#8221; hosted by Robert Klein, Comedy Central&#8217;s &#8220;Heroes Of Jewish Comedy &amp; Stand Up Stand Up&#8221;, MTV&#8217;s &#8220;The Buried Life&#8221; and his own commercial campaign for Spike Television where he played the ficticious presidential elect Biff Wolinski. Trackman has also done numerous television appearances in Canada on the &#8220;Mike Bullard Show&#8221; and in Holland on the &#8220;Comedy Factory&#8221; and the &#8220;Raymaan Is Laat Show&#8221;.</p>

<p>In addition to Trackman headlining around the country, both of his CDs have received critical acclaim and were produced by XM Radio&#8217;s comedy program director, Joel Haas. Trackman is played regularly and has had specials (featuring his CDs) on both XM and Sirius radio. Other venues Trackman headlines include &#8220;The Improv&#8221; (Las Vegas, Nevada), &#8220;Tommy T&#8217;s&#8221; (Pleasonton, California), &#8220;The Stardome&#8221; (Hoover, Alabama), &#8220;Hilarities&#8221; (Cleveland, Ohio), Helium Comedy Club (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania) and the legendary &#8220;Punchline&#8221; (San Francisco, California). Brad&#8217;s first performance ever at &#8220;Punchline&#8221; was to a sold out room where he soon won a standing ovation.</p>

<p>If you&#8217;re wondering what makes Brad such a unique comedian, it&#8217;s his versatility, his ability to work squeaky clean and still kill. Maybe that&#8217;s why &#8220;Radio Shack&#8221; had Trackman headline the &#8220;Net Together Concert&#8221; in Times Square with a 20-foot tall jumbotron behind him and a crowd of 5,000 people in front of him. This concert was also simulcast in San Francisco.</p>

<p>Trackman has opened for Dana Carvey, Joan Rivers and Weird Al Yankovic in arenas with crowds of up to 7,000. His pursuit of ensuring other people&#8217;s happiness is still evolving, as is Brad. Despite all these major accomplishments, Brad considers his biggest breaks in entertaiment were meeting his wife, Christina (who, at the time, booked &#8220;Carolines on Broadway&#8221;) and having their son Tyler.</p>

<p>Trackman has been teaching stand up comedy for the past eight years in both Princeton NJ and New York City. Brad than decided to open his own school The Philadelphia Comedy Academy out of Helium Comedy Club which has become one of the most successful stand up comedy programs in the country. He was also recently hired to teach stand up comedy at the highly prestigious Ivy League University of Pennsylvania/Wharton School of Business as well. He also does two-day seminars in the many cities he headlines around the country.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Brad-Trackman.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Queen Aishah</name>
  <slug>queen-aishah</slug>
  <tag>Her Spirit Fills The Room</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Known for her “girl next door, in yo face” wit, Comedienne Queen Aishah is recognized nationally and internationally. Hailing from Newark, New Jersey, this sophisticated, sultry, comedic vixen started her career in the DC metropolitan area over 18 years ago.&nbsp; She has hosted and headlined countless comedy shows in the United States and abroad including several trips to entertain our troops in Japan, S. Korea, Europe and Haiti.&nbsp; Keeping busy and always expanding her talents, Queen Aishah has been featured in commercials; print ads; various publications;&nbsp; VH-1 series &#8220;awesomely bad”; BET ComicView, ShowTime @ The Apollo; and has been a celebrity guest and mentor on several episodes of Judge Hattchet, Ricki Lake and the coveted OPRAH Winfrey show.</p>

<p>She has worked with noted comedians such as Steve Harvey, Cedric the Entertainer, Kevin Hart, Mike Epps, Rickey Smiley and Bruce Bruce to name a few. She’s also shared the stage with vocal artist such as Chuck Brown, Yolanda Adams, Heather Headley, Howard Hewitt, Tyrese, Jaheim, K-CI and Jo Jo.&nbsp; Her comedic flair gained the attention of several stage producers such as YYP’s tours where she was focal member of “The Vagina Monologues and Pocketbook Monologues.”&nbsp; These tours offered the opportunity to work with extraordinary actresses as Sherri Sheppard, LisaRaye McCoy, Star Jones, Ella Royce, Phyllis Yvonne Stickney, Vanessa L. Williams and a host of other remarkable personalities.&nbsp; Most recently, Queen Aishah was also casted in the play “Love Under New Management” and is the creator of “Comedienne Queen Aishah Presents Funny ~N~ Stiletto’s,” a comedy tour featuring diverse female comedians.&nbsp; She&#8217;s received numerous accolades from her peers but is most proud of remarks made by Comedian and Activist Dick Gregory who said of her performance in the Vagina Monologues, “Outstanding!”</p>

<p>Queen Aishah resides in the Washington, DC area with her family where she manages her own company “QA Enterprises” and philanthropic ventures.&nbsp; She is the founder of THE M.A.R.R.K. FOUNDATION&#8212;“Massive Action to Reach and Rescue Our Kids,” based out of her hometown of Newark, New Jersey.&nbsp; The foundation was established to support and promote leadership in the inner city where stewardship can be aspired.&nbsp; Queen Aishah also makes it a priority to lend her support to schools all over the country by speaking to their students.&nbsp; She currently works with the Michael Walton Foundation for the “Speak out to Reach Out” tour out of Washington, DC. and is a longtime supporter of the Baltimore Youth of Womb Work Production – NuWord Art Ensemble which is a platform for upcoming young performers.</p>


      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/QueenAishah.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Gary Vider</name>
  <slug>gary-vider</slug>
  <tag>Finalist in Philly's Phunniest Competition</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Gary Vider&#8217;s jokes have been published in the NY Times &amp; Time Out NY. In 2011, he was a finalist in the Philly&#8217;s Phunniest Competition. You can see Gary perform every Tuesday in Midtown Manhattan at The Irish Exit where he host&#8217;s the very popular weekly comedy show, &#8216;Super Marvelous&#8217;.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Gary_Vider.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Mandy Dalton</name>
  <slug>mandy-dalton</slug>
  <tag>Washington DC Comedy Writers Group co-founder!</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>What do you get when you take a bright woman, mix in a healthy dose of good humor, add an education in the classics, top it off with interests in new media, video, theatre, and circus?&nbsp; Mandy Dalton is what you get.&nbsp; She fearlessly pursues anything that fascinates her from philosophy to pop-culture, from video editing to news, and from children’s theatre to Shakespeare. She loves ideas.&nbsp; Whether interviewing someone for a web video or writing a children’s play, she lives for creative activity.&nbsp; Mandy is also the co-founder of the Washington DC Comedy Writers Group.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Mandy_Dalton.png</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Wayne Manigo</name>
  <slug>wayne-manigo</slug>
  <tag>The founder of "WayneMan Comedy!"</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>As an aspiring artist, Wayne took the proactive approach to comedy with the ‘trial by fire’ method.&nbsp; He created a series of open mic shows (including ‘Bellylaughs in Betheda’, now entering their 2nd year) and comedy showcases. He’s the founder of ‘WayneMan Comedy’, and has discovered ways to reach audiences with his brand of humor.&nbsp; His material will include jokes about unemployment, relationships, family and other things we share as human beings.&nbsp; In addition to co-founding the Washington DC Comedy Writers Group, he also co-founded ‘Starting Stand Up: A Comic Beginning’.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Wayne_picture_light_version.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Will Hessler</name>
  <slug>will-hessler</slug>
  <tag></tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Will Hessler is a performer on the comedy scene “that every fan of stand-up comedy should know.”&nbsp; Needing the validation of strangers, Will began performing stand-up comedy and since then audiences have embraced his smart &amp; irreverent perspective, his rare ability to say exactly what people are thinking – but are often too afraid to say, and his absurd &amp; acerbic take on life.&nbsp; Will has a unique blend of unpredictable material &amp; comedic style that keeps audiences coming back to see him time &amp; time again.&nbsp; Will is making his presence known on the stand-up scene by hosting his own weekly comedy showcase in DC, at comedy clubs, colleges &amp; festivals across the country.&nbsp; Will has performed with some of the biggest names in stand-up, like TJ Miller, Todd Barry, and Doug Benson.&nbsp; If you don’t know Will Hessler now, it’s OK.&nbsp; You will very soon!
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Will_Hessler_headshot.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Tyler Richardson</name>
  <slug>tyler-richardson</slug>
  <tag></tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Tyler Richardson has been making a name for himself in the Washington, DC and Baltimore, MD area working clubs and universities with a casual tone and naive delivery. He has worked with national touring headliners such as Aisha Tyler, Rob Cantrell, Alonzo Bodden, Reggie Watts, Kyle Grooms and more. In a very short amount of time he could be heard on XM/Sirius Satellite Radio&#8217;s Too Much Information and was locally available through Comcast On Demand. Recently he has been invited perform in comedy festivals across the country and just performed at an international festival in Canada. Come enjoy his stories and laugh until he is done going through your pocket contents and belongings, he is not above looting. Please get to know him&#8230;
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Tyler_Richardson_headshottyler richardson headshot</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Pete Bladel</name>
  <slug>pete-bladel</slug>
  <tag>An up-and-comer in the DC comedy scene!</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>The critics agree, Pete Bladel hates writing comedy biographies.&nbsp; So this will be brief and to the point.&nbsp; Pete has performed at all of the major venues in the DC/MD/VA area, making audiences laugh at places like the Baltimore Comedy Factory and Arlington Cinema and Drafthouse.&nbsp; He has also been selected for the Laughing Skull and North Carolina Comedy Arts festivals.&nbsp; In just a few short years, he has worked with notable comedians such as John Mulaney, Tim Meadows, Wyatt Cenac, Chris Hardwick, Amy Schumer and Bob Marley, among others. His parents are very proud of him, mostly because he hasn&#8217;t lived in their basement since 2009.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Pete_Bladel_headshot.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Lafayette Wright</name>
  <slug>lafayette-wright</slug>
  <tag></tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Lafayette Wright is unique in that he is a comic, to whose self-obsessions with rejection, inadequacy, and loneliness some can relate but most can laugh at. A favorite on the DC comedy scene for quite a while, Lafayette has been described as a compelling, layered and visually striking comedian. Armed with his clever material and a major inferiority complex, he is definitely an act worth watching.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Lafayette_Wright.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Marcus Paulsen</name>
  <slug>marcus-paulsen</slug>
  <tag>A hot new up-and-comer in the DC Comedy scene!</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Roaming the scene of the young, 20-something crowd in Washington, DC, Marcus Paulsen is a local favorite at comedic venues across the District where his wit and knack for sarcastic observations has earned him a reputation as one of DC’s hot, new up-and-comers.<br />
Born and raised in small town Texas, Marcus moved to Washington in 2007 where he has worked in politics and consulting, often noting the peculiarities of life on the job and in the Capitol City.&nbsp; He writes extensively, working to find the sweetest mix of word play and sarcasm to the delight of his audiences.<br />
Marcus is a graduate of the DC Improv Comedy School and has performed across the DC area at venues including Riot Act Comedy Theater and the DC Improv.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/MarcusPaulsenHeadshot.jpeg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Joyce Rebar</name>
  <slug>joyce-rebar</slug>
  <tag>From the 2010 World Series of Comedy and Co-headliner for New Year's Annapolis 2009-2010 Comedy Show</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Joyce Rebar was born and raised in Maryland and still resides there.&nbsp; However, she is not without an adventurous side.&nbsp; A former archaeologist who had been wanting to return to the field for many years, she finally learned that sleeping late, doing nothing all day, and staying in air-conditioned clubs all night was preferable to getting up at the crack of dawn, spending 8 hours in a hot field, and going to bed early every night.&nbsp; Like the soils in which the best archaeological treasures are found, Joyce&#8217;s comedy is sort of a mottled, silty loam with elements of witty observation, sarcasm, and downright ridiculousness. </p>

<p>Joyce took her first comedy class at the DC Improv in October of 2006, and was surprised to find that people actually laughed&#8230;a lot&#8230;when she was on stage.&nbsp; Told by her instructor that she had the talent to really make it in this business, she took a few tentative steps out into the &#8220;real&#8221; world of comedy.&nbsp; Since then, she has opened for Mimi Gonzalez, Jennie McNulty, Carole Montgomery, Bob Gautreau, Kelly Terranova and Kevin Lee; and she has been fortunate to appear in shows with many other talented comedians.&nbsp; The list includes Bob Saget, Kate Clinton, Rich Vos, Bonnie McFarlane, Rob Cantrell, Roger Mursick, and Matt Kazam, among others. </p>

<p>One of only 56 comics to receive a regular (non-wild card) spot at the first (2010) World Series of Comedy in Las Vegas, Joyce returned to the World Series in 2011.&nbsp; She also has headlined shows at New Year’s Annapolis, NASA (Goddard), and various private events.&nbsp; She did three 30-minute sets, during the successful attempt by Magooby’s Joke House to break the Guiness World Record for longest comedy show (81 hours).&nbsp; Joyce has appeared in shows at the DC Improv; Riot Act (Washington, DC); Caroline’s on Broadway (New York, NY); The Comedy Factory (Baltimore, MD); Funnybone (Richmond, VA); The Comedy Spot (Arlington, VA); Charlie Goodnight’s (Raleigh, NC); and many other venues in MD, DC, NY, VA, NC, NV, FL, OH, and PA (as well as on a couple of cruise ships).
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Joyce_Rebar.jpeg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Dave Siegel</name>
  <slug>dave-siegel</slug>
  <tag>From Comedy Central, Fox and CNN</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>A native New Yorker, Dave Siegel started as a doorman at a comedy club while still a college student.&nbsp; His first show as a performer came at an open call at the ‘Comic Strip’ on Manhattan’s upper east side.&nbsp;  Since that time Dave has headlined premier comedy clubs across the country from ‘Carolines&#8217; on Broadway to the ‘Laugh Factory’ on Sunset Blvd.</p>

<p>In 2004, Dave was selected to take part in Comedy Central’s ‘Laugh Riots.’&nbsp; He has since appeared on CNN, FOX and Headline News.</p>

<p>In 2009, Dave began to write for and appear in Comedy Central’s &#8216;Atom TV.&#8217;&nbsp; His films have been produced and featured by ‘Funny or Die’ and screened in premier festivals around the country.</p>

<p>In 2011, Dave began writing for CNN’s ‘OutFront.’&nbsp;  He also has a weekly comedy/relationship blog on MSN.&nbsp; </p>

<p>
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Dave_Siegel_Med.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Chipp Jones</name>
  <slug>chipp-jones</slug>
  <tag>From NPR, PBS and finalist for Maryland's Funniest Comic</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>From featuring for the Last Comic Standing’s Reject Tour to warming up the audience for the  PBS television show &#8220;Money Wise&#8221;, Chipp Jones’ irreverent, thought-provoking brand of comedy has audiences rolling in the aisles throughout Washington DC and up and down the East Coast.</p>

<p>Whether he’s suggesting a new Hallmark card collection to celebrate Congress’s recent “apology for slavery” or wondering why a recent celebrity didn’t just pay the money for a “spotter” to cut him down after sexual asphyxiation, Chipp is fast-becoming a well-known comic in the DC area comedy scene and has twice made it to the finals of Maryland’s Funniest Comic. He has written for theNPR website and is regularly booked at many of the local venues in the Washington DC area such as Sully&#8217;s Comedy Cellar and has performed at NYC clubs including Stand Up NY and Gotham Comedy Club.</p>

<p>Chipp Jones’ stand-up comedy was a gift. During a difficult year when his wife was diagnosed with a brain tumor, she gave him comedy classes as a gift for their 17th wedding anniversary. After her surgery was successful, he performed a 12-minute bit called “Tumor Humor” for his graduation showcase. The crowd loved it and Chipp has pursued comedy ever since. He lives in DC with his wife Sue and son Chris, and runs his own computer consulting business.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Chipp_Jones.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Wendy Ho</name>
  <slug>wendy-ho</slug>
  <tag>The Queen of Sass and Crass from MTV and FX</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>The Queen of Sass and Crass: Wendy Ho. One part skilled singer, one part comedienne, one part white rapper, and one part flamboyant entertainer.&nbsp; Ho sounds like Lil’ Kim and Aretha eatin’ Peaches on a Lonely Island. Stealing ladies’ handbags from coat rooms at parties inspired her track “Bitch, I Stole Yo Purse!,” which became the #1 Funniest Video of 2008 on the MTV/LOGO Network, and was spoofed on FX’s Nip/Tuck with Jennifer Coolidge playing their version of Wendy Ho.&nbsp; This track came from the beloved cult classic album, The Gospel According to Ho  which includes the torch song parody of Brenda Russel’s “Get Here,” now known as, “Fuck Me,” and the tell all story of her own drug intervention“Cocaine.” This irreverence and balls-out femininity struck a special chord with the gay community, inspiring drag queens around the world to perform her songs and celebrate Ho. </p>

<p>With a rainbow hurricane of gay support behind her, Wendy Ho owned 2009-10, performing across North America and abroad, with venues in San Francisco, Los Angeles, Las Vegas, Montreal, Miami, Washington DC, Philadelphia, Ft. Lauderdale, Orlando, and her hometown of Kansas City, as well as an Atlantis gay cruise to Rome, Greece, and Egypt.&nbsp; She also appeared on Showtime’s series I Can’t Believe I’m Still Single.</p>

<p>And the music don’t stop. Ho recently dropped Number Two, a mixtape packed with fresh song jacks, freestyles, mashups and remixes, including the dirty disco anthem “Poop Noodle.” The “Poop Noodle” video, meanwhile, is delighting and disgusting thousands of viewers daily on YouTube. </p>

<p>Ho’s new full-length album Yes, I’m a Ho! has recently been released to satisfied hobags worldwide.&nbsp; Featuring edgy, musically and thematically diverse tracks like “I Can’t Afford It (I’m Gonna Have to Abort It)” and “Gurl, Putcho Tampon In,” Yes, I’m a Ho! is a soon-to-be-notorious classic hip-hop/r&amp;b record. Loaded  with eleven original songs (no samples this time around), Ho combines tongue-in-cheek delivery with in-your-face prophecy. </p>

<p>Most recently Ho headlined at the world’s largest Pride Festival in San Francisco.&nbsp; That same weekend she performed with Sandra Bernhardon her show, I Love Being Me, Don’t You?</p>

<p>Ho is an artist.&nbsp; Ho is a state of mind.&nbsp; Ho redefines women in music with true liberation.&nbsp; She is funny and sexy, never sacrificing one for the other.&nbsp; A pretty bitch, a witty feminist, a self-possessed, self-assured mashup of street and trash who makes you laugh while she makes you think.&nbsp; The responses she evokes from audiences are as diverse as her roots, but at the core there is no question about who she is.&nbsp; Wendy is all woman.&nbsp; All Ho.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Wendy_Ho.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Dan Piraro</name>
  <slug>dan-piraro</slug>
  <tag>Stand up comedian, musician, cartoonist in one-man comedy show!</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Piraro, also a stand up comedian &amp; musician has a one-man comedy show and has performed in a number of cities around the country, including Dallas, Houston, San Francisco, Los Angeles, Chicago, Portland and New York. His show&#8217;s run in the 2002 New York International Fringe Festival was voted &#8220;Best Solo Show,&#8221; and The New York Times called it &#8220;...a shrewd tour of a cartoonist&#8217;s imagination&#8221; and &#8220;...wildly applauded.&#8221;<br />
 <br />
BIZARRO appears daily in several hundred newspapers across the U.S. and in internationally and has won three consecutive Reuben Awards from the National Cartoonist Society for Best Cartoon Panel of the Year in 1999, 2000, and 2001.&nbsp;  For the years 2002 through 2005, Dan Piraro was nominated for its highest award, Outstanding Cartoonist of the Year and received it in 2009,<br />
 <br />
A well-known animal lover and animal rights activist, Piraro was awarded the Humane Society&#8217;s Genesis Award for Outstanding Cartoonist in 2002, 2003, and 2005.<br />
Last Gasp Comics has just released a book called BIZARRO HEROES –<br />
a collection of his superhero themed spoofs from the last 25 years of BIZARRO.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Dan_Pirraro.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Dennis Regan</name>
  <slug>dennis-regan1</slug>
  <tag>From "The Late Show with David Letterman" and "</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>If ever one wanted to prove that comedy is genetic, Dennis Regan may be the perfect example. Like his brother Brian, Dennis is a successful stand-up comedian. Since entering the stand-up circuit in 1987, Regan has toured regularly. Audiences all over the country have experienced and embraced Dennis Regan&#8217;s observational comedy, from nightclubs and cruise ships to colleges and corporations. His universal appeal has landed him appearances on &#8220;Comedy Central&#8221;, &#8220;The Late Show with David Letterman&#8221;, &#8220;The Tonight Show with Jay Leno&#8221; and Showtime&#8217;s &#8220;A Pair of Jokers&#8221; with his brother Brian.</p>

<p>Dennis Regan was born and raised in Miami, Florida. Dennis is the third of eight children. His brother, Brian Regan is also a very successful, in-demand comedian,&nbsp; Dennis held a variety of jobs and owned a business before becoming a comedian in 987. Starting out in small local clubs, he soon moved to New York, where he worked his way through the Manhattan comedy scene over a five year period.</p>


      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Dennis_Regan.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Reesa Renee</name>
  <slug>reesa-renee</slug>
  <tag>Singer/Songwriter</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Reesa is an artist, musician, songwriter, and lyrical poet from the DC Metropolitan Area. Her voice skims through the soulful sounds of the jazz era and then fast fowards your musical clocks to the more modern sounds of the R&amp;B greats of today. Add that to an energetic ensemble of musical harmonies and undertones and you get an amazing experience.</p>

<p>Reesa Renee made her musical debut as &#8220;Sis&#8221; with underground band Achosen Generation ni August of 2008 releasing her first single &#8220;Got Me Loose&#8221;. Two years later, and she is now launching her solo career working with local artists and producers on an album entitled &#8220;Reelease&#8221;.</p>

<p>With a promising voice and stellar stage presence Reesa Renee is bound to make a lasting impact. She is a true contender and an utter vessel of passion, creativity, and artistic freedom!</p>


      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Reesa_Renee.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Ray Lipowski</name>
  <slug>ray-lipowski</slug>
  <tag>From HBO Def comedy Jam, HBO White Boys in the Hood and Martin Lawrence Presents 1st Amendment Stand Up</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Ray Lipowski’s comedy is the best of both worlds – not black, not white—but true. He started his comedy career back in 2000 and has been blowing up clubs, colleges, and comedy rooms ever since. Entering a comedy contest with absolutely no experience—not even touching a mic—he took 3rd Place. BET’s Comic View took notice and placed Lipowski on as a regular from 2002-2005 where he received standing ovations. In 2005 Lipowski was called up to perform at P. Diddy’s Bad Boys of Comedy featured on HBO. Lipowski toured Europe the last four years performing for our troops stationed in Germany, London, Ireland and Amsterdam, as well as the locals. Yes Lipowski’s comedy is in your face, brash, bold, and has entertained to sold out crowds of 2,500 to shows of 25 to audiences of 10. It doesn’t matter how many people are there, he just loves to make people laugh. Look out America, a star is about to be born! 
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Ray_Lapowski.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Ashley Linder</name>
  <slug>ashley-linder</slug>
  <tag>From Phasefest: Phase One’s Queer Arts and Music Festival</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Ashley Linder has been enchanting audiences throughout DC, Maryland and Virginia with her quick wit and adorable smile. She enjoys nature walks, the female form, existential musings, and mad libs. Most recently she performed at Phasefest: Phase One’s Queer Arts and Music Festival in Washington DC. Prior to pouncing onto the comedy scene in early 2011, Ashley was seen and heard all over local airwaves dutifully reporting the downright depressing traffic of the DMV.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Ashley_Linder.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Kevin Downey Jr</name>
  <slug>kevin-downey-jr</slug>
  <tag>From "The Bob and Tom Show" and Sirius/XM Radio</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Kevin Downey, Jr., comedian and beer spokesman. Kevin&#8217;s explosive comedy style keeps audiences coming back to see him every chance they get.&nbsp; Kevin is the new face of Little Kings Cream Ale beer. He can be heard on The Bob and Tom Show, Sirius and XM Satellite radio. You can catch Kevin in Las Vegas 4 times a year. </p>

<p>His ever-growing fan base has taken him from a cult following to a national headliner. Kevin writes a column called, “Drinking on $11 a Night”, which can be read in Bachelor Pad Magazine and GC magazine.&nbsp; Kevin’s song, “Secret Garden of Dirty Little Whores, (who think they’re better than me)”, can be heard on college and traditional radio stations throughout the country. Kevin is not related to Robert.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Downey_Jr.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Wali Collins</name>
  <slug>wali-collins</slug>
  <tag>From Comedy Central, "The View", NBC and HBO</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>His first time on stage Wali was convinced that he had bombed, but the manager paid him and asked him to come back every week as a featured act. Wali moved to New York City to work on a show for Comedy Central called “Stand-up Stand-up”. He hosted the largest, funniest, most varied collection of stand-up comedians in the world.</p>

<p>Nominated three years in a row as “College Campus Entertainer of the Year,” Wali is also sought after for corporate events. One of Wali&#8217;s greatest achievements was hosting an event for First Lady Michelle Obama. Collins’ television stand-up credits include NBC, CBS, FOX, HBO, ABC’s “The View”, Comedy Central’s “Tough Crowd” and Commentary on VH1. David Letterman caught Wali’s act and recruited him to warm-up for his show. Later that season Wali performed his stand up on the “Late Show with David Letterman”. In the words of Robert Klein, “Wali Collins is versatile, smart and very, very funny.”
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Wali_Collins.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Dan Naturman</name>
  <slug>dan-naturman</slug>
  <tag>From "The Tonight Show" and "The Late Show With David Letterman"</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Dan began performing stand-up comedy several years ago in,<br />
believe it or not, law school. After graduation he decided to<br />
devote himself to stand-up full time. Comedy, he discovered, was<br />
his true passion. Besides, his grades were bad and nobody would<br />
hire him.</p>

<p>Dan&#8217;s charming combination of self-deprecation and outright grouchiness has had audiences <br />
howling from coast to coast and has earned him spots on The Tonight Show, Late Show with <br />
David Letterman and The Late, Late Show with Craig Ferguson as well as his own Comedy Central<br />
Presents special.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Dan_Naturman_BW.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Michael Colyar</name>
  <slug>michael-colyar</slug>
  <tag>Comic Superstar from HBO, BET, Showtime and Disney</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Michael Colyar was always headed for Hollywood…From the time he was a little boy when he would run away from home…he would always head west, because that’s where Hollywood was…he didn’t realize it was 3000 miles west, by the time he got to the west side of Chicago, his big brother would find him and bring him home.</p>

<p>Best known for his performances on Venice Beach California…For nine years he entertained the crowds…bringing together people from all parts of the world… with his thought-provoking humor, Colyar left a positive imprint in the hearts and minds of his audience. Dubbed The King of Venice Beach where every Saturday and Sunday for over 9 years Colyar would perform 5 one-hour shows a day. His audience ranged from old to young…all colors…all nationalities….the gang bangers to the bank presidents…his audience could truly be called a melting pot.</p>

<p>His informative and highly entertaining brand of comedy guarantees positive response. As &#8216;The Original Host&#8217; of “BET Live From LA”, his point blank delivery and razor-sharp insight connected to the guest that joined him on the sofa, as well as over 55 million viewers coast to coast.</p>

<p>Colyar is known to bring the same high energy, perfect delivery and dynamic stage presence to every show, whether the audience is a local comedy club in Los Angeles, an elementary school where he jokes with 5th graders, or Hosting “The Big Black Comedy Show” for an audience of over 6000.</p>

<p>Colyar gained notable attention after winning the $100,000 Grand Prize Comedy championship on “Star Search”, the nationally televised talent competition, and donating $50,000.00 to homeless charities in the Los Angeles area.<br />
In December of 2000, the city of Venice California honored Michael Colyar by placing his shoe prints, handprints and money grabber in cement for the new Venice boardwalk.</p>

<p>Star Search Champion…Talk Show Host…Actor/Comedian and Motivational Speaker …Colyar stays busy. But no matter how busy, he always takes time out to be share the laughter by visiting homeless shelters, rehabilitation centers, schools and military bases.</p>

<p>August 2010 Colyar’s 1st CD “Michael Colyar’s Greatest Hits &amp; The Great Unknowns” was released Nationally and on iTunes. Currently in production for Re-release “The Michael Colyar Project”…a 1 Hour Comedy Special, shot in the projects of several major cities, including Chicago’s Robert Taylor Homes where Colyar grew up. This project will be available on DVD.</p>

<p>Most recent films include &#8220;The Last Laugh&#8221; starring Tony Rock scheduled release 2011 and &#8220;The Princess &amp; The Frog&#8221; starring Anika Noni Rose and Oprah (the 1st Black animated film produced by Disney Studio).</p>

<p>Colyar was encouraged by Motivational Speaker Les Brown to get it together and take his story on the road…and he began &#8216;Motivational Speaking&#8217;…telling his incredible story of struggle and triumph to his audiences around the world in “Michael Goes Motivational”. Soon to be released… A poetry book for adult children entitled “Miss Innocent Goes To Kool Skool and Other Silly Stuff.”</p>

<p>Currently playing Bishop Love Jones the stage production Je Carious Johnson’s Marriage Material on Tour until May 2011.</p>

<p>New Projects …Where In The World Is Michael Colyar” a series of concert films with Colyar and Friends shot in various locations around the world…The series begins in Washington Dc with his Documentary “A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to The White House, I knocked on the Door…and A Brother Answered”, and goes to Venice Beach California for “Michael Colyar Returns To Venice Beach”…and continues to the African Continent for “Michael Colyar Live From Africa”.</p>

<p>Michael Colyar … Hard To Ignore … Impossible To Forget!
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Michael_Colyar_Butterfly.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Freddi Vernell</name>
  <slug>freddi-vernell</slug>
  <tag>From Jamie Fox's Laffapalooza New Faces of Comedy</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>After graduating from college and building a successful career, Freddi Vernell realized that something was missing in her life. A friend and Oprah Winfrey (several episodes) encouraged her to live her passion. She changed her name to protect her career as an engineer by day and then embraced her inner clown at night. She built an impressive resume in a short period of time.<br />
 <br />
Ms. Vernell has opened for national acts, done voiceovers, hosted numerous events, and done commercials. Just to name a few places, she has performed at; Carolines On Broadway, Laugh Out Loud Comedy Club, Jokes On Us in DC, The New York City Comedy Club, The Lincoln Theater, Laffs on The Harbor, The Baltimore Comedy Factory, The Sage Theater on Broadway, as well as the Uptown in Atlanta. In 2006 Ms. Vernell was chosen as one of Jamie Fox&#8217;s Laffapalooza New Faces of Comedy, and in 2007 she was crowned Washington DC&#8217;s very first &#8220;Funniest Federal Employee&#8221;! In 2008 she was the only female finalist in the Bay Area Comedy Competition. In 2009 she joined the Donnie Simpson Morning show as the “Hollywood Gossiping Beautician” and has done reoccurring commentary on CBS Radio and BET. Her greatest accomplishment is volunteering her time to perform for injured soldiers at Walter Reed Hospital. She believes in the healing power of laughter!
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Freddi_Vernell_Big.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Erik Myers</name>
  <slug>erik-myers1</slug>
  <tag>Named Funniest Comedian in Florida 2011</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Erik Myers is a high-energy comedian with a rapid fire, machine gun delivery and a crowd-pleasing stage presence. He talks about his personal life struggles with drinking, woman and finding a job from an upbeat and silly perspective. He has appeared on the Latino Laff Festival on SiTv hosted by Pablo Francisco. He was named funniest comedian in Florida 2011 and funniest comedian in Baltimore 2005. Erik Myers is a riotus act not sure to miss.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Erik_Myers_Arm.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Iliza Shlesinger</name>
  <slug>iliza-shlesinger</slug>
  <tag>From "Chelsea Lately", NBC's "Last Comic Standing" and "The Soup"</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Originally from Dallas, Iliza currently lives in Los Angeles and is the first female and youngest comedian to hold the title of NBC’s &#8220;Last Comic Standing&#8221;. Her television credits include having her own half hour special on Comedy Central Presents, Comedy Central’s &#8220;Live At Gotham&#8221;, Showtime&#8217;s &#8220;Pauly Shore &amp; Friends&#8221;, E! Network’s &#8220;Chelsea Lately&#8221;, &#8220;The Soup&#8221; and NBC’s &#8220;Last Call with Carson Daly&#8221;. <br />
 <br />
This fall Iliza will be the host of the nightly CBS Syndicated, &#8220;Excused&#8221;. She is also currently in production on her own late night talk show pilot for VH1.&nbsp; Her standup comedy resume includes performing at the coveted Just for Laughs Festival in Montreal and for our troops in various countries. She can currently be seen headlining at variety of colleges and clubs across the US.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Iliza_PinkSmile.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Ayanna Dookie</name>
  <slug>ayanna-dookie</slug>
  <tag>From 98 Rock's Mickey, Amelia, &amp; Spiegel Morning Show</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Honest, bold, fearless, and fly is what you will encounter when you 5’4”, big-haired, comedienne, Ayanna Dookie. While attending the University of Maryland, College Park, she recognized her ability to make her classmates laugh, resulting in a daily, unofficial, lunchtime show in the engineer’s lounge. Finally, in October 2004, Ayanna officially hit the stage, becoming a regular in the DC Comedy circuit. A first generation American, born to Trinidadian immigrants, she pokes fun at her biracial upbringing and coined the race “blindian” – the product of a Black mother and Indian father. Ayanna’s style is one of sarcasm, mixed with a bit of arrogance, and a splash of “TMI,” drawing from her life experiences – all done in an array of thigh high boots, stilettos, and peep toes. She’s had several career highlights, such as opening for Tommy Davidson and Mark Curry and performing for the first female mayor of Baltimore City in an all female comedy show. Ayanna can also be heard as a regular guest on Baltimore’s 98 Rock Mickey, Amelia, &amp; Spiegel Morning Show.</p>


      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Ayanna_Dookie.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Abe Barth</name>
  <slug>abe-barth</slug>
  <tag>Finalist in Funniest Federal Employee Competition and Semi-Finalist at Boston Comedy Festival.</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Originally from Delaware, Abe and his comedy have been described as smart and unique.&nbsp;  Abe has performed all over Boston and now is a regular on the DC comedy scene.&nbsp; He was named a finalist in the Funniest Federal Employee competition and was a Semi-Finalist at this year’s Boston Comedy Festival.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Abe_Barth.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Jim David</name>
  <slug>jim-david</slug>
  <tag>From Comedy Central, "The Tonight Show" and NBC's "Last Comic Standing"</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Jim David was the first out male comedian to have his own special &#8220;Comedy Central Presents Jim David&#8221; which has been shown many times on Comedy Central and Logo. He also appeared on Comedy Central&#8217;s &#8220;Tough Crowd&#8221;, &#8220;Out On The Edge&#8221;, &#8220;Friar&#8217;s Club Roast Of Rob Reiner&#8221;, NBC&#8217;s &#8220;Tonight Show&#8221; and &#8220;Last Comic Standing&#8221;, and many other shows. A national headliner, his one man comedy South Pathetic has been performed in theaters nationwide. His three comedy CDs, &#8220;Eat Here And Get Gas&#8221;, &#8220;Live From Jimville&#8221; and &#8220;Notorious F.A.G.&#8221; are available on Itunes and Amazon. &#8220;A tirelessly gregarious trouper.&#8221; - NY TIMES &#8220;Laugh out loud funny.&#8221; - TIME OUT NY &#8220;Hilarious.&#8221; - SAN FRANCISCO WEEKLY &#8220;A hoot.&#8221; - HOLLYWOOD REPORTER
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Jim_David.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Danny Rouhier</name>
  <slug>danny-rouhier</slug>
  <tag>Host of show "Overtime" weeknights on 106.7 The Fan</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Danny Rouhier is the host of Overtime weeknights from 7-11 on 106.7 The Fan in Washington, DC. His highly acclaimed show has landed him spots on Comcast Sportsnet, features in the Washington Post, and the regular slot hosting the station’s Redskins post game show with Lavar Arrington. As a comic, Danny has traveled all over North America performing at clubs, colleges, and festivals. Combined with his incredible gift of impersonations and character imitation, Danny uses a lightening quick wit with a charming self-deprecating style. His unique voice resonated with Washington Redskins fans and the weekly videos he produced about the struggles of the team have garnered over 200,000 views to date.</p>

<p>Danny has performed with industry giants like Jim Gaffigan, Kevin Nealon, Bill Burr, Dave Attell, Jim Norton, Todd Barry, Daniel Tosh, Bob Saget, Reggie Watts, Adam Ferrara, and more. In addition to many of the best clubs in the US and Canada, he has performed at numerous festivals including the Bumbershoot, DC, Boston, and Detroit Comedy Festivals. Danny has also been featured on numerous TV programs including: &#8216;The A-List&#8217; on Animal Planet, &#8216;TV&#8217;s 25 Biggest Blunders&#8217;, and &#8216;The History of Sex on TV&#8217;. He was also the studio comic for the Tyra Banks Show which means he performed in front of over 300 judgmental women per day.</p>


      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Danny_Rouhier_Live.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Herbie Gill</name>
  <slug>herbie-gill</slug>
  <tag>From ABC, TBS and XM Radio</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Herbie Gill is a DC area native whose entertaining sense of humor has been featured across the country. Changing expectations and skewing stereotypes, this young comic can finesse any crowd with professionalism, style and wit. Herbie&#8217;s comedy has been featured on XM Radio, TBS, Comcast, and Local Point TV for ABC.</p>


      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Herbie_Gill.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Joe Clair</name>
  <slug>joe-clair</slug>
  <tag>From HBO's "Def Comedy Jam", BET's "Rap City" and WPGC 95.5FM</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Joe Clair is unique in the fact that he is a comic turned rapper.</p>

<p>Joe has been on a number of television shows some of his credits include: Black Entertainment Television&#8217;s &#8220;Rap City&#8221;&nbsp; he was host of Black Entertainment Television&#8217;s &#8220;Madd Sports.&#8221;&nbsp; HBO&#8217;s &#8220;Def Comedy Jam&#8221;, BET&#8217;s &#8220;Comic View&#8221;, and &#8220;Snaps&#8221; were some of his best television work.</p>

<p>Clair has also been featured in motion pictures &#8220;Train Ride&#8221; and &#8220;High Frequency&#8221;.</p>

<p>Clair has been featured at the top comedy clubs in the nation and he was recently added to headline on the nations&#8217; top college tour. 
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Joe_Clair_Tongue.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Bobcat Goldthwait</name>
  <slug>bobcat-goldthwait</slug>
  <tag>From "The Tonight Show", "Shakes the Clown" and The Police Academy Series</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Bobcat Goldthwait is a legend. It is about time you get to know him if you don&#8217;t already. </p>

<p>Born in the outskirts of Hollywood (Syracuse, New York) in 1962, Bobcat Goldthwait wrote and directed his first film “Shakes The Clown” in 1991. A dark cult comedy, “Shakes” was heralded by the Boston Globe as the –“Citizen Cane of Alcoholic clown movies, and lays claim to such fans as Martin Scorsese and Michael Stipe” – in fact; the REM song “Binky the Doormat” was based on a line from “Shakes The Clown”.&nbsp; Goldthwait’s next movie “Windy City Heat” appeared in the Cine Vegas Film Festival in 04 and won best film at the Montreal Comedy Festival that year. Matt Stone (co-creator of South Park) has called “Windy City Heat” –“beyond genius” and Vice Magazine called it, -“quite simply the greatest movie of all time”. “Sleeping Dogs Lie” marked Bobcat’s third feature film as a director. Written by Goldthwait, and financed by friends and pawn shops, the movie was shot entirely during a two week hiatus from his job directing “Jimmy Kimmel Live”. The film was chosen to compete in Sundance’s 2006 Dramatic competition, and was also in the London, Toronto, and San Sebastian Film Festivals that year. “Sleeping Dogs Lie” was hailed as “earnest and improbably moving” by Esquire Magazine, and “demonically funny and surprisingly sweet” by Rolling Stone. Bobcat credits his failure to appear in the film as a good part of its success.&nbsp; Bobcat&#8217;s new movie “God Bless America” was featured at the 2011 Toronto International Film Festival as one of the festivals Midnight Madness picks. Goldthwait&#8217;s new black comedy stars Joel Murray and Tara Lynne Barr. It&#8217;s a modern Bonnie &amp; Clyde in which a middle-aged guy and a young girl go on a killing spree inspired by hatred for the garbage glut of MTV ‘reality’ shows. Check out the trailer here <a href="http://youtu.be/ul4CZrnEFxU">http://youtu.be/ul4CZrnEFxU</a> <a href="http://www.facebook.com/godblessamericamovie">http://www.facebook.com/godblessamericamovie</a></p>

<p>In 2009 Magnolia pictures released Goldthwait’s film “World’s Greatest Dad”. The movie stars long time friend Robin Williams, and was again made independently from the studio system with a cast made up primarily of close friends, (although this time Process and Darko Productions came on board and prevented any pawn shops from having to be involved). The movie was met with rave reviews; “HILARIOUS” – Washington Post, “See it. A gem with a terrific, remarkably funny script.”– At the Movies, “Scandalously entertaining!”– Village Voice, “****” – Time Out Chicago,&nbsp; “Wonderful” –&nbsp; MTV.&nbsp; Also at Sundance in 2009 was Bobcat’s short film “Goldthwait Home Movies: Anniversary Edition”.&nbsp; Upon hearing that he would have 2 separate films at the festival this year, Bobcat reportedly cried like a little baby girl. “World’s Greatest Dad” is now out on DVD.</p>

<p>Bobcat directed the new movie-musical that he wrote based on The Kink’s 1976 concept album, Schoolboys in Disgrace.&nbsp; Goldthwait’s script tells the story of a schoolboy and his gang who are constantly in trouble with their teachers and fellow pupils.&nbsp; One day, the student is humiliated by his headmaster and vows to fight back against “the Establishment.”&nbsp; The new flick will unfold the genesis story of a supervillian set to some of the greatest rock songs you’ll ever hear.&nbsp; It includes the world’s most charming criminal and a realistic high school musical for all the kids who hate sugary, sweet, unrealistic high-school musical.&nbsp; The songs for the film were written by former Kink’s frontman Ray Davies in which the cast for the movie will re-record the original songs for the film’s soundtrack.</p>

<p>Goldthwait has come a long way from his first appearance on David Letterman at the age of 20. In addition to directing movies Bobcat has lent his behind the camera talents to shows such as; Jimmy Kimmel Live, The Demetri Martin show, The Chappelle Show, The Man Show, and Crank Yankers.&nbsp; Best known for his unforgettable movies that were huge in the 80&#8217;s, Bobcat has also starred in several HBO specials and a slew of television appearances to numerous to mention.&nbsp; Bob continues to push the envelope with his unique brand of humor headlining major comedy clubs across the country and all of this has allowed him to live in an impossibly luxurious rental home in the Los Angeles area.</p>


      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Bobcat_Moustache.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Antoine Blackman</name>
  <slug>antoine-blackman</slug>
  <tag>3 Seasons of BET Comic View and Master P's Hoodstars</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Currently Touring with Eddie Griffin,&nbsp; includes 3 Seasons of BET Comic View, Master P&#8217;s Hoodstars of Comedy DVD Vol. 1, My Big Phat Hip Hop Family, Bikes &amp; Babes DVD.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Antoine_Blackman.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Hilary Schwartz</name>
  <slug>hilary-schwartz</slug>
  <tag>2011 Women in Comedy Festival in Boston</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Ranging from personal subjects to social commentary, Hilary Schwartz’s stand-up comedy is intelligent, dark, honest, and somehow still adorable. She has been heard on XM Radio and seen on MTV. Hilary has been featured in TimeOut New York, Heeb Magazine, and The Washington Post. Hilary has opened for established comedians, including Dave Attell, Cory Kahaney, and Jonathan Katz. She was selected to perform at the 2010 and 2011 Women in Comedy Festival in Boston and appeared in the long-running San Francisco show, Kung Pao Kosher Comedy.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Hilary_Schwartz.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Doug Powell</name>
  <slug>doug-powell</slug>
  <tag>From 98 Rock and XM/Sirius Radio</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Doug Powell has been writing and performing comedy around Washington DC and Baltimore for over a decade. A veteran recording artist, Doug has released four comedy albums and numerous ringtone albums with DC-based Hahaas Comedy. Combining multiple disciplines, Powell twists structured material with improv making each performance a unique experience for both himself and the audience. This past year marked the release of his latest stand-up album/DVD &#8220;I Am You An Hour From Now,&#8221; recorded live at the Frederick Cultural Arts Center by Fool Martyr Productions and Hahaas Comedy. Within the past year Doug has teamed up with Frederick-based Flying Dog Brewery on numerous creative projects. The most recent is a charming burglar who breaks into homes in order to videotape his personal beer reviews. &#8220;Sipping Tom&#8221; as the character is known, has given Powell an opportunity to sharpen his understanding of improv comedy while working with a film crew. Doug Powell is once again slated to co-host this year&#8217;s 72 Film Fest in Frederick, MD along-side good friend and collegue Mikael Johnson. With each passing year Doug Powell hopes to mature and grow as a writer and a performer with the overall goal being a Kung-Fu type mastery of his art.</p>

<p>
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Doug_Powell.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Adam Lehman</name>
  <slug>adam-lehman</slug>
  <tag>From HereTV's stand-up special “Hot Gay Comics”</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Adam Lehman is a staple in the gay comedy circuit, having been featured on HereTV&#8217;s stand-up special “Hot Gay Comics” and as a regular panelist on the popular HereTV.com weekly podcast “Topical.” Outside of New York, he has entertained audiences across the country with his quick wit and creativity, headlining several touring shows in PA, ME, DC, and CA. His successful monthly comedy show “The Brew HAHA” features national headliners and created a new environment for stand-up comedy in the East Village. After moving to New York, Adam studied improv with Second City Training Center and in 2009 made his indie movie debut in &#8220;Jonathan, Just Because&#8221; which was featured in the New York Times.</p>

<p>
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Adam_Lehman.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Zach Toczynski</name>
  <slug>zach-toczynski</slug>
  <tag>Winner Baltimore's "Funniest Person Contest"</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Zach Toczynski burst onto the Washington, DC stand up comedy scene in 2003 by taking a chance at a local open mic hosted by a drag queen at a (now defunct) seedy little gay bar on the wrong side of town,&nbsp; After getting his first laugh he was instantly hooked (like what happens when you take Vicodin, Red Bull and Walker Black).&nbsp; Long story short&#8230; Zach quickly became a instant favorite and a darling on the comedy circuit, not just locally, but cities nation wide!</p>

<p>In 2004, Zach hit the road on his bike to set off on his never ending &#8220;Flamin&#8217; Pollack Tour,&#8221; making appearances in well-known clubs all over the USA and Canada, such as the Riot Act Comedy Theater, Baltimore Comedy Factory, San Fran Comedy Club, and more; featuring for comedy greats, Jim Gaffigan, Caroline Raye, Judah Friedlander and many, many others!</p>

<p>Zach&#8217;s high energy, knack for mockery, grasp of pop culture and commanding stage presence combine ever so nicely with his natural ability of quick, yet smart humor.&nbsp; Zach uses his recently bleached ultra white smile to inflict charm on his viewers, blurring all boundaries making Zach not only like-able, but easily relatable to a diverse range of audiences. </p>

<p>Early on in Zach’s comedy career, he found he possessed natural skills at hosting all sorts of stuff that he knew nothing about!&nbsp; Like in 2005 Zach hosted the London-based smash hit &#8220;Sing-a-Long Sound of Music&#8221; at the George Washington’s Lisner Auditorium; and in 2008 Zach was the featured comic at the “2008 Mr. Leather Maryland” contest&#8230;....I think PETA just egged my website.</p>

<p>A few high points in Zach’s rollercoaster comedy career have been &nbsp; being a featured acts at the DC Comedy Fest 2005, the Baltimore Comedy Fest 2008, and one of the hosts/comedians of the 2007 Capital Pride event in Washington, DC.&nbsp; </p>

<p><br />
Zach is also one of the co-producers, founders, and featured comedians in Washington, DC’s only monthly gay and lesbian comedy showcase called “Gaylarious” which recently won “Best of Gay DC 2011” from the Washington Blade.&nbsp; </p>

<p><br />
Not only is Zach 100% Polish, but also he is Catholic, Queer, Ex-Republican, and from Buffalo, NY ...which admittedly is a lot of crap to deny on a daily basis! He was raised in Kodak-run Rochester, NY by loving, supportive, amazing, parents who tried in vain to create a normal son but apparently the heavy metals in the Monroe County water supply defeated them.</p>

<p>Surprisingly, comedy does not support the lavish lifestyle Zach enjoys full of designer clothes, high class cocktails at noon, and weekend shopping trips to foreign lands for a cute lunch (or KFC at a West Virginia Walmart and warm beer near the dumpsters, it’s all good).&nbsp; So, Zach finds happiness and cash money in his profession as well respected and established international public speaker on law enforcement issues for a trade association.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Zach_Toczynski.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Chris Doucette</name>
  <slug>chris-doucette</slug>
  <tag>1st place winner at 2011 Snubfest Comedy Festival</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>This world is full of surprises, and the stand-up comedy of Chris Doucette is no exception. Weighing in at 110 pounds and measuring under 5’7″, Chris is living proof that big things really do come in small packages. Chris is the son of a trucker and the first in his family to graduate college. He’s got a blue collar attitude with an ivy league wit. Chris also represents the next generation of gay comedians. His audience knows he’s gay and he uses it to full advantage without resorting to stereotypes or cliches. His humor is current, topical, and completely original. Said one audience member, “I hate stand-up comedy – but you, you made me laugh out loud!”</p>

<p>In June 2011, Chris won 1st place at the Snubfest Comedy Festival in Chicago. He has performed for colleges all over the country and recently received a standing ovation from the students at Florida Tech. Chris was selected as a feature comic at the Charleston Comedy Festival, Baltimore Comedy Festival, Baltimore Artscape Festival, and headlined the Ganymede Arts Festival. He has performed on FOX, NPR, The Joey Reynolds Show, WTOP, and WAMU, and Comedy Nonsense. He has appeared in The Washington Post, The Washington Post Express, Miami Sun-Sentinel, Metro Weekly, Time Out New York, Next Magazine, New York Post, and the Village Voice. 
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Chris_Doucette.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Tom Rhodes</name>
  <slug>tom-rhodes</slug>
  <tag>From Comedy Central, NBC and the Montreal Comedy Festival</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Tom Rhodes was born in Washington DC on January 14th, 1967.</p>

<p>At the age of 12 Tom’s father, David Rhodes, a decorated Vietnam war hero with a great sense of humour and a love of stand-up comedy, took Tom to see his uncle Bob perform. The entrance to the room was right next to the stage and as a joke the comedian pulled Tom up because he wearing a Washington Redskins jacket. He interviewed him as if he was the coach of the Washington Redskins. It was that moment on stage in Washington DC, seeing the happy people with their heads thrown back in laughter, that Tom Rhodes decided to be a stand up comedian.</p>

<p>In the end, that makes Tom one of those rare exotic creatures who has dedicated his life to stand-up comedy.&nbsp; He is one of the most sought after comedians working the world wide circuits today and his stunning long list of credits include: His own sitcom on NBC called &#8220;Mr. Rhodes&#8221;. The critically acclaimed Comedy Central special &#8220;Viva Vietnam&#8221; and two &#8220;Comedy Central presents&#8221; half hour specials.</p>

<p>He had his own Late Night talk show in Amsterdam for 3 years &#8220;Kevin Masters starring Tom Rhodes&#8221; as well as presenting a travel show on Dutch television for 1 year &#8220;Yorin Travel&#8221;.</p>

<p>Tom Rhodes is also currently a featured writer for The Huffington Post, writing about whatever catches his fancy as he travels the world as a stand up comedian. In 2012 Tom&#8217;s first ever uncensored hour long stand up special &#8220;Light Sweet Crude&#8221; will air on the Showtime network as well as &#8220;Live in Amsterdam&#8221; featuring provocative comedians from all over the world, also to air on the Showtime network.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/TomRhodesMic.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>The Cabinet</name>
  <slug>the-cabinet</slug>
  <tag>DEZ THE PREZ X DANNI K X B DANIELS -  Funk Master Generals</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>The CABINET’s sound is and eclectic blend of all things POP Culture mixed with a healthy dose of musical inspiration.&nbsp; An artist collective compromised of three very unique sounds blended to create an exciting, rhythmic portrayal of “Good Times”&nbsp; With “Live and Let Party” being the center of the Cabinet’s philosophy, they have a versatile sound that drives deep into almost every sector of music.&nbsp; The greatest inspirations come from the Fugees and the Black Eyed Peas, but the CABINET is also influenced by many great artist of the past and the present.&nbsp; From Sly Stone to Kanye West to David Guetta, a diverse medley of styling that anyone can get up “Live and Let’s Party”
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_The_Cabinet.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Johnny O</name>
  <slug>johnny-o</slug>
  <tag>From Tru TV’s “All Worked Up”</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Johnny O. quit his job as a bond broker in 1999 and started doing standup in September of that year.&nbsp; He basically got tired of people telling him that he should be a comedian and said “What the hell”.&nbsp; Johnny O. has performed all over the country and featured in Canada.&nbsp; He started out at “The Gleason’s Gym” of comedy called “Pips” in Sheepshead Bay, Brooklyn and has performed everywhere from Caroline’s on Broadway to Foxwood’s.&nbsp; He can currently be seen as an angry massage parlor owner on this seasons Tru TV’s “All Worked Up”.&nbsp; His edgy, slightly agitated take on what’s going on in the world has made him a crowd favorite.&nbsp; Johnny O. mixes observational humor along with some killer impressions and a lot of hilarious one-liners that will not soon be forgotten.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Johnny_O.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Basile</name>
  <slug>basile</slug>
  <tag>From HBO, Showtime, Comedy Central and the Jay Leno Show</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Perhaps one of the most explosive diverse entertainers in the world today, Basile has entertained millions of comedy fans in the United States, Canada, Europe, Australia, and Africa.&nbsp; From his “Born to be wild” opening to his Broadway-style closing that would make Walt Disney blush and turn over in his grave… Basile’s unique blend of material, improvisation, and characters has made him one of the most sought after comedians in the entertainment industry today!&nbsp; </p>

<p>Recently nominated for an Emmy for ESPN’s “30 for 30 Series”, “The Legend of Jimmy The Greek”; Basile not only captured the voice of Jimmy “The Greek” Snyder, but also the spirit of the man and the pain that he and his family went through during that turbulent time when fired from CBS’s “NFL TODAY”.&nbsp; Basile’s diversity in entertainment continues as he stars in his critically acclaimed comedy series entitled, “Growing Up Greek in America.”&nbsp; </p>

<p>Basile’s voices and characters have been heard on Armed Forces Radio, Television, Cable, Syndicated Radio in North America, and on SIRIUS/XM Satellite Radio.&nbsp; Basile has over 100 television appearances to his credit throughout the world, from,&nbsp; HBO, Showtime, Comedy Central and the Jay Leno Show on NBC to name a few.&nbsp; Basile is also known for his voice work as Universal Studio’s “Bullwinkle J. Moose”, as well as for the Cartoon Network and many Japanese Anime series.&nbsp; So spice up your comedy pallet and sprinkle some Basile on it! 
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Basile_Smilie.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Mambo Sauce</name>
  <slug>mambo-sauce</slug>
  <tag>High-energy, fresh fusion of old-Soul, new school Hip-Hop, cross-bred with Rock and Go-Go roots</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>The electric-red mystery concoction that is a staple comfort and must-have of Washington, DC, has found itself a namesake, and a sound. Mambo Sauce (the band) brings to life a tapestry of unparallel musicianship. Although their sound is oft described as mystical, it is undisputed by their vast array of loyal fans that this coveted band looks, feels and sounds like pure, unadulterated music. Jawn Murray, Entertainment Reporter with the Tom Joyner Morning Show and columnist with AOL Black Voices called the group’s sound “the quintessential savior the industry needs to return authenticity, quality and pure rhythm to music.” Mambo Sauce delivers a high-energy, fresh fusion of old-Soul (think Marvin Gaye), new school Hip-Hop, cross-bred with Rock and the deep and thick percussions of Go-Go, the indigenous sound of DC.</p>

<p>Mambo Sauce and their company, Mambo Sauce Entertainment, LLC, is not only a band; they are a brand and a movement. Their endeavors include infiltrating the international music market and expanding their talents into other entertainment genres. Mambo Sauce’s zeal and passion for music is only matched by their commitment to community service. They use the “Mambo Sauce” brand to speak out against prevailing societal issues such as the world AIDS epidemic, homelessness, child soldiers in Africa, and domestic violence; and to mentor and educate young people.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Mambo_Sauce.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Cory Fernandez</name>
  <slug>cory-fernandez</slug>
  <tag>From "Who's Got Jokes", Jamie Foxx's "Laffapalooza" and HBO's "Def Comedy Jam"</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Donned as the young veteran, Cory Fernandez is one of the fastest rising stars in comedy today. In 2004 Cory made his debut television appearance as a finalist on BET&#8217;s stand-up comedy competition, &#8220;Coming to the Stage,&#8221; with comedians Kim Coles and Bruce Bruce. Three years later, Cory became the first Puerto Rican on &#8220;Russell Simmons&#8217; Def Comedy Jam&#8221; on HBO (hosted by D.L. Hughley). He has since made his first transition to the big screen in the upcoming 2010 release of &#8220;A Couple of Dicks,&#8221; starring Bruce Willis and Tracy Morgan, and directed by Kevin Smith.</p>

<p>In 2006 Cory performed on Bill Bellamy&#8217;s &#8220;Who&#8217;s Got Jokes&#8221; on TV One and &#8220;Jamie Foxx Presents Laffapalooza&#8221; on Comedy Central. In the same year, NBC/Universal held their annual nationwide search for the top ethnic comics in the country and selected Cory as a finalist.<br />
Cory currently lives in his hometown of New York City and continues to perform at comedy clubs and colleges across the country. 
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Cory_Fernandez.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Chris Thomas</name>
  <slug>chris-thomas</slug>
  <tag>The Mayor of BET’s "Rap City", "Star Search" and HBO</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Comedy came easy for Chris Thomas, at age 8 he learned he had a knack for impersonating just about anybody. At the ripe age of 19, the Washington Star dubbed the young stand-up comedian as an &#8220;impressionist headed no place but up.&#8221; So began Chris’s professional career. However, his swift and steady rise since has lead Chris to become one of the nation’s brightest comedians, and in the words of the Washington Post magazine &#8220;an accomplished impressionist…on his way to fame and fortune.&#8221;</p>

<p>Chris Thomas is the master of over 2000 amazing realistic celebrity impressions, including Denzel Washington, F. Lee Bailey, Mike Tyson, and Orson Welles. One of Chris’s favorite subjects, Sugar Ray Leonard, says &#8220;Chris Thomas knocks me out!&#8221; The Charlotte Observer lauded his ability to &#8220;move like a comic juggernaut from one famous voice to another.&#8221; Chris combines this versatility with a quick wit and deft timing to create remarkably funny conversations between several personalities at once. Chris has added impressions of singers including Frank Sinatra and Jeffrey Osborne, plus outrageous rap numbers to his repertoire to create his own fresh brand of humor.</p>

<p>Audiences have been knocked out by Chris’ stand-up performances at major venues including New York’s Catch A Rising Star and The Comedy Store in Los Angeles. He has performed with an array of artists including Stevie Wonder, Aretha Franklin, Prince, Luther Vandross and Anita Barker. Chris continues his extensive live performance schedule both on his own as well as with fellow comedians, Jamie Foxx and Mark Curry.</p>

<p>Success as a stand-up comedian has allowed Chris to expand his work into all major media’s. His radio work includes weekly appearances on WRKX, New York’s morning show, and the nationally syndicated Chris Thomas Comedy Hour. Advertising work has included such clients as Levis, Xerox, and Lee Jeans. Chris has been featured in film and video work including &#8220;Body and Soul&#8221; and Public Enemy’s &#8220;Fight The Power.&#8221; While television appearances include &#8220;Star Search,&#8221; &#8220;Live At The Apollo,&#8221; and &#8220;The Sugar Ray Leonard Roast.&#8221; Chris’ work on the 1988 Run/DMC and Public Enemy national tours established him as the King of Hip Hop comedy and led to his most popular role as The Mayor of Black Entertainment Televisions’ (BET’s) &#8220;Rap City&#8221;; the cable network’s highest rated show.</p>

<p>Perhaps his biggest break to date, however, has been the opportunity to team up with the renowned Whoopie Goldberg for an HBO comedy special. Whoopie happened to see a tape of Chris&#8217;’ stand-up act, and wanted to give him a wider showcase on the cable channel known for its outstanding comedy programming. As a result, Thomas was one of two featured comedians on Whoopie’s &#8220;Chez Whoopie&#8221; on HBO.</p>

<p>As his audience continues to grow, more and more fans find they converted to Chris’ unique comedy. Meanwhile, he continues to find new ways to keep his fans laughing and coming back for more. He&#8217;s an act you wont want to miss.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Chris_Thomas_BW.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Rob Maher</name>
  <slug>rob-maher</slug>
  <tag>From Comedy Central’s Laugh Riot Competition and 98 Rock</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Rob Maher is a two time finalist in Comedy Central’s Laugh Riot Competition and can be heard regularly on Baltimore’s 98 Rock.&nbsp; Rob’s had the fortunate opportunity to go overseas and perform for our troops. He just got back from a tour through the Middle East including Afghanistan.&nbsp; He’s also been to Japan three times as well as tours throughout Kyrgyzstan, Turkey, Portugal and Italy, Greece and Egypt.&nbsp; <br />
 <br />
As well as comedy Rob is an accomplished actor.&nbsp; He played the lead role in the short film “The P.O.B. Conspiracy.”&nbsp; The film was a 2007 Silver Telly Award Winner and a 2007 DC Independent Film Festival Finalist.&nbsp; Rob can be seen now in two PSA’s.&nbsp; First, the EPA’s Learn Before You Burn and also in nationally airing Flu Shot PSA.<br />
 <br />
Very few comics ever find their voice, but Rob Maher has found his.&nbsp; It’s loud, clear, insightful, confident, and funny.&nbsp; Above all, it’s not to be missed. 
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Rob_Maher_Color.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Adrienne Iapalucci</name>
  <slug>adrienne-iapalucci</slug>
  <tag>NBC's Last Comic Standing and Just For Laughs Comedy Festival in Montreal</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Born and bred in the Bronx, Adrienne Iapalucci&#8217;s skewed look on life is reflected in her unique brand of intelligent comedy. Her dark sense of humor is enhanced by her political incorrectness, and counteracted by her love of puppies.</p>

<p>Comedy fans might recognize Adrienne by her performances as a semifinalist on season 7 of NBC&#8217;s Last Comic Standing.</p>

<p>In 2009, Adrienne won the First-ever People&#8217;s Choice Opening Act Competition, and got the opportunity to perform at NYC&#8217;s Town Hall Theater for 1400 people as part of the New York Comedy Festival. She was also a semifinalist in &#8220;New York&#8217;s Funniest Stand-Up Contest&#8221;, also part of the New York Comedy Festival, and was the runner-up in the 2009 New York Underground Comedy Festival&#8217;s &#8220;Best of the Boroughs&#8221; contest.</p>

<p>Adrienne has been featured in the Daily News, New York Times, Stage Time Magazine and was featured in Reader&#8217;s Digest in the summer of 2010. Later on that summer Adrienne made her International debut as part of the Just For Laughs Comedy Festival in Montreal.</p>

<p>Adrienne can be seen performing throughout New York City, and colleges across the country.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/adrienne_iapalucci.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Brad Loekle</name>
  <slug>brad-loekle</slug>
  <tag>From TruTV, Sirius XM, Nick at Night and The New York Times</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>From TruTV, Sirius XM, Nick at Night and The New York Times
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Brad_Loekle_Chair.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Shahryar</name>
  <slug>shahryar</slug>
  <tag>Runner Up in the Funniest Fed Contest and Voice of America</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Shahryar is a comedian out of the DC area.&nbsp; He&#8217;s been featured in the Washington Post and Voice of America.&nbsp; He was runner up in the Funniest Fed contest and was also voted the funniest contestant in the Washington Post.&nbsp; 
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Shahryar.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Karen Bergreen</name>
  <slug>karen-bergreen</slug>
  <tag>From Comedy Central, USA Network and HBO Comedy Festival </tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p> </p>

<p>I grew up in New York City and then went to Harvard University, where I was the only person I knew who had a TV set in her dorm room (relax, it was black and white and cost fifty dollars). I majored in European history, and spent my summers and free time interning for politicians, museums, and non-profit development organizations. This all prepared me for: you guessed it, a job as a paralegal in a white shoe law firm.</p>

<p>There, I never saw the inside of a courtroom and instead spent seventy hours a week, stapling, collating and proofreading.</p>

<p>I was terrible at all of these things.</p>

<p>I was certain I would never work in a place like this again.</p>

<p>Despite this, I remained optimistic. A fan of LA Law (for those of you who are still confused by the black and white TV reference, this was a TV show), I went to law school at the University of Minnesota. They chose me for my brown hair—I was considered diverse. I chose them for their proximity to some of our nation’s best malls.</p>

<p>After law school, ever hopeful, I started as an associate at another upscale law firm where I worked seventy hours a week stapling collating and proofreading. I was down, but not for long. As luck would have it, I got the opportunity to clerk for a federal district judge. This was the closest to LA Law I would ever get, and I knew it.</p>

<p>When the job ended I made the obvious and predictable transition: I became a comedian.</p>

<p>It was exciting and horrifying at the same time, and remains that way. I have had the opportunity to perform all over the country, sometimes in other countries, (if you count Canada as another country), and with some frequency at just about every club in New York and am currently a regular at Comix, Gotham, and The Comic Strip. I am frequently on Comedy Central, and was a regular panelist on Can You Tell, an ill-fated game show on The Oxygen Network. I’ve been on VH1, Court TV and USA networks. I have performed at the Friars’ Club, the Kennedy Center, the HBO Comedy Festival in Aspen twice (I even had a deal with HBO, but that fizzled—see, I told you it could be horrifying)</p>

<p>I have done some acting, although to be honest my range is limited: I can’t do anything that involves crying or porn, but you might have seen my fine work on Law and Order or on several national commercials hawking products I don’t own.</p>

<p>During all of this, I fell in love with my husband. We got married and we have two kids. We also have anywhere between one and three hermit crabs—they apparently die. And a fish.</p>

<p>The kids, the crabs and the fish require my presence at home. I can’t run around the country making people laugh all the time. Instead, I started to write. A novel seemed easier than a poem. And so I wrote Following Polly.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Karen_Bergreen.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Steve Hofstetter</name>
  <slug>steve-hofstetter</slug>
  <tag>From ESPN, Comedy Central, VH-1 and CBS</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>&#8220;His sterling academic credentials&#8230;combined with his propensity for provoking intelligent laughs, has earned Hofstetter the title of &#8220;The Thinking Man&#8217;s Comic.&#8221;<br />
&nbsp;  &nbsp;   -The Queens Tribune</p>

<p>Author, columnist, and comedian Steve Hofstetter is often called the hardest working man in show-business. With all due respect to the late James Brown.</p>

<p>Hofstetter&#8217;s national TV debut came on ESPN&#8217;s Quite Frankly, where Stephen A. Smith yelled at him for three minutes. Hofstetter has also appeared on CBS&#8217; &#8220;Late Late Show With Craig Ferguson,&#8221; Showtime&#8217;s &#8220;White Boyz in the Hood,&#8221; VH1&#8217;s &#8220;Countdown,&#8221; Sundance&#8217;s &#8220;On the Road in America,&#8221; and ABC&#8217;s &#8220;Barbara Walter&#8217;s Special,&#8221; where he thankfully did not cry. Having appeared on networks from Boston to Miami to Denver, his local television appearances are too numerous to count, especially if you&#8217;re using your fingers.</p>

<p>One of the top booked acts on the college circuit, the original writer for collegehumor.com has also released four albums and three books. Hofstetter has written humor columns for the New York Times, Sports Illustrated.com, and NHL.com, where he publicly admitted to being a Ranger fan.</p>

<p>After hosting Four Quotas on Sirius Satellite Radio for two seasons, Hofstetter moved to broadcast radio, and his Sports Minute (Or So) was syndicated on over 170 stations and in over 30 newspapers. Hofstetter&#8217;s second live comedy album (&#8220;Cure For the Cable Guy&#8221;) reached #20 on Billboard&#8217;s comedy charts. His third album (&#8220;Dark Side of the Room&#8221;) was the first ever pay-what-you-want&#8221; comedy album, since people were going to steal it anyway. His fourth album consisted of an hour of 100% ad-libbed material, which is, frankly, nuts. And his fifth album hit #1 on iTunes&#8217; comedy charts, which is also a bit nuts.</p>

<p>Hofstetter&#8217;s brutal tour schedule consists of over 100 colleges and dozens of clubs every year, and is fueled by an immense online popularity, tons of press, and a Prius with great gas mileage. He reached 200,000 friends on Facebook and 400,000 more on MySpace, and high shelves in grocery stores.</p>

<p>While Hofstetter&#8217;s live shows are routinely sold out, he is best known for his writing, first published at age 15, mainly to impress girls. At 18, he co-founded &#8220;Sports Jerk of the Week,&#8221; an irreverent website featured by press like USA Today&#8217;s Baseball Weekly, Sports Illustrated and CNN. And at 20, Hofstetter took a year off of school to head up web content for the New York Yankees. The Yankees won the World Series that year, which would have been wonderful if they hadn&#8217;t beaten Hofstetter&#8217;s Mets. Yes, he&#8217;s also a Mets fan.</p>

<p>While an undergraduate at Columbia University, Hofstetter was a well-read columnist for the Columbia Daily Spectator and a voice of the Lions. After a summer writing for Maxim, ESPN, and Sports Illustrated for Kids, Hofstetter turned his column into two books, and syndicated it in several newspapers.</p>

<p>Without his glasses, Hofstetter also looks a great deal like Michael Rappaport.</p>

<p>Awards/Accolades</p>

<p>&nbsp;   Nominee, Performer of the Year, Association for the Promotion of Campus Activities (2008)<br />
&nbsp;   Pick of the Week, Milwaukee Express (January, 2008)<br />
&nbsp;   DC Pick of the Week, The Onion (August, 2007)<br />
&nbsp;   Pick of the Week, DC City Paper (August, 2007)<br />
&nbsp;   Nominee, Best Comedy Act, Winthrop University (2007)<br />
&nbsp;   Album Cover of the Month, Stuff Magazine (June, 2006)<br />
&nbsp;   Nominee, Comedian of the Year, Association for the Promotion of Campus Activities (2006)<br />
&nbsp;   20 Under 40, Columbia University (2004)<br />
&nbsp;   Best New Face, Two Drink Minimum Magazine (2004) </p>

<p>
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Steve_Hofstetter.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Sylvia Traymore</name>
  <slug>sylvia-traymore-morrison</slug>
  <tag>Renowned Impressionist</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>When’s the last time you saw Wendy Williams, Diana Ross, Mo’Nique, Whoopi Goldberg and First Lady Michelle Obama in one evening’s performance?&nbsp; Well, all you need to do is catch the Sylvia Traymore Morrison Show the next time she’s in town. 
</p><p>
Originally from Washington, DC, Sylvia is the only renowned African American Female Impressionist in the country.&nbsp; She was one of the first solo artists to tour and open for Whitney Houston when Ms. Houston was one of the biggest names in the entertainment business.&nbsp; The arenas they performed in sometimes housed well over 30,000 people. 
<p>
When heavyweight boxing was at its zenith and Muhammad Ali was in his prime, Sylvia was asked to host a Roast of the Champ at the legendary Apollo Theater. The hosting job was so prolific and the imitation of the World Heavyweight Champion was so spot-on that he looked at her in amazement and said, “You&#8217;’re doin’ me? A woman doin’ me? That’s awesome!”
<p>
As a result of that roast, Sylvia was offered a position as an associate-writer for one of America’s longest-running TV shows, Saturday Night Live.&nbsp; She is one of few African American Women offered that position.&nbsp; Since that time Sylvia has opened for some of the biggest names in the entertainment industry, including Gladys Knight, Chaka Khan, The Temptations, and Cher. 
<p>
Most recently, she has worked with Yolanda Adams and Marcus D. Wiley. 
<p>
As the result of her profound career, Sylvia has released her first book, based on her true story, entitled &#8220;Almost There, Almost&#8230;The Many Faces of Sylvia Traymore Morrison.&#8221; 
<p>
The proud mother of two daughters, Jasmin and Michelle, she is presently engaged in the DC Urban Arts Project, where she is being honored for her many contributions to the industry, while working the national comedy circuit and also starring in the 5th Commandment Tour.&nbsp; She&#8217;s a lot of fun to watch!&nbsp; 
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Sylvia_Traymore_Fist.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Irwin Loring</name>
  <slug>irwin-loring</slug>
  <tag>Winner of best new talent comic at the Comedy Outlet 2008</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>It all began when he was 16 years old watching an HBO comedy special featuring David Brenner , he wanted to be a comedian, and in 1980, and on a Friday night in November 2006 in Rockville, Maryland, Irwin finally took the stage for the first time. Since then, he has been on stage  hundreds of times. He has performed in comedy clubs, bars, and even at his own high school reunion.<br />
His comedy revolves around his family, relationships, religion, and society in general.&nbsp; He was raised in a farming community in upstate New York, by a single Jewish mother household.&nbsp; He blames his mother for his bizarre views on parenting,&nbsp; and his overall outlook on life.&nbsp; He brings an energy to the room that makes audiences laugh wherever he performs.&nbsp; His style can be described as a mix of David Brenner and George Carlin, with a touch of Don Rickles. </p>

<p>He was a finalist in the 2007 “Comic of the Year” competition for  Maryland, Washington DC and Virginia,&nbsp; was the winner of best new talent comic at the Reading Comedy Outlet 2008, and a finalist in the Big Break Comedy Competition in 2009.&nbsp; He currently teaches comedy classes at a local college for aspiring comics, focusing on the business of comedy and writing.&nbsp; Irwin has performed in venues ranging from New York staples such as the Laugh Factory, Comix, Broadway Comedy Club, New York Comedy Club and Gotham Comedy Club, to the Tropicana Hotel and Casino in Atlantic City, to more regional clubs such as the The Comedy Zone, Reading Comedy Outlet, Liberty Laughs VA, and the Baltimore Comedy Factory.&nbsp; He also participated in the Guinness Book of World Records Longest Consecutive Comedy Show at Magooby’s Joke House in 2011.&nbsp; He has also co-produced a comedy variety show for a local public television station in Montgomery County MD.</p>


      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Irwin_Loring.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Mark Matusof</name>
  <slug>mark-matusof</slug>
  <tag>From CNBC, XM Radio and "The Bob and Tom Show"</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Ma-tu-sof (ma-tu-sof) n. 1. A comedian based in Washington D.C. who has been described in the press as: &#8220;funny without being vulgar or nasty&#8221; and &#8220;going the smarter, hipper direction to the joke&#8221;. </p>

<p>2. Natural habitat: Clubs, colleges, corporate events, country clubs, and cruise ships. Sightings include: &#8220;Night Shift&#8221;, CNBC&#8217;s America&#8217;s Talking Network, XM Satellite Radio and the nationally syndicated &#8220;Bob and Tom&#8221; radio show. Opening act for a CBS David Copperfield special.</p>

<p>3. Diet: Material ranging from his immigrant family to the aggravations of modern life, current events and the fragility of the male ego. A little music tossed for dessert!</p>

<p>- Syn. 1. One who misuses the mandolin for fun and/or profit.</p>

<p>[Prob. Slavic - Former aerospace engineer fast becoming a favorite entertainer across North America from Las Vegas to the Bahamas. His comedy is clever, thoughtful, and most importantly, hilarious!</p>


      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Mark_Matusof.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Joe Recca</name>
  <slug>joe-recca</slug>
  <tag>Winner of "Coming to the Stage", "Def Comedy Jam" and "Showtime at the Apollo"</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Joe&#8217;s comedy relates to everyone no matter what your background laughter is the common denominator that breaks down barriers.&nbsp; We might come from different walks of life but we all laugh the same. My comedy is a ministry designed to entertain, uplift and inspire comedy should take you to another place so that you leave better than you came.
</p><p>
What does HBO, &#8220;Showtime at the Apollo&#8221; and BET&#8217;s &#8220;Comic View&#8221; have in common?&nbsp; Joe Recca has appeared on all of them.&nbsp; In addition Joe was DL Hughley&#8217;s head writer for &#8220;The Kings of Comedy&#8221; movie.
<p>
Joe has been to Iraq and Afghanistan to entertain the troops. And was the last season winner of BET&#8217;s &#8220;Coming to the Stage&#8221;....BET&#8217;s number one rated show.&nbsp; Joe also recently appeared on &#8220;Comics Unleashed&#8221; with Byron Allen.
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Joe_Recca_Smile.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Eddie Bryant</name>
  <slug>eddie-bryant</slug>
  <tag>From Jamie Foxx's Laffapalooza!, BET's "Coming to the Stage", Starz</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Creativity, perserverance, ingenuity and a sincere gift for tickling the funny bone are just a few characteristics to describe Eddie Bryant, of our nation&#8217;s capital.&nbsp; Coupled with a perfect sense of timing and delivery, &#8216;Eddie B&#8217; can take the mundane particle of life and flip it into a side-splitting &#8216;Where&#8217;d that come from?&#8217; work of art that gives critics cause to pause and take notice of this on-the-rise comedic talent. Eddie Bryant&#8217;s comedic brilliance captures and retains the attention of audiences and takes them on a smooth ride to the other side of hilarity.&nbsp; His talent takes him from writing impeccable material to stand-up, to the world of acting.&nbsp; He currently is the owner/proprietor and weekly show host of the Laugh Out Loud Comedy Club&#8212;which is one of only six remaining urban comedy clubs in the country! 
</p><p>
Eddie has blessed stages across the nation winning a supportive fan base wherever he goes.&nbsp; Comedy lovers of diverse backgrounds show him nothing but love because they recognize his unmistakable talent!&nbsp; His credits include:&nbsp; Martin Lawrence Presents the 1st Amendment Standup on STARZ; Finalist, Bay Area Black Comedy Competition-2008, Oakland, CA; HBO Mobile, (TV), WDC; Jamie Foxx&#8217;s Laffapalooza! 2005 &#8220;Fresh Faces&#8221; Showcase, Atlanta, GA; Sierra Mist 2005 &#8220;Next Great Comic&#8221; Semi-Finalist, National Competition; BET&#8217;s &#8220;Coming To The Stage&#8221; 2004.
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Eddie_Bryant_BW.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Adam Dodd</name>
  <slug>adam-dodd</slug>
  <tag>From MTV, VH1, and UPN's 'On Air With Ryan Secrest' with Adam Sandler</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Adam Dodd is one name you&#8217;ll want to remember.
</p><p>
Strapped with his guitar, he&#8217;s toured coast-to-coast, performing his unique style of musical comedy at colleges and comedy clubs all over. He&#8217;s been featured on MTV, VH1, and UPN&#8217;s &#8216;On Air With Ryan Secrest&#8217; with Adam Sandler. Dodd was also selected to perform at the &#8216;Las Vegas Comedy Festival&#8217;, spotlighted on collegehumor.com, as well as, being named one of MySpace&#8217;s Top-Featured Comedians.
<p>
Splitting his time between VA and California, Adam recently kicked off his east coast &#8216;Wasted Crabcake&#8217; tour, and is currently penning a movie script and recording a new hip-hop album.
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Adam_Dodd_Guitar.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Nema Williams</name>
  <slug>nema-williams</slug>
  <tag>From BET's "Comic View", "P. Diddy's Bad Boys of Comedy" and Comedy Central</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Nema Williams stepped right into a spot on BET&#8217;s &#8220;Comic View&#8221; and never looked back! He&#8217;s appeared on BET&#8217;s &#8220;Comic View&#8221; 7 times, on Cedrick the Entertainer&#8217;s &#8220;Starting Line Up&#8221;, in addition to &#8220;Comic Groove&#8221; on Comedy Central, Sean Puffy Combs&#8217;s &#8220;Bad Boys of Comedy on HBO! Nema has gone back to his roots in Theater in the Stage Play &#8220;I Sing 4 Luv&#8221;, a Gospel Play Starring Howard Hewett, James Avery, Dawn Lewis &amp; Freda Payne. Nema has been able to return to Asia several tines Entertaining the Troops in Korea, Japan &amp; Iraq with the USO! Most Recently performed on the LOL Comedy Festival on Showtime &amp; &#8220;Martin Lawrence&#8217;s Presents 1st Amendment Comedy Special!
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Nema_Williams_Riot_Act.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Jay Phillips</name>
  <slug>jay-phillips</slug>
  <tag>From "The Late Show", "Semi Pro" with Will Ferrell and "Baby Mama"</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>One of the Variery&#8217;s &#8220;10 Comics To Watch&#8221; for 2008-2009, Jay Phillips&#8217; recent film credits include &#8220;Semi-Pro&#8221; opposite Will Ferrell, &#8220;Prom Night&#8221; with Brittany Snow and &#8220;Baby Mama&#8221; opposite Tina Fey and Amy Poehler. Jay’s recent television credits include his recurring role on NBC’s &#8220;Kath and Kim&#8221; and his role opposite Donald Sutherland in the pilot &#8220;The Eastman&#8217;s&#8221; for CBS. Jay’s stand-up credits include HBO’s &#8220;Def Comedy Jam,&#8221; &#8220;The Late Show&#8221; and &#8220;Laffapalooza.&#8221; 
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Jay_Phillips_WhiteLean.jpeg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Yamaneika</name>
  <slug>yamaneika</slug>
  <tag>Considered New York City's favorite comic among gay audiences</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Considered New York City&#8217;s favorite comic among gay audiences, Yamaneika is bold, bawdy, and takes no prisoners. She brought down the house on Fire Island with a tour de force performance that resulted in a well-earned standing ovation. Her unorthodox brand of humor has enlightened and entertained audiences from Los Angeles to New York. A native of Baltimore, Yamaneika deals with such topics as the Baptist Church and why women have to go kayaking in the middle of the Pacific Ocean to discuss feminine hygiene. Yamaneika entertains  with her intense energy and quick wit. Recently, she taped a DVD with Tigar Star Productions that is currently on sale and continues to work on independent comedy projects in New York City. 
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Yamaneika.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Leah Bonnema</name>
  <slug>leah-bonnema</slug>
  <tag>One Huffington Post's Favorite 53 Female Comedians</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Leah Bonnema is a Stand-Up Comic in New York City. Huffington Post recently named her one of their ‘Favorite 53 Female Comedians’ and College Candy listed Leah as one the ‘Ten Funniest Female Comics.’ She has been featured on WeTV’s ‘Cinematherapy,’ The BBC, Logo TV, SiriusXM Radio (Patrice O’Neal’s ‘The Black Philip Show’ on Opie and Anthony’s Virus Channel, Maxim Radio and OutQ) and on various podcasts such as the popular shows ‘Keith and the Girl’ and ‘Gandhi, is that You?!’&nbsp; Leah has opened for comedy legends Paul Mooney, Pat Cooper and Gilbert Gottfried. She has had the honor of performing for the troops in Iraq, toured throughout the Middle East and performed for the US Marines at the famed Friar’s Club. Leah was a finalist in ‘The New York&#8217;s Funniest Competition’ during the NY Comedy Festival at renowned Caroline’s on Broadway and has just returned from featuring on ‘The America Stands Up Showcase’ at The Magner&#8217;s Glasgow Comedy Festival in Scotland. . Leah headlined the ‘Breakout Artist Series’ at Caroline&#8217;s on Broadway July 2011 for which she received a ‘Top Pick’ by AM NY Newspaper. Leah also performed on the first ever Maine Comedy Festival in August 2011. This year Holly Pinafore Magazine featured Leah as their ‘It Girl’ and described her as “...brash and bold, leaving no prisoners and issuing no apologies…A New York City comic, the kind that leaves a trail of “Oh-my-gosh did she just say that?” in her wake. The answer is: Yes she did.” </p>


      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Leah_Bonnema.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Eddie Griffin</name>
  <slug>eddie-griffin</slug>
  <tag>From HBO, Comedy Central and "Undercover Brother"</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>A popular comedian turned actor who started his career on-stage as a dare, funnyman Eddie Griffin has built an ever-growing fan base since jumping onto the comedy scene in 1990.<br />
 </p><p>
Born in Kansas City, Missouri, Eddie was voted class clown three years in a row in high school. His first love was always dance and by the young age of 16, he opened his own dance studio and was choreographing the Kansas City Chiefs half-time shows. But all of that would soon change when one night his cousin dared him to go on stage at the local comedy club Sanford and Sons where he was told to do 3 minutes. He performed off-the-cuff for 45 minutes successfully. It was then that Griffin purchased a one-way ticket to Los Angeles to pursue his dream of becoming a stand up.
<p>
In only one short month, he was a regular at the renowned Comedy Store, where he was compared with esteemed talents such as Richard Pryor, Redd Foxx, and Lenny Bruce. After only 2 short months, Griffin was chosen to open for Andrew Dice Clay at Madison Square Garden that kicked off a 22-city tour.
<p>
These many successful performances led to Eddie Griffin&#8217;s appearance on Russell Simmons&#8217; Def Comedy Jam"1992&#8221;, the Cable Ace Award-nominated HBO special One Night Stand &#8220;1992&#8221;, HBO Comedy Half Hour Special &#8220;1995&#8221;, the HBO special Voodoo Child &#8220;1997&#8221; and onstage at the legendary Apollo Theater. He also recorded the successful comedy albums Message In The Hat &#8220;1993&#8221; and The Message &#8220;1999&#8221; featuring comedic and musical performances by him as well as Master P, Sikk the Shocker, and Fiend.
<p>
Griffin began branching out into acting.
Roles in such films as The Last Boy Scout &#8220;1991&#8221;, Coneheads &#8220;1993&#8221;, and Jason&#8217;s Lyric &#8220;1994&#8221; soon led to his own hit comedy series Malcolm and Eddie &#8220;1996-2000&#8221;, for which role he was nominated (1996) and won (2000) the NAACP Image Award for Best Actor in a Comedy Series. In addition to lending his acting experience to this sitcom, he also wrote and directed four episodes, one of which starred his mentor and Richard Pryor.
After, he was offered a lead role in Double Take &#8220;2001&#8221; alongside Orlando Jones. Griffin then starred alongside Denzel Washington in John Q &#8220;2002&#8221;, earning him respect as a dramatic actor. Shortly thereafter, his leading-man status lead to his role as Anton Jackson in Undercover Brother &#8220;2002&#8221;. Mr. Griffin&#8217;s extensive film resume includes films such as and Armageddon &#8220;1998&#8221;, and the worldwide successful comedy franchise Deuce Bigalow: Male Gigolo &#8220;1999&#8221; and Deuce Bigalow: European Gigolo &#8220;2005&#8221;, as well as Date Movie &#8220;2006&#8221;, Scary Movie 3"2003&#8221;, My Baby&#8217;s Daddy &#8221; 2004&#8221; &#8220;which he starred, wrote and Executive Produced for Miramax. 
<p>
Eddie also contributed and performed on Dr. Dre&#8217;s Multi-Platinum selling albums The Chronic &#8220;1992&#8221; and Chronic 2001 &#8220;2001&#8221;.
Eddie Griffin is widely known for his award winning Comedy Stand-up Special Dysfunktional Family &#8220;2003&#8221; which he starred, wrote, Executive Produced and performed on the film&#8217;s soundtrack with Snoop Dogg, Dr. Dre and Tupac.
Eddie most recently starred alongside Eddie Murphy in the hit feature Norbit &#8220;2007&#8221; and starred, wrote and Executive Produced his next comedy special Freedom Of Speech &#8220;2007&#8221;. Later that year he contributed to and performed on T-Pain&#8217;s worldwide successful album Circus &#8220;2008&#8221; and starred in Disney&#8217;s Beethoven&#8217;s Big Break &#8220;2008&#8221;. 
<p>
Eddie&#8217;s most recent comedy special YOU CAN TELL &#8216;EM I SAID IT premiered on Comedy Central on February 19, 2011.
<p>
Comedy Central honored him as the Top 100 Greatest Stand-ups of all time.
Eddie Griffin has conquered not only the stage, but the silver screen as well. 
<p>
Eddie has appeared in 47 films and numerous television shows.
In addition to his Comedic talent, Griffin is also a gifted Actor, Dancer, Choreographer and Singer.
Eddie Griffin is a highly accomplished individual who has contributed significantly to the arts and the entertainment industry and is a star and gifted entertainer in the entertainment world.
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Eddie_Griffin_BlueHat.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>LeAnn Rimes</name>
  <slug>leann-rimes</slug>
  <tag>Winner of two Grammy® Awards, Three Academy of Country Music Awards and 12 Billboard Music Awards.</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>LeAnn Rimes has sold more than 37 million albums, won two Grammy® Awards, three Academy of Country Music Awards and 12 Billboard Music Awards. Rimes is the youngest recipient of a Grammy® Award, and was also the first country recording artist to win in the “Best New Artist” category. Rimes has placed 42 singles on the Billboard Hot Country Songs chart, 13 of which are top-10 hits, and has scored numerous hit singles in her career, including “Can’t Fight the Moonlight” which went #1 in 11 countries, and “How Do I Live,” which is the second longest charting song ever on the Billboard Hot 100 chart.<br />
Rimes is as an accomplished actress and author, including writing two children’s books Jag and Jag’s New Friend, as well as the novel, Holiday in Your Heart and the inspirational book What I Cannot Change. LeAnn recently released two songs from her forthcoming album, Lady &amp; Gentlemen, where she reinterprets classic country songs by men, including the Grammy® nominated song “Swingin’” and the original new song, “Crazy Women.”
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_LeeAnn_Rimes_1.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Dylan Ratigan</name>
  <slug>dylan-ratigan</slug>
  <tag>Host of NBC's "The Dylan Ratigan Show"</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Dylan Ratigan is the host of msnbc&#8217;s &#8220;The Dylan Ratigan Show,&#8221; an opinion and analysis-fueled daily broadcast program airing weekdays at 4pm on MSNBC. Ratigan also writes regularly for the Huffington Post and produces one of America’s most insightful and provocative podcast’s &#8220;Radio Free Dylan&#8221; and dylanratigan.com. His upcoming book to be published by Simon &amp; Schuster later this year, is tentatively titled &#8220;Greedy Bastards.&#8221;</p>

<p>Ratigan’s political commentary is a throw-back to ambitious reformers exemplified by Teddy Roosevelt in the early 1900’s. Central to this mission is a fearless engagement of powerful private and public interests that seek to protect their power and profits by depriving America of its core values of fairness and equal opportunity</p>

<p>The country, now more than ever, needs passionate debate and smart policy, a brazen willingness to scrap what doesn&#8217;t work, and the entrepreneurial spirit to try what does. It needs heroes to take on the establishment, and fight for the new American ideal. Ratigan is one of this movement&#8217;s most powerful mouthpieces.</p>

<p><br />
Previously, Ratigan worked and thrived on the front lines of global finance and trade for nearly 10 years at Bloomberg LP, where he established multiple beats, including their coverage of mergers and acquisitions. He launched and hosted their flagship morning tv broadcast and ultimately consolidated and oversaw Bloomberg News’ worldwide coverage of banking, investment, insurance and hedge funds as their founding Global Managing Editor for Corporate Finance.</p>

<p>In 2003, Ratigan joined CNBC where he created and hosted Fast Money in addition to co-anchoring CNBC&#8217;s The Call and Closing Bell. From seven trips to the World Economic Forum, to 5 to Warren Buffett’s annual meeting, to thousand’s of interviews in dozens of countries, Dylan understands the structural economic unfairness rotting America&#8217;s core and he&#8217;s not afraid to call it for what it is.</p>

<p>Following the 2008 financial crisis, Ratigan resigned his position at CNBC and launched The Dylan Ratigan Show on msnbc.&nbsp; Disgusted and disturbed by the rampant evidence of fraud, the theft and cover-up in American government, mega banks and mega-corporations, he is on a mission to create fairness for all Americans.&nbsp; Using the mantra &#8220;Truth to Power&#8221;, he focuses on showing the audience ideas that are working and making sure the government helps provide a level playing field as we need to make the American dream more reachable by more people. 
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Dylan_Ratigan_Desk.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Andy Hendrickson</name>
  <slug>andy-hendrickson1</slug>
  <tag>Winner at HBO's U.S. Comedy Arts Festival </tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Andy Hendrickson is a New York City based comedian and writer. He was a showcase winner at HBO&#8217;s U.S. Comedy Arts Festival in Aspen, performed at TBS&#8217; The Comedy Festival in Las Vegas and a finalist at the Great American Comedy Festival. He has performed at well over 100 colleges and is a favorite headliner at comedy clubs across the country. In New York City, Andy appears regularly at the world famous Comedy Cellar. Internationally, Andy has performed at clubs and festivals throughout Canada, England, Holland and Ireland, as well as throughout the Middle East to entertain the troops. He&#8217;s had multiple appearances on the nationally syndicated Bob and Tom radio and TV show and his CD, It&#8217;s Ready, airs regularly on SiriusXM Radio.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Andy_Hendrickson_GreyShirt_1.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Ben Lerman</name>
  <slug>ben-lerman</slug>
  <tag>From The Upright Citizens Brigade, Logo TV and Sirius Satellite Radio</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>If the Flight of the Conchords and Zach Galifianakis raised a secular Christmas miracle baby, it would be NYC&#8217;s ukulele comedian Ben Lerman. Lerman is a rising star of the New York Comedy scene, playing at all the top New York Comedy clubs and theaters like Caroline&#8217;s, Gotham, Comix, and The Upright Citizens Brigade Theater.
</p><p>
Ben tours internationally playing theaters and festivals. His career has been propelled by appearances on Logo TV, Here TV, and Sirius Satellite Radio, where he is recurring guest on the Frank DeCaro Show. Ben has become a regular guest on &#8220;Keith &amp; the Girl,&#8221; the most popular independent podcast in the world with more than a million downloads per month. In 2010, podcast fans voted him &#8220;Best New Guest&#8221; from among a pool of top-notch comedians.
<p>
Armed with his wee ukulele, powerful voice, and twisted point of view, Ben gets huge laughs because his songs have real emotion behind them. From a pirate love story to a lullaby for crazy people, Ben&#8217;s songs point to the humor in all of our lives and relationships, and in the world around us. His affable nature and playful wit have made his live show a perennial hit in Chicago, as Time Out Chicago raved, &#8220;Lerman&#8217;s stage presence is his best asset.&#8221;
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Ben_Lerman.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Josh Blue</name>
  <slug>josh-blue</slug>
  <tag>From NBC's "Last Comic Standing" and Comedy Central</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Josh Blue has been a fast-rising star since first appearing on Comedy Central’s “Mind of Mencia” before gaining the attention and endearment of the country as a favorite on NBC’s “Last Comic Standing.”&nbsp; Josh is a diverse and triumphant individual - hilarious stand-up comedian, stand-out guest star on television, talented artist, and stellar U.S. Paralympic Soccer player – refusing to bow to any of the challenges that come from living with Cerebral Palsy.&nbsp; Blue jokes, “I realize that people are going to stare so I want to give them something to stare at.”&nbsp; Josh uses his incredible sense of humor and versatile persona to defy stereotypes and encourage others to overcome their preconceived notions about people who are considered “disabled.”&nbsp; His unique brand of “reverse teasing” affords him the great joy of “humbling condescending people.”&nbsp; 
</p><p>
Josh’s stand-out performances at the 2004 Las Vegas Comedy Festival earned him $10,000 as Grand Prize Winner of the Royal Flush Comedy Competition.&nbsp; He has appeared on NBC, MSNBC, FOX News, and Fox Sports Net.&nbsp; In 2005, Josh emerged as a major force on the college circuit with Main Stage Showcases that garnered rave reviews and a helped earn him a nomination for BEST DIVERSITY EVENT OF 2006 by APCA.&nbsp; A Lewis &amp; Clark College programmer remarked “Not only did Josh Blue receive a standing ovation, but he was the funniest comedian of the entire three day convention.”  <p>

From comedy clubs and theater engagements to college campuses and
corporate events, wherever he takes the stage Josh elicits a wildly appreciative crowd response.&nbsp; His uncanny ability to improvise with any audience coupled with comedic timing rarely found in a performer of his age has enabled Josh to rapidly develop a fan base across the country.&nbsp; His rise is perhaps best described by a well known club owner following a recent show when he exclaimed:
“Josh is rolling like a ROCK STAR!”
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Josh_Blue_by_Bryce_Boyer.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Dave George</name>
  <slug>dave-george</slug>
  <tag>Winner of DC's Best New Standup!</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Winner of DC&#8217;s &#8220;Best New Standup&#8221; Dave George is a regular on the local comedy scene and has performed in clubs and casinos around the country. East Coast air travelers may remember Dave as Independence Air&#8217;s &#8220;FLYi Guy&#8221;&#8212;America&#8217;s most beloved defunct airline mascot. Recently, Dave has been a featured writer for AOL News, providing humorous commentary on current events, as well as starring in a series of man-on-the-street interviews in and around Washington. Dave&#8217;s offbeat sense of humor, confident stage presence and quick-footed audience interactions are guaranteed to get a crowd going.</p>


      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Dave_George.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Marcus Brown</name>
  <slug>marcus-brown</slug>
  <tag>Finalist in the Big Easy DC Regional Comedy Festival</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>A native Washingtonian, Marcus Brown became interested in stand up comedy after keeping all of his co-workers in the back of the staff meetings, all of the people sitting in hearing distance at church, and anyone inquiring &#8220;how life has been?,&#8221; in stitches minutes after talking. No matter the situation Marcus is good for laughs (many times unintentionally) .
</p><p>
A full-time idiot, he decided to use his quick wit and ignorant since of humor to not only educate and inspire the youth but entertain and motivate adults. 
Marcus&#8217; versatile, educated, and creatively urban style of comedy has caused him to quickly become a fan favorite in the Washington, D.C. area sharing the stage with such famous comedians as Renaldo Rey, Bruce Bruce, Rickey Smiley, Tony Woods, Michael Blackson, JB Smoove, Gary Gulman, Joe Clair, Mike Brooks, Gary Gulman, and Chris Tucker. Bringing laughs to everyone he encounters, Marcus Brown has appeared at Teddy&#8217;s House of Comedy, Zigs Comedy Zone, WiseAcres Comedy Club, the Comedy Dock, Baltimore Comedy Factory, Jokers Wild, Five Seasons, Tuckers Comedy Club, Jokes on Us, Laugh Lounge NYC,&nbsp; Comic Strip Live, Laugh Out Loud Comedy Club, Broadway Comedy Club, Gotham Comedy Club, UDC, George Washington, and Howard Universities as well as various clubs, bars, and venues along the East Coast. In 2007 Marcus was the comedic entertainment for DTLR’s Corporate Christmas celebration. 
<p>
In 2009 Marcus appeared in a Sierra Mist online commercial showcasing his comedic talent, and was a Finalist in the Big Easy DC Regional Comedy Festival as well as the Kaleidescope Comedy “So You Think You’re Funny” Annual Comedy Contest in 2010. In 2011 he was chosen to perform in the Staten Island Comedy Festival as a feature in the &#8220;Kings of the Capital&#8221; show with fellow DC Native and Last Comic Standing Finalist Rob Cantrell.
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Marcus_Brown_Jacket.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Jeff Maurer</name>
  <slug>jeff-maurer</slug>
  <tag>Semifinalist on NBC's "Last Comic Standing", 2009 Winner Funniest Fed</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Jeff Maurer was a Semifinalist on Season 7 of Last Comic Standing and is known in the Washington area as a blogger for the Washington Post and the face of the Washington Auto Show&#8217;s &#8220;Dr. Guy&#8221; ad campaign. He has been featured on Sirius Satellite Radio and Comcast on Demand, and also won the 2009 Funniest Fed Contest and the 2008 Drafthouse Comedy Challenge. A DC resident, he was recently featured at the Great American Comedy Festival and has been seen at clubs and colleges across the country and in Europe. 
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Jeff_Maurer.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Lamont King</name>
  <slug>lamont-king</slug>
  <tag>From Spike TV, CBS, UPN and Comedy Central</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>For years Lamont King was known as &#8216;Lazee Lamont&#8217; on nationally syndicated morning radio, but he is far from a slacker. His cynical and irreverent persona compliments his nonchalant demeanor, which he is known for. His clever yet conversational style on stage as a stand-up comedian has been winning audiences over for nearly a decade. His skill at improvising, celebrity impressions, and original characters make for a hilarious mix of thought provoking observational comedy and side-splitting act outs. 
</p><p>
Lamont has appeared on CBS (&#8220;Gary Unmarried&#8221;), UPN (&#8220;All Of Us&#8221;), Comedy Central (&#8220;The Showbiz Show&#8221;), SpikeTV (&#8220;Manswers&#8221;), BET (&#8220;Comic View/Bring That Week Back&#8221;) and co-stars in the movies &#8220;Love For Sale&#8221; and &#8220;Something Like A Business&#8221;. He is an alumni of the National Lampoon&#8217;s Lemmings sketch comedy troupe and was a writer for the legendary George Wallace. You can read some of his hilarious social commentary as he is a regular contributor to &#8220;The Humor Mill Magazine&#8221;. He has worked along-side some of the biggest names in the industry while still producing his own comedy shows in LA and DC. 
<p>
On the radio Lamont also had recurring roles on The Tom Joyner Show’s “It’s Your World” radio soap, as a writer and voice actor, and was a co-host on The John Salley Block Party with Ananda Lewis on 100.3-FM The Beat in Los Angeles. He made a name for himself with a nation-wide audience as a main cast-member on the nationally-syndicated Russ Parr Morning Show for six years, and he makes occasional appearances on Foxxhole Radio (Jamie Foxx&#8217;s SiriusXM channel). Currently he hosts his own Hot-Talk radio show called Street Senators Radio which broadcasts from Washington, DC.

      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Lamont_King.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Jimmy Meritt</name>
  <slug>jimmy-meritt</slug>
  <tag></tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Because he’s amazing at comedy, Jimmy Meritt is a nationally touring feature act for clubs and colleges, performing in 38 states a year! Thanks to his geeky charm, clever writing, and high-energy performance, he’s quickly become a crowd favorite!
</p><p>
Jimmy has worked with Saturday Night Live’s Norm Macdonald, Kevin Nealon, The Cast Of ABC’s Whose Line Is It Anyway, Last Comic Standing’s Ralphie May, VH1’s Doug Benson, and Maria Bamford!. I know, right?

      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Jimmy_Meritt.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Sean &#8220;Joxe&#8221; Savoy</name>
  <slug>sean-savoy</slug>
  <tag>From Comdy Central and International touring opener for Pablo Francisco</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Considered to have a noticeably refreshing style of comedy, whose voices and characters bring a sense of newness to the craft, while his laid back demeanor and witty ideals are a huge hit with audiences. His themes are universal enough to be understood by all demographics of people in all corners of the world.
</p><p>
Sean is not just one of the rising great stars of the east coast. In fact, he has even traveled the globe entertaining and delighting audiences throughout the US, Europe, and even Japan. He captures you right from the start and takes you on a ride of wacky thoughts that make you think of something differently than you are used to think.
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Joxe_BW_Close.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Larry XL</name>
  <slug>larry-xl</slug>
  <tag>Finalist Philly's Funniest Contest, 98 Rock and XM Satllite Radio</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Larry XL is ready to rock the house. Larry XL&#8217;s wacky style has made him a favorite with audiences from Florida to Canada. He&#8217;s been a finalist in comedy competitions in his native Baltimore and neighboring cities like Washington, DC and Philadelphia. Soon after he started performing at area clubs, Larry XL recorded a concert CD with the DC Standup All-Stars, DC Standup vs. Earth and later his own live DVD, 2009’s Crowd Control. He then hit the road performing in some of the nation&#8217;s best comedy clubs, and anywhere else with electricity, opening for the likes of Bobby Slayton, John Witherspoon, Jim Florentine, Finesse Mitchell and Charlie Murphy. He has also been heard on XM Satellite Radio and Baltimore&#8217;s 98 Rock.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Larry_XL_BW.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Jermaine Fowler</name>
  <slug>jermaine-fowler</slug>
  <tag>Rising star and a comic to look out for</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Jermaine Fowler has all the tools to be a comedy superstar: confidence, intelligence, bravery, and he&#8217;s only 22 years old.&nbsp; He moved from Washington DC to New York City when he was 19 to live the dream; and he is well on his way.&nbsp; Jermaine is already playing some of the better comedy clubs in NYC and has been seen in commercials for McDonald&#8217;s, Bud Light and Starbuck&#8217;s.&nbsp; Jermaine also performed on behalf of Riot Act at this years&#8217; DC101/Lindy Promotion New Year&#8217;s Eve Party at The Grand Hyatt with over three thousand people in attendance.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Jermaine_Fowler_BW.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>John Betz Jr</name>
  <slug>john-betz-jr</slug>
  <tag>Voted Carolina's Funniest Comic in 2009 </tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Fresh off an appearance at the inaugural Laughing Skull Comedy Festival in Atlanta, John uses well-written material with killer delivery, impeccable timing, fantastic facial expressions and cleverly-placed voice inflections to entertain audiences to the point where they might wet themselves.&nbsp; His jovial demeanor and ability to relate well with people makes it easy to see why he&#8217;s considered America&#8217;s Funniest Math Teacher.&nbsp; John was voted Carolina&#8217;s Funniest Comic 2009.&nbsp; 
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/John_Betz.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Jeff Kreisler</name>
  <slug>jeff-kreisler</slug>
  <tag>Winner of the Bill Hicks Spirit Award for Thought Provoking Comedy and author of the bestselling satire book "Get Rich Cheating"</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Jeff is a host on the Progressive Radio Network, a regular contributor to MSNBC and Headline News, a writer for Comedy Central, TheFinalEdition.com, Huffington Post, TheStreet.com and IFC, cast member of Shoot The Messenger, executive editor of &#8220;My Wall Street Journal&#8221; and star of several hit international festival shows.&nbsp; Jeff Kreisler dissects America with passion, absurdity and hope which made him the winner of the coveted Bill Hicks Spirit Award for Thought Provoking Comedy.&nbsp; Jeff is also the author of the bestselling HarperCollins satire &#8220;Get Rich Cheating.&#8221;&nbsp; He has had stops at Princeton, Virginia Law School and in San Francisco.&nbsp; Jeff now lives in New York City.
</p><p>
&#8220;Somebody get Jeff Kreisler on &#8216;The Colbert Report&#8217;&#8221; - The New York Times
&#8220;Hilarious&#8221; - Chicago Tribune
&#8220;Slightly demented&#8221; - San Francisco Chronicle
&#8220;You&#8217;ll be laughing all the way to the bank&#8221; - Rachel Maddow
&#8220;Very funny, very timely&#8221; - Terry Jones of Monty Python
&#8220;Hilarious&#8221; - Flavorpill
&#8220;Laugh out loud - roaring&#8221; - CNBC
&#8220;A really great performer&#8221; - Time Out New York
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Jeff_Kreisler_Color.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Michael Brooks</name>
  <slug>michael-brooks</slug>
  <tag>From HBO's "Def Comedy Jam", BET's "Comic View" and "Showtime at the Apollo"</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>What&#8217;s up world? This is the story of Mike Brooks, comedian/actor. Mike was born and raised in Washington. D.C/ Maryland and knew at an early age that comedy was his gift.&nbsp; Growing up with sisters and no brothers around the house, Mike found comedy wherever was needed. He burst onto the comedy scene in 1996 at a local talent show. Having won second place at the show, he quickly realized that comedy was what he wanted to do in life. He&#8217;s toured all over the east and west coast.&nbsp; You may have seen him on HBO&#8221; Def Comedy Jam,&#8221; &#8220;Comic View&#8221; and P. Diddy&#8217;s &#8220;Bad Boy&#8217;s of Comedy&#8221;.&nbsp; You can also catch Mike in the film &#8220;The Salon&#8221; with Vivica Fox and Terrence Howard. Mike recently filmed a project with Martin Lawrence that was aired on STARZ titled &#8220;The 1st Amendment Comedy Stand- Up&#8221;. He was also the opening act of Martin Lawrence film &#8220;Runteldat.&#8221;&nbsp; Mike has opened for other entertainers such as, Bernie Mac, Dave Chappelle, Monique, Damon Wayans, DL Hughley, Eddie Griffin, Patti Labelle, Maze, Anthony Hamilton and The Isley Brothers, just to name a few. Be on the lookout for this next rising star, Michael Brooks.&nbsp;  
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Michael_Brooks_Stage.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Tammy Pescatelli</name>
  <slug>tammy-pescatelli</slug>
  <tag>From NBC's "Last Comic Standing", Comedy Central and "The Tonight Show with Jay Leno"</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Comedienne Tammy Pescatelli is the kind of woman you wish was your sister or your best friend; she‘s always ready with a good joke or lively quip. Tammy learned her funny skills growing up in a large Italian household outside of Cleveland. 
</p><p>
Tammy balances her family and her growing career with a lot of laughs on WE TV‘s new reality series, &#8220;A Stand Up Mother&#8221; coming this summer. Tammy and her husband moved from Los Angeles to the small town of Meadville, PA to raise their son. The docu-series follows her life as she juggles a career as a stand-up comedienne, being a wife and mother and a large and loud extended family including her mother-in-law.
<p>
On her album, &#8220;It is what it is,&#8221; she uses every bit of her experience to make us laugh about family, religion and even politics; her sister thinks Al Qaeda is a guy from the neighborhood.
<p>
Like a best friend, she also gives us great advice on everything from drinking tips to keeping us grounded: “Just because a man wants to sleep with you doesn‘t mean you‘re sexy. I have brothers that will hump a couch.&#8221; When people ask her, “Where do you get your material?&#8221; Tammy famously replies, “I wake up!“ 
<p>
As one of the Final Five on NBC‘s “Last Comic Standing 2&#8221; Tammy‘s career catapulted and won her a slew of new fans, solidifying her as one of the sharpest women in the comedy world. She just won Comedy Central‘s 2010 &#8220;Stand-Up Showdown&#8221; and has appeared twice as a guest on “The Tonight Show with Jay Leno.“ She has also appeared on National Lampoons “Funny Money,&#8221; NBC‘s “Last Comic Standing: The Best of the Best&#8221; and Comedy Central‘s “The World Stands Up!&#8221; Tammy also recently appeared in her own half-hour special for Comedy Central, “Comedy Central Presents: Tammy Pescatelli.&#8221;&nbsp; She has performed on the “Jerry Lewis Telethon“ several times. More recently, she has performed on “TBS‘s Evening at the Laugh Factory,&#8221; “Last Call with Carson Daly&#8221; and has been a guest a number of times on the syndicated show “Comics Unleashed,&#8221; and was chosen for their “Best of the Best&#8221; world wide top selling DVD!
<p>
She was also featured weekly as part of the “Fashion Police“ panel for US Weekly.&nbsp; Giving pros a run for their money in the poker department, Tammy recently participated in the GSN poker series “Poker Royale: Comedians vs. Pros&#8221;, making it all the way to the finals. She co-stars in the upcoming indie films “Everybody Wants to Be Italian,&#8221; “Single&#8221; and “Made in Brooklyn.&#8221; Most recently, she has been writing for TBS and performing all over the country.
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Tammy_Pescatelli_BWLarge.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Jeff Caldwell</name>
  <slug>jeff-caldwell</slug>
  <tag>From "The David Letterman Show", Comedy Central and ESPN</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Jeff Caldwell is known to audiences nationwide as a clean, clever comedian with one of the brightest standup acts around.
</p><p>
Whether at a comedy club or a corporate event, Jeff delivers smart, funny jokes on topics ranging from the daily news to the daily grind, subtly tailoring his material to fit any crowd.
<p>
CBS got wise to Jeff, scooping him up to develop his own sitcom (which didn&#8217;t get on the air, but that&#8217;s a story for another day). He just made his third appearance on &#8220;The Late Show with David Letterman,&#8221; has made three appearances on &#8220;The Late Late Show with Craig Ferguson&#8221; and made his Comedy Central debut on &#8220;Live at Gotham.&#8221; Jeff has also appeared with Keith Olbermann and Dennis Miller, on SiriusXM Radio.&nbsp; He is also a regular on the nationally syndicated &#8220;Bob and Tom&#8221; radio show.
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Jeff_Caldwell_BW.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Jason Stuart</name>
  <slug>jason-stuart</slug>
  <tag>From "Entourage", "House" and "It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia"</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Jason Stuart has been making people laugh out loud with his hysterical performances all over the country since coming out in 1993. He has accomplished what few other gay comics have ever achieved: humorous brutal honesty about in a world that’s not always kind. Stuart’s material about his experiences as a single Jewish gay man living in Hollywood is original, cutting edge and just plain funny.Not only is Stuart an all-out crowd pleaser, he transcends the boundaries of race, gender and sexual orientation with his edgy comedic style. 
</p><p>
Stuart has performed at all of the top comedy clubs and festivals, hundreds of gay events, colleges and universities and even on Broadway. Since Stuart makes such a strong connection with his audience, he is in high demand by corporate programs with his lecture &#8220;Coming Out In Hollywood&#8221; which is about being openly gay in the workplace. Most recently, he appears in Logo’s new comedy series, &#8220;One Night Stand-Up&#8221;.
<p>
Although his semi-celebrity came via stand-up, Stuart is also well-known for his work as an actor playing gay and straight roles on over forty popular television shows. Stuart has wowed audiences on the TV screen with guest roles in hits such shows as &#8220;The Closer,&#8221; &#8220;Will &amp; Grace,&#8221; &#8220;George Lopez,&#8221; &#8220;Everybody Hates Chris,&#8221; &#8220;House, M.D.,&#8221; &#8220;It&#8217;s Always Sunny in Philadelphia,&#8221; and &#8220;Charmed&#8221;. He is best known playing “Dr. Thomas”, the gay family therapist on &#8220;My Wife and Kids.&#8221;
<p>
As a character actor, filmmakers say his talent is a cross between the depth of Philip Seymour Hoffman, the comedy timing of John Ritter and the quirkiness of Steve Buscemi. He has worked with heavy hitters George Clooney, Faye Dunaway, Angelina Jolie, Damon Wayans, Drew Carey, George Lopez, David Spade and even Arnold Schwarzenegger.&nbsp; Stuart was featured in the comedy hit &#8220;A Day Without a Mexican&#8221; and the HBO award winning drama &#8220;Gia.&#8221;&nbsp; Among the big studio pictures he appeared in, &#8220;Kindergarten Cop&#8221; and &#8220;Vegas Vacation&#8221; are favorites among TV fans.
<p>
Stuart has become a major player in the independent film world after being nominated for a Gay International Film Award for best supporting actor in &#8220;Coffee Date&#8221;. Proving that he is more than just an actor and comedian.&nbsp; Stuart also produced and starred in his own totally improvised independent film &#8220;10 Attitudes&#8221;. This award winning romantic comedy proved to be a huge success both in the U.S. and abroad. In addition to that, he just completed the remake of Edgar Allan Poe’s horror film, &#8220;The Pit &amp; the Pendulum&#8221; where he plays the villain.
<p>
Stuart uses his talents as an openly gay actor and comedian to support the community by performing at countless benefits for issues from AIDS to the homeless. He is the Chairman of the first ever Screen Actors Guild LGBT Committee and also chairs the comedy shows for Lifeworks Mentoring Program.
<p>
Stuart released his stand-up comedy CD, &#8220;Jason Stuart: Gay Comedy Without A Dress&#8221; with great success. His stand-up comedy special, &#8220;Jason Stuart: Making It To The Middle for Here!&#8221; is now available on DVD.
<p>
His groundbreaking stand up comedy and his versatility as an actor make his career an amazing ride.

      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Jason_Stuart_BlackT.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Nick DiPaolo</name>
  <slug>nick-dipaolo</slug>
  <tag>From "Late Night with David Letterman", "The Tonight Show", "The Sopranos" and "Beer League"</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>In this day of watered down comedy, Nick DiPaolo&#8217;s brutally honest performances remind us of what great stand up should be: funny, socially relevant and a little bit reckless. Nick began his career in his hometown of Boston and two-years later, made the jump to New York, where he found his seething, sarcastic style was welcomed with open arms by New York audiences.
</p><p>
Dubbed, the comicʼs comic by his contemporaries, Nickʼs range has allowed him to perform on shows as tame as &#8220;The Tonight Show,&#8221; yet as edgy as HBO&#8217;s &#8220;Young Comedians Special,&#8221; &#8220;Late Night with David Letterman&#8221; and &#8220;Conan OʼBrien.&#8221; He was twice nominated for an Emmy for his writing on &#8220;The Chris Rock Show.&#8221; He has also had three half hour stand up specials of his own on Comedy Central.&nbsp; He was one of the stars on &#8220;Tough Crowd with Colin Quinn&#8221; and a stand out on many Comedy Central &#8220;Roasts.&#8221; His latest effort, is a critically acclaimed one hour Showtime special entitled &#8220;Raw Nerve.&#8221; Not limited to stand-up and writing, he has had guest starring roles on “ Louie,” &#8220;The Sopranos&#8221; and many sitcoms as well as in films including Artie Langeʼs &#8220;Beer League.&#8221; A critic for <em>The Winnepeg Press</em> said it best when he described Nick as, &#8220;Gentle as a starved wolverine and as predictable as a tipsy hopping through a minefield.&nbsp; Nick DiPaolo is an experience constrained only slightly by the demands of stand up comedy.&#8221;
<p>
His strong political opinions have been heard on Foxʼs &#8220;Hannity&#8221;, &#8220;Red Eye&#8221;, &#8220;Fox and Friends&#8221; as well as CNNʼs &#8220;Joy Behar&#8221;. His razor wit also allows him to sub for Dennis Miller as well as Dan Patrick. He is a favorite on both Howard Stern and Opie &amp; Anthony and hosted his own show on New Yorkʼs 92.3 Free FM.&nbsp; Hide the women and children, here comes Nick Di Paolo.
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Riot_Act_Nick_DiPaolo_Wiseguy.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Open Mic</name>
  <slug>open-mic</slug>
  <tag>Amateur and Mainstream Comics, Veteran Hosts, Prizes and Giveaways!</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Every Tuesday is Open Mic Night at Riot Act Comedy Theater, the only comedy club in the area that offers a true open mic and a dedicated place for comics to work on their craft.
</p><p>
Each show begins with a hand full of real first timers cutting the rug in one of their first stage performances ever.  <p>
For the rest of the night enjoy local and national comics who have come to showcase themselves and their new material.  <p>
Every few comics listen for your ticket number for prizes from some of our awesome sponsors.
<p>
Each show hosted by a cagey veteran comic with superhuman MC skills.  <p>
 Wear your sexy Riot Act Comedy Theater T-shirt and receive free admission EVERY Tuesday night and some other shows too!&nbsp; Fashionable and functional!
<p>
Out late?&nbsp; Riot Act will continue to run comics as long as we have people in the seats, so come down, get some laughs and support live comedy!&nbsp; You could be watching the next comedy superstar.&nbsp; 

      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Microphone.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Dick Gregory</name>
  <slug>dick-gregory</slug>
  <tag>Social Activist, Comic and Legend</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Dick Gregory entered the national comedy scene in 1961 when Chicago&#8217;s Playboy Club (as a direct request from publisher Hugh Hefner) booked him as a replacement for white comedian, &#8220;Professor&#8221; Irwin Corey. His tenure as a replacement for Corey was so successful — at one performance he won over an audience that included southern white convention goers — that the Playboy Club offered him a contract extension from several weeks to three years. By 1962 Dick Gregory had become a nationally known headline performer, selling out nightclubs, making numerous national television appearances, and recording popular comedy albums.
</p><p>
It&#8217;s important to note that no biography of Dick Gregory would be complete without mentioning that he and his beloved wife, Lil, had ten kids who have become highly respected members of the national community in a variety of fields. They are: Michele, Lynne, Pamela, Paula, Stephanie (aka Xenobia), Gregory, Christian, Miss, Ayanna and Yohance. The Gregory&#8217;s had one child who died at birth but they have shared 42 years of historic moments, selfless dedication and tremendous personal love.
<p>
From an early age, Dick Gregory demonstrated a strong sense of social justice. While a student at Sumner High School in St. Louis he led a march protesting segregated schools. Later, inspired by the work of leaders such as Dr. Martin Luther King Jr., and organizations such as the Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC), Dick Gregory took part in the Civil Rights Movement and used his celebrity status to draw attention to such issues as segregation and disfranchisement. When local Mississippi governments stopped distributing Federal food surpluses to poor blacks in areas where SNCC was encouraging voter registration, Dick Gregory chartered a plane to bring in several tons of food. He participated in SNCC&#8217;s voter registration drives and in sit-ins to protest segregation, most notably at a restaurant franchise in downtown Atlanta, Georgia.
<p>
Dick Gregory demonstrated his commitment to confronting the entrenched political powers by opposing Richard J. Daley in Chicago&#8217;s 1966 mayoral election. He ran for president in 1968 as a write-in candidate for the Freedom and Peace Party, a splinter group of the Peace and Freedom Party and received 1.5 million votes. Democratic candidate Hubert Humphrey lost the election to Republican Richard Nixon by 510,000 votes, and many believe Humphrey would have won had Dick Gregory not run. After the assassinations of King, President John F. Kennedy, and Robert Kennedy, Dick Gregory became increasingly convinced of the existence of political conspiracies.
<p>
Gregory&#8217;s autobiography &#8220;Nigger&#8221; was published in 1963 prior to the assassination of President Kennedy, and became the number one best-selling book in America. Over the decades it has sold in excess of seven million copies. His choice for the title was explained in the forward, where Dick Gregory wrote a note to his mother. &#8220;Whenever you hear the word &#8216;Nigger&#8217;,&#8221; he said, &#8220;you&#8217;ll know their advertising my book.&#8221;
<p>
Dick Gregory also wrote books such as &#8220;Code Name Zorro: The Murder of Martin Luther King Jr.&#8221; (1971) with Mark Lane, world famous author, attorney and documentary filmmaker, whose findings published in the best-selling 1966 book &#8220;Rush To Judgment&#8221; Gregory credited with reversing the nation&#8217;s opinion on who assassinated the president and the facts which contradicted the official government version contained in the Warren Report. Lane and Gregory have been best friends, co-authors and have lectured together for over 40 years and both live in Washington D.C. Gregory and Lane&#8217;s book on the assassination of Dr. King was recently released under another title, &#8220;Murder In Memphis&#8221;, as a trade paperback.
<p>
Dick Gregory&#8217;s activism continued into the 1990s. In response to published allegations that the Central Intelligence Agency (CIA) had supplied cocaine to predominantly African American areas in Los Angeles, thus spurring the crack epidemic, Gregory protested at CIA headquarters and was arrested. In 1992 he began a program called &#8216;Campaign for Human Dignity&#8217; to fight crime in St. Louis neighborhoods.
<p>
In 1996, he returned to the stage in his critically acclaimed one-man show &#8220;Dick Gregory Live!&#8221; The reviews of Gregory&#8217;s show compared him to the greatest stand-ups in the history of Broadway.
<p>
In 1998, Dick Gregory spoke at the celebration of the birthday of Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr. and President Clinton were in attendance. Not long after that, the President told
Gregory&#8217;s long-time friend and public relations consultant Steve Jaffe, &#8220;I love Dick Gregory, he is one of the funniest people on the planet.&#8221;
<p>
In 2001, Dick Gregory announced to the world that he had been diagnosed with a rare form of cancer. He refused traditional medical treatment – chemotherapy –and with the assistance of some of the finest minds in alternative medicine, put together a regimen of a variety of diet, vitamins, exercise, and modern devices not even known to the public, which ultimately resulted in his reversing the trend of the cancer to the point where today he is 100% cancer free. Dick Gregory&#8217;s going public with his diagnosis has helped millions of his fans around the world to understand what cancer specialists have been trying to explain for decades, which is that &#8220;Cancer is curable.&#8221;
<p>
Dick Gregory was honored recently at the Kennedy Center in Washington D.C., by a sold out house and a tribute hosted by Bill Cosby, with special tributes by Mrs. Martin Luther King Jr., Stevie Wonder, Isaac Hayes, Cicely Tyson, Mark Lane, Marion Barry and many more.
<p>
Dick Gregory&#8217;s most recent book &#8220;Callus On My Soul&#8221;, which became a best-seller within weeks of publication, is an autobiography that updates his earlier autobiography, &#8220;Nigger&#8221;, because as Dick says, &#8220;I&#8217;ve lived long enough to need two autobiographies which is fine with me. I&#8217;m looking forward to writing the third and fourth volumes as well.&#8221;
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Dick_Gregory_Newspaper.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Tony Woods</name>
  <slug>tony-woods</slug>
  <tag>From "Comedy Central Presents", Conan O'Brien and "P. Diddy's Bad Boys of Comedy" </tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Tony Woods is a one-of-a-kind comedic legend that is always in control of his audience.&nbsp; A seasoned veteran in the comedy business, Tony is recognized not only by fans but by his peers as one of the best and most engaging comedians in the business.
</p><p>
Tony has a strong following in the US, UK, Australia and Europe. Born in North Carolina and raised in the D.C. area, Woods kicked off his career as an original member of Russell Simmons&#8217; &#8220;Def Comedy Jam&#8221; on HBO and P. Diddy&#8217;s &#8220;Bad Boys of Comedy&#8221;, he is an all-round veteran and one-of-a-kind comic. His playful and cool demeanor, combined with sharp and mischievous subject matter, create a show that is unmistakably entertaining at every level. A natural entertainer, Woods understands an audience and encourages them to become part of his strange world.
 <p>
Tony’s recent appearances: Comedy Central Presents Tony Woods, Comedy Central USO Tour, and Comedy Central World Comedy Tour have made him a comic favorite of international renown. He has also appeared on &#8220;Last Comic Standing&#8221;, A&amp;E’s &#8220;Caroline’s Comedy Hour&#8221;, &#8220;Showtime at the Apollo&#8221;, NBC’s &#8220;Friday Night Videos&#8221;, &#8220;Just for Laughs&#8221;, &#8220;NYPD Blue&#8221;, &#8220;HACK&#8221;, &#8220;Late Night with Conan O&#8217;Brien&#8221;, &#8220;HBO Comedy Spot&#8221; and Australia&#8217;s &#8220;The Footy Show&#8221;.
<p>

Woods has also appeared in the film &#8220;The Brooklyn Project&#8221; and his festival appearances include triumphs at the Just For Laughs Comedy Festival in Montreal, the HBO U.S. Comedy Arts Festival in Aspen, Colorado, the Melbourne Comedy Festival and is a favorite at the Sydney Comedy Festival.

 <p>

&#8220;Tony&#8217;s cool demeanor and sharp delivery provide sublime comedic entertainment. Satisfaction guaranteed.&#8221; - Chortle.co.uk 
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Tony_Woods.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Charles Fleischer</name>
  <slug>charles-fleischer</slug>
  <tag>Comic Genius and the voice of Roger Rabbit!</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>A Washington D.C. native, Fleischer is reported to have spent several summers at Kamp Kewanee in La Plume, Pennsylvania, where he started practicing his stand-up routine at age nine. He attended Southampton College of Long Island University and studied acting at Chicago&#8217;s Goodman Theatre. He moved to Los Angeles in 1970 to pursue his comedy career.
</p><p>
His stand-up routines are known for their intelligent and unusual bent, discussing such obscure topics as merkins and his mathematical formula, &#8220;moleeds.&#8221; He has a knack for voices and manic facial expressions reminiscent of a mad scientist.
<p>
He is best known as the voices of Roger Rabbit, Benny The Cab, Psycho and Greasy in Disney and Amblin Entertainment&#8217;s 1988 live action/animated hybrid film &#8220;Who Framed Roger Rabbit&#8221;. After that film&#8217;s success, Fleischer continued to perform the voice of Roger in several Disney television and theme park appearances at several of the Walt Disney Parks and Resorts in three follow-up short subjects to the original film. Other voice roles for Fleischer include &#8220;The Polar Express&#8221; and &#8220;We&#8217;re Back! A Dinosaur&#8217;s Story&#8221;. On-screen roles include &#8220;Back to the Future Part II&#8221; and &#8220;Gridlock&#8217;d&#8221;.
<p>
Fleischer has had numerous roles on many TV shows through the years including a recurring role on the 1970s hit TV series &#8220;Welcome Back, Kotter&#8221; as Carvelli, as Chuck on the hit ABC series &#8220;Laverne &amp; Shirley&#8221; and on the popular Disney cartoon series &#8220;House of Mouse&#8221; as the voice of Benny The Cab. He guest starred in &#8220;The Weird Al Show&#8221; as a guy in a band. He also appeared on the short lived Saturday morning show &#8220;Wacko&#8221;.
<p>
He is also a musician and songwriter. He performed as a guest on harmonica with the group Blues Traveler at the Wiltern Theater in Los Angeles on November 22, 1995.
<p>
Fleischer is now the part-owner of a multi-media company in Southern California and a writer for TV and movies. Since December 2010 he is hosting his own weekly web-show Fleischer&#8217;s Universe on Ustream.tv produced by Brad Wyman.



      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Charles_Fleischer_Blue.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Alycia Cooper</name>
  <slug>alycia-cooper</slug>
  <tag>From Comedy Central, NBC, BET and "The Mo'Nique Show"</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Stand-up Comedienne Alycia Cooper is a force to be reckoned with. She is a headlining comic who performs on national television shows and is a huge hit on the college circuit. 
</p><p>
Alycia recently became the first female comic to perform on “The Mo’Nique Show,” hosted by Oscar Award winner, Mo’Nique. She has been a featured comic on NBC’s “America’s Got Talent,” BET&#8217;s &#8220;Comicview,&#8221; Comedy Central&#8217;s &#8220;Wanda Does It,&#8221; “Byron Allen’s Comics Unleashed,” “The Gossip Queens” on Logo, several VH-1 clips shows and BET&#8217;s &#8220;Oh Drama.&#8221; She recently played a feisty bus driver in the short, independent movie, &#8220;Knocked Down,” and appeared as Dana, the corrections officer, in the pilot episode of the hit NBC comedy, “Raising Hope.” She is currently touring the country performing comedy, while trying to sell her version of Kathy Griffin’s D List, about her life as a struggling comic trying to “make it” in the rough and tumble world of entertainment.
<p>
Alycia has written for &#8220;The Steve Harvey Morning Show&#8221;, TV One’s hit sitcom, “Love That Girl,” Executive Produced by Martin Lawrence and Bentley Evans, and UPN’s hit sitcom, “The Parker’s.”&nbsp; She holds the title of the &#8220;first female audience &#8216;warm-up&#8217; person for several sitcoms; including &#8220;The Parker&#8217;s,&#8221; “Girlfriends,” “Wanda at Large,” and “The Tyra Banks Show.” In May of 2004, she was featured in “Essence Magazine” as one to watch! She also performs for the troops overseas.

      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Alycia_Cooper.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Rob Cantrell</name>
  <slug>rob-cantrell</slug>
  <tag>From NBC's "Last Comic Standing"</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Rob Cantrell has appeared on several major networks including CBS, NBC, HBO and COMEDY CENTRAL. He performs all over the world, most recently at the “Bonnaroo Music Festival”, SXSW and the “High Times Cannabis Cup in Amsterdam”. Rob is currently acting in the play &#8220;The MARIJUANA-LOGUES&#8221; and is a contributing writer to “HIGH TIMES MAGAZINE”. He has acted in promos for &#8220;FLIGHT OF THE CONCORDS&#8221; and written video shorts for &#8220;HOWARDTV&#8221;, Howard Stern&#8217;S ON-DEMAND channel. Rob was born in WASHINGTON DC and spent part of his childhood in southern Virgina. Cantrell first started performing stand-up comedy in coffee shops in San Francisco, CA over ten years ago. He now lives in Brooklyn, NY with his wife and 14 “Imperial Poodles”.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Rob_Cantrell_Color_Grey.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Allah Made Me Funny</name>
  <slug>allah-made-me-funny</slug>
  <tag>Sold Out On All 7 Continents</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Allah Made Me Funny Comedy Tour: The concept of this tour is to make a comprehensive effort to provide effective, significant, and appropriate comedy with an Islamic perspective, which is both mainstream and cross-cultural.
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Allah_Logo_Orange.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Todd Rexx</name>
  <slug>todd-rexx</slug>
  <tag></tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>For over a decade, Todd Rex aka T-Rexx has been a natural who quickly wins over any audience with his cunning wit, over the top impersonations and brilliant crowd interaction.&nbsp; His on stage antics, accompanied by his twisted imagination, create a comedic concoction that captivates audiences, literally leaving them rolling in the aisles, crying for more.&nbsp; If you’re in the market for a new generation comedian, then look no further!&nbsp; Todd is a true disciple of alternative comedy, who applies his sheer talent and genius to create an off center style of comedy comprised of a mixed bag of personal experience, everyday observations, and hypothetical situations to connect with any audience.
</p><p>
Born in Long Branch, New Jersey, Todd was adopted at birth and immediately scurried to his new home in Cleveland Heights, Ohio, a multi-cultural artsy suburb of Cleveland. There he attended different schools and at each one, to the dismay of his parents, quickly established himself as the “class clown”. When Todd was ten, he and his family moved to Silver Spring, Maryland, where he continued to “bless” classrooms with impersonations, sound effects, jokes, and comedic antics that not only classmates would laugh at, but teachers and staff as well. His classroom comedy continued through junior high, high school, and two years of junior college(basically 13th grade) where he studied television production. In 1992, after encouragement from friends and family, Todd finally brought his talents to the stage at “The Comedy Café” in Washington, D.C., and hasn’t looked back since. Todd prides himself with being able to connect with any audience presented to him. He credits his multi-cultural surroundings growing up, coupled with the fact that he was a bi-racial child adopted by a caucasian family for being able to transcend barriers and truly entertain all.
<p>
Todd’s comedic exploits have taken him to Europe, Japan, Canada, Mexico, U.S. Virgin Islands, as well as coast to coast nationally, touching almost every state in the union.&nbsp; He has worked with Jerry Seinfeld, David Alan Grier, Dane Cook, D.L. Hughley, Bernie Mac, Russell Peters, Gilbert Godfrey, Dave Chappelle, and Tommy Davidson; the list goes on and on, but why stop there? Todd has also done crowd warm up at Sony Studios, Los Angeles, for the sit-com, “Between Brothers”, tours with Bill Bellamy, and performs at the Darryl Armstrong (New Orleans Hornets) Foundation for Premature Babies’ annual Charity event.
<p>
Todd’s talents have not been limited to live performances, however. Todd has made numerous television appearances, including BET’s Comicview(1994-2005), Tonight show with Jay Leno(1995), HBO’s Def Comedy Jam all-stars(1996), Comedy Factory (Netherlands, 2001-2005), Raymond is Late (Netherlands, 2002), Rumbles (HDNet, 2004), Baggin’ (VH1 2005). He has also appeared in such films as,”The Fear Chamber”(Night Light Films, 2007) “Premonitions” (Latte Stone Films, 2005); NTV (Grifftyme Prods 2005); “I’ll be back”, an industrial film for DeVry institute (Hope Prods., 1995), “Love Jones” (Newline Cinema, 1995), “For the Love of Money (Pee-Air Prods. 2002). He currently is a card carrying member of S.A.G. as well as AFTRA. 
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Todd_Rexx_Red.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Otto And George</name>
  <slug>otto-and-george</slug>
  <tag>From The Late Show with David Letterman, Opie &amp; Anthony and "The Aristocrats"</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>No matter what you think you&#8217;re seen or heard before, you have never seen anything as outrageous as the legendary Otto &amp; George. Within seconds of hitting the stage, Otto&#8217;s mannequin George comes to life with a explosive barrage of insults, bad taste and pontifications about life that would even make a truck driver blush. He&#8217;ll lay waste to every politically correct social precept, the first two rows of those in the audience and anyone daring enough to get up to go to the bathroom. When Otto &amp; George co-hosted the Porno Awards in Las Vegas, they were later told that he offended the people in attendance. Now that&#8217;s extreme.
</p><p>
Otto is a regular closing act at Caroline&#8217;s on Broadway, The Riviera in Las Vegas, and every major comedy club in the country. He was a featured performer on Showtime&#8217;s &#8220;Comedy&#8217;s Dirtiest Dozen,&#8221; Penn &amp; Teller&#8217;s TV Specials, Penn &amp; Teller’s Bullsh*t, The Playboy Channel, HBO, The Aristocrats (Movie) and most recently on The Late Show with David Letterman. Everyone loves Otto &amp; George it is not uncommon to see movie, TV, and other nationally known celebrities in the audience of an Otto &amp; George show. Some of Otto&#8217;s big fans are Opie &amp; Anthony and The King of All Media himself, Howard Stern. Once when Otto &amp; George were working in Chicago, comedy genius George Carlin attended Otto&#8217;s show, saying that he had heard about Otto for years and just had to make time to come see him. Mr. Carlin later said that the one hour ride to see Otto was well worth the trip and that he loved Otto&#8217;s work and bold approach to stand up comedy. Otto and George&#8217;s truly tasteless and twisted comedy is a no holds barred show. If you like your comedy completely over the line, this is a must see!

      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Otto_George_Color2.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Will Durst</name>
  <slug>will-durst</slug>
  <tag></tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>As the sacred cows routinely paint targets on their foreheads practically begging for someone to puncture their pomposity, America cries out for a man with the aim, strength, and style to hit them where it hurts the funniest. Will Durst is that man. Sweeping both sides of the aisle with a quiver full of arrows dipped in common sense, Durst transcends party ties, having performed at events honoring former Presidents Bill Clinton and George HW Bush as well as acclaimed appearances at both a Mayors Convention and Governors Conference. 
</p><p>
Outraged and outrageous, Durst is as current as today’s headlines, as accurate as a sniper, and universally acknowledged by even his peers as the nation’s foremost political comic.
<p>
Although a prolific writer, he professes little need for material, having it regularly delivered at 7:00 a.m. every morning in the five papers he reads daily. Busier than a blind squirrel neck deep in an almond sorting warehouse, Durst is a regular commentator for audible.com, Air America, CNN and NPR, writes a nationally syndicated op- ed column, daily website jokes—yet still finds time to perform hundreds of comedy shows every year—at clubs, corporate events, theaters and benefits…not to mention the occasional acting and voice-over role. 
<p>
Reigning as C-SPAN’s favorite comic (8 appearances,) Durst is a 5-time Emmy nominee and recipient of 7 consecutive nominations for the American Comedy Awards Stand Up of the Year. He is the first comic invited to perform at Harvard’s Kennedy School of Government and the first American to be nominated for the prestigious Perrier Award at the Edinburgh Fringe Festival for the show “Myth America.” He has racked up more than 400 television appearances in 14 different countries while slinging jokes around the globe in his one man crusade to make people laugh out loud on purpose against their will. Hobbies include the never-ending quest for the perfect cheeseburger, while his heroes remain the same as when he was twelve—Thomas Jefferson and Bugs Bunny.
<p>
Will Durst’s performances are made possible by the First Amendment.
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Will_Durst_Wall.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Judy Gold</name>
  <slug>judy-gold</slug>
  <tag>Emmy Award Winning Actress and Comedian</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Emmy Award winning actress and comedian, Judy Gold is best known as the star of the critically acclaimed long-running Off Broadway hit show 25 Questions for a Jewish Mother, for which she was nominated for a 2006 Drama Desk Award for Outstanding Solo Performance. In addition, the show won the 2007 GLAAD Award for &#8220;Outstanding New York Theater.&#8221; The New York Times called this one-woman show &#8220;fiercely funny, honest and moving.&#8221;&nbsp; A book based on the show was nominated for the prestigious Quill Award. Judy&#8217;s new show, &#8220;It&#8217;s Judy&#8217;s Show - My Life As A Sitcom&#8221; debuted to rave reviews in Washington DC and was featured at this year&#8217;s Williamstown Theatre Festival to more rave reviews. 
</p><p>
&nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp; Most recently, Judy has been in the cast of Nora &amp; Delia Ephron&#8217;s Off-Broadway play, &#8220;Love, Loss and What I Wore.&#8221; Gold can be seen regularly on Tru TV&#8217;s &#8220;The Smoking Gun Presents.&#8221; She has guest-hosted ABC&#8217;s &#8220;The View&#8221; - where she has appeared numerous times, and appears regularly on &#8220;The Joy Behar Show&#8221; on CNN. Judy recently appeared on &#8220;The Wendy Williams Show&#8221; and &#8220;Dr. Oz.&#8221; She was the host of HBO&#8217;s &#8220;At the Multiplex with Judy Gold&#8221; from 1999 - 2009, and Judy also hosted Comedy Central&#8217;s &#8220;100 Greatest Stand-ups of All Time&#8221; and the GLAAD MEDIA AWARDS, which aired on LOGO and VH1. Her TV specials include a half-hour comedy special for LOGO and she is featured in the HBO documentary, &#8220;All Aboard&#8221;. 
<p>
&nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp; Her stand-up specials include &#8220;Comedy Central Presents: Judy Gold&#8221;, Comedy Central&#8217;s &#8220;Tough Crowd Stands Up&#8221;, and Judy&#8217;s HBO half-hour special, which received a Cable Ace Award. Gold was seen in the smash hit film &#8220;The Aristocrats&#8221; and the documentaries &#8220;Making Trouble&#8221; and &#8220;I Am Comic&#8221;. Gold won two Emmy Awards for writing and producing &#8220;The Rosie O&#8217;Donnell Show.&#8221; She was nominated twice for The American Comedy Award&#8217;s Funniest Female Stand-Up. Judy has written for Wondertime Magazine, Momlogic.com and The Advocate. She has also appeared on &#8220;Ugly Betty,&#8221; &#8220;Law &amp; Order,&#8221; &#8220;Law &amp; Order SVU,&#8221; &#8220;Hollywood Squares&#8221;, &#8220;The Tonight Show with Jay Leno,&#8221; and &#8220;The Conan O&#8217;Brien Show&#8221;</strong> to name a few. Gold lives in New York City with her two children. She frequently tours theaters and comedy clubs around the country. 
<p>
&nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp; Her CD, &#8220;Judith&#8217;s Roommate Had a Baby&#8221; is currently available. 
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/judy_umbrellas.png</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Don Jamieson</name>
  <slug>don-jamieson</slug>
  <tag></tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>“He’s a sarcastic, caustic rib-splitter who can wind up any audience and splatter them hysterically” – The Village Voice
</p><p>
Don is currently co-hosting VH1 Classic’s hit heavy metal talk show series, &#8220;That Metal Show&#8221;. The program is a round-table talk show where legends of rock hang out and discuss their past and current projects in front of a live studio audience full of metal maniacs. Rolling Stone Magazine just dubbed &#8220;That Metal Show&#8221; one of the 50 Best Reasons to Watch TV!
<p>
Among his many accomplishments, comedian Don Jamieson’s proudest moment was becoming an Emmy Award-Winner for his work on HBO’s &#8220;Inside the NFL&#8221;. During that season Don and long-time comedy partner Jim Florentine lent their brand of humor to the popular sports show by writing, producing and performing sports-themed comedy sketches for the show.
<p>
The two have also collaborated on the hidden-camera DVD and Comedy Central web series,&#8220;Meet the Creeps&#8221; as well as a series of prank call CD’s, &#8220;Terrorizing Telemarketers&#8221;, which get a lot of airplay on &#8220;The Howard Stern Radio Show&#8221;. He is also a joke writer for the country’s best celebrity roaster, Lisa Lampanelli and has lent his voice to MTV2′s &#8220;Crank Yankers&#8221;.
<p>
Don’s stand-up act brings his everyday take on life, the hip, the cool and the tragically sublime into the spotlight. Besides performing at clubs in New York City, Don tears it up at clubs and theaters all over the country. For the last four years, he has been the regular opener for Andrew Dice Clay. His reputation as one of New York City’s top comics was cemented when he was asked to perform live on ABC’s &#8220;Good Morning America&#8221;.
<p>
Don started his career as one of the young and talented comedy minds at MTV helping to launch the careers of comics like Jon Stewart, Kevin James, Pauly Shore (sorry) and Tom Green, but unbeknownst to many, Don was spending his nights on the local comedy scene developing his own comic style.
<p>
Making the transition from comedian to television host isn’t easy for most. Don has hosted his own series, &#8220;OLN’s Beach Ambush&#8221;, and is currently in production for the SEVENTH season of VH1 Classic’s, &#8220;That Metal Show&#8221;.
<p>
Enter 2010: Don Jamieson inked a deal with legendary metal label Metal Blade Records to release the comedian’s debut stand-up comedy album. The album, titled Live and Hilarious, was filmed during Don’s performance at Bar Anticipation in Lake Como, NJ on January 30 and will be released in 2011. When asked about why he chose Jersey as the location for his performance for the upcoming stand-up album, Don had this to say; “I’m a Jersey boy and there’s nowhere better to record my first ever live comedy CD than good old Dirty Jerz! Malls, mullets and metal!!”
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Don-Jamieson-publicity-photo.jpeg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Jim Florentine</name>
  <slug>jim-florentine</slug>
  <tag></tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Jim Florentine is the current host of &#8220;That Metal Show&#8221; on VH-1.&nbsp; Florentine has also been seen on The Apprentice, Comedy Central&#8217;s Mother Load, HBO&#8217;s Inside the NFL, Late Late Show with Craig Kilborn, The Opie and Anthony Show, The Howard Stern Show, Spike TV&#8217;s Video Game Awards, MTV Music Video Awards, Jimmy Kimmel Live, Last Call with Carson Daly, Tough Crowd with Colin Quinn on Comedy Central, VH1&#8217;s The List, and Louie Anderson&#8217;s Comedy Showcase. He also voiced the redneck radio host Bobbie Ray in the video game Grand Theft Auto: Vice City Stories.
</p><p>
He has a series of prank call CDs known as Terrorizing Telemarketers Volumes 1-5.&nbsp; The CDs feature a series of recorded telephone conversations, often with Florentine receiving calls from telemarketers, wherein he turns the tables on often aggressive salespeople by being deliberately difficult and creating awkward situations.
<p>
In 2004, he worked one season on HBO&#8217;s Inside the NFL performing various comedy sketches. The show won an Emmy that season and Florentine has proudly said in various interviews that when he was single he kept it on his night stand and it would close the deal anytime he had a date over. He called it his &#8220;Mariano Rivera&#8221;.
<p>
At the same time, Florentine released two hidden camera DVDs called Meet The Creeps where he and his partner Don Jamieson pull outrageous pranks on people. The DVD has got in the hands of some Comedy Central executives and they brought Meet The Creeps to their broadband channel called Motherload. After the two successful seasons, Comedy Central did a Meet The Creeps pilot for the network. The pilot was deemed too mean spirited and the show never made it on the network.
<p>
Between 2004 and 2008, he made 3 appearances on Jimmy Kimmel Live! on ABC. He also appeared on The Late Late Show with Craig Kilborn. In 2007, Florentine appeared on the last episode of The Apprentice in season 4 doing his edgy stand-up comedy at a conservative charity event. He asked Trump&#8217;s partner George if he wears a diaper. He has not been asked back on the apprentice since.
<p>
He is an occasional guest on the late-night Fox News Channel show Red Eye w/ Greg Gutfeld.
<p>
Later in 2010, Florentine appeared in the feature film A Little Help as Brian.
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Jim-Florentine.jpeg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Paul Mooney</name>
  <slug>paul-mooney</slug>
  <tag>From "The Chappelle Show", head writer for Richard Pryor and Redd Foxx, Emmy nominee</tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Mr. Mooney&#8217;s most recent appearances have been on BET&#8217;s &#8220;Top 25 Most @#%!* Moments in Black History&#8221;, TV Land and &#8220;The Dave Chappelle Show&#8221;, where he is known as the infamous &#8220;Negrodamus.&#8221;&nbsp; Mr. Mooney was also the head writer for Richard Pryor and Redd Foxx in addition to being the lead writer for &#8220;In Living Color&#8221; on which he created &#8216;Homie the Clown&#8217;.&nbsp; His other television writing credits include episodes of &#8220;Good Times&#8221;, &#8220;Sanford and Son&#8221;, &#8220;Saturday Night Live&#8221;, &#8220;The Richard Pryor Show&#8221;, and &#8220;Roseanne&#8221; among others.&nbsp; 
</p><p>
Mr. Mooney is also credited with writing on such films as &#8220;Richard Pryor Live on the Sunset Strip&#8221;, &#8220;JoJo Dancer&#8221; and Ice Cube and Chris Tucker&#8217;s &#8220;Friday&#8221;.&nbsp; In addition he has also made appearances in films &#8220;Bustin&#8217; Loose&#8221;, &#8220;Hollywood Shuffle&#8221; and &#8220;Bamboozled.&#8221; He&#8217;s made numerous television appearances including &#8220;Soul Train,&#8221;&nbsp; &#8220;The Oprah Winfrey Show,&#8221; and &#8220;Politically Incorrect.&#8221; Mr. Mooney has been nominated for an Emmy for his writing on &#8220;Pryor&#8217;s Place&#8221; as well as a Grammy.
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Mooney_Hands.jpg</photo>
</artist>

 <artist>
  <name>Big Al Goodwin</name>
  <slug>big-al-goodwin</slug>
  <tag></tag>
  <bio>
      <![CDATA[
        <p>&#8216;My friends call me Big Al, the Sears catalog calls me husky&#8217;</p>

<p>Allan Goodwin is one of the funniest and respected comics on the circuit today. Creative and loveable, Al can do any room anywhere, anytime. A comedy veteran of more than 15 years, Allan has worked in almost every area of the country on every level from corporations to house parties to Bar Mitzvahs. Al&#8217;s strength comes from his ability to connect with people and appreciate the lighter side of their own lives through his observations and material.</p>

<p>Allan was a winner on &#8220;America&#8217;s Funniest People&#8221;, has been seen on &#8220;The Billy Bush Show&#8221;, numerous commercials on PBS and even an appearance on &#8220;The Bottom Line&#8221; with Qweisi Mfume. Having played almost every club and college in the country, Al recently made the step up to the theaters opening for Dave Chappelle, Wayne Brady and Steven Wright on their most recent tours. Another sign that Al is about to hit the big time was his recent admittance into New York&#8217;s Friar&#8217;s Club in recognition of his comedy achievements and dedication to his craft.</p>

<p>Last year Al was one of only 21 comics chosen from around the country for HBO&#8217;s &#8220;Lucky 21 Contest&#8221; in Las Vegas.</p>

<p>
</p>
      ]]>


  </bio>
  <photo>/assets/uploads/comedians/Has_anybody_seen_my_act_before.jpeg</photo>
</artist>

</artists>